<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voice on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voice on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Build memorable responsive Real-Time Communications Widgets.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</guid>
      <description>There’s no question that live chat is getting huge. More and more, websites in every corner of the web are featuring that inviting little widget in the corner of their screens. Live chat support is a huge opportunity for businesses to add a powerful, customer-loved channel to their customer service strategy.
We do not understand Live Chat just for texting. From the beginning, our Live Chat Widgets have been designed to provide Text, Voice and Video at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Dialer · Escalating Text, Voice, Video.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons In the Digital Age, any business has to create the most advanced interactions with their customers. Add text, voice, and video chat to your business without reinventing communications and complexity. At Interactive powers, we understand business communications in real-time with a flexible, multi-channel and convergent approach that has to work on any device, any modern browser, any location or Internet access.
Text Chat Some online businesses requires to make the first step enabling a text chat conversation for any device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>