<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technology on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/technology/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technology on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/technology/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Video-Audio SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint comes into Video Gateway (WebRTC | RTMP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins.
WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>A WebRTC system can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>