<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>videoid on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in videoid on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Web Browser Standard for an universal Password-free sign-in</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A new web standard makes it possible to sign into virtually any web service without needing a password!  This Authentication standard from W3C will use your fingerprint reader or inside camera in a wide variety of web browsers. That, in turn, lets you access virtually any online service in a PC or mobile device through password-free FIDO Authentication, not just specific services. You can continue to use familiar biometrics methods like fingerprint readers, cameras and USB keys, and it can serve both in place of and in addition to passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video ID</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 09:52:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-id/</guid>
      <description>Protect your Real-Time Communications with Secure Identification API integrations.  Overview Video ID feature helps you to improve security in your real-time communication services. Our solutions include partner options for ID Verification through an external provider certified API. This capability enables to comply with identity verification processes required, for instance, by banks, insurances, e-commerces or telemedicine.
Video ID functionality captures and validates users’ information, whilst conducting a real-time check. Video ID capability is a set of API, which can optionally include Facial Recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economist: Visual Recognition with &#39;Deep Learning&#39; is suparsing Humans for First Time</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Visual Recognition Algorithms reach an accuracy of 96% with &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning&amp;rdquo; The rehabilitation of “AI”, and the current excitement about the field, can be traced back to 2012 and an online contest called the ImageNet Challenge. ImageNet is an online database of millions of images, all labelled by hand. For any given word, such as “balloon” or “strawberry”, ImageNet contains several hundred images.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
