<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>videorec on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videorec/</link>
    <description>Recent content in videorec on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videorec/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Transactional Video Calls: Revolutionizing Virtual Interactions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/transactional-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Feb 2024 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/transactional-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Desktop Transactional Video Call Embracing Enhanced Video Capabilities in the Shift Towards Modern Business Communications In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, remote communication has become ubiquitous, underscoring the importance of robust and feature-rich video calling platforms. Amidst the myriad options available, Transactional Video Calls shine as a transformative solution, seamlessly integrating with ACD (Automatic Call Distributor) platforms in any IP Contact Center. This integration marks a significant advancement, offering a comprehensive suite of features specifically crafted to address the evolving needs of modern communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suite 2024 Updates</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/suite-2024-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/suite-2024-updates/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Getting started&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce the latest enhancements and advancements across our suite of platforms and solutions for the 2024 roadmap. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of what&amp;rsquo;s our evolution and changes:
New Roadmap 2024 Video RTC (Real-Time Communications) v5.x Our 5th generation flagship platform of Video RTC continues to deliver unparalleled stability, ensuring smoother and more reliable communication experiences than ever before.
Video REC (Video Call Recording) v1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
