<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Updates on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/updates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Updates on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/updates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR v13.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 13.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 13.1:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>