<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to Customer Experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of Video Chat:
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Currently, Bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.
A large number of different businesses could benefit from offering Live Video Chat services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>