<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Human: The Crucial Factor of CX</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-crucial-role-of-human-in-cx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-crucial-role-of-human-in-cx/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik Beyond automation: The best customer experience, lies in an authentic and human interaction. While Artificial Intelligence (AI) tools can provide speed, efficiency and convenience, they lack sufficient empathy, a full emotional understanding of the customer to take nuanced decisions that humans possess. Face-to-Face conversations bring a personal touch, better connection and adaptability that are essential for fostering trust and building customer effective transactions for businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Communications for Tourism &amp; Hostelry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/embracing-video-calls-over-traditional-communication-tourism-industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/embracing-video-calls-over-traditional-communication-tourism-industry/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons The Future in Hostelry: Embracing Video Calls Over Traditional Communication for the Tourism Industry In an era where connectivity shapes our interactions and experiences, the tourism and Hostelry industry must actively participate in the Digital Revolution. One of the transformative tools in the evolution of more humane customer care is the use of direct transactional video calls. Beyond mere convenience, integrating video calls into the fabric of hotel and tourism services offers a myriad of benefits that transcend traditional communications methods like phone numbers, chats, toll free calls&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transforming Car Dealerships with Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/transforming-car-dealerships-with-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2024 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/transforming-car-dealerships-with-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Expanding Sales Opportunities: How Video Calls Empower Car Dealers to Connect Beyond the Showroom Floor In today’s rapidly evolving automotive industry, car dealerships are continually seeking innovative ways to enhance customer experiences and drive sales. One transformative solution gaining momentum is the integration of video calls into dealership operations. Here are several compelling reasons why car dealers should consider adopting video calls:
1. Quick Personalized Vehicle Consultations Video calls enable car dealerships to offer personalized vehicle consultations to customers, allowing them to explore different car models, features, and options from the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep your Business connected Everywhere</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/keep-your-business-always-connected-everywhere/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 10:30:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/keep-your-business-always-connected-everywhere/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Enhancing Customer Engagement with Video Calls In today&amp;rsquo;s fast-paced and interconnected world, maintaining meaningful connections with customers is paramount for businesses. One powerful tool that enables businesses to stay connected with customers regardless of location is video calls. In this post, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how businesses can leverage video calls to enhance customer engagement and foster stronger relationships.
1. Outstanding Customer Care Experience Video calls provide businesses with a platform to deliver the most personalized customer experiences that go beyond traditional communication methods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Retail Success through Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Six key reasons to consider adding real-time video calling support to your retail business with or without online store. In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, video calls are not just a means of meetings or scheduled communications; they&amp;rsquo;re a powerful tool for transforming the retail landscape. Here&amp;rsquo;s how integrating video calls can significantly boost the success of retail businesses:
1. More Personalized Customer Service Video calls enable retailers to offer personalized customer service experiences from the comfort of a customer&amp;rsquo;s home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Business Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Leading companies have a wholeness approach about how to communicate better with customers across their processes. Communicate is a top priority for businesses today — but how can you quantify its value to your organization? That’s especially important in these times, with businesses managing the economic impact and uncertainty of disruptive events, and how this will impact both their customers and employees going forward. The History of Business Communications is, of course, closely linked with the histories of Communications itself and that of Business Operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Dialer, Click-to-Call</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-dialer-click-to-call-reloaded-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:12:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-dialer-click-to-call-reloaded-copy/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Make calls from any Web Browser. From now, phone numbers are no longer required. In today’s increasingly digital world, customers have come to favor online service options available from the convenience of their screen. From chatbots and self-service features to digitally connecting to a live agent with a simple button click, companies aim to deliver a digital customer experience that is personal, seamless, quick, and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Reasons why you should add Video channels to your Contact Center (ES)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-contact-center-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-contact-center-infographic/</guid>
      <description>Infographic source: Interactive Powers. Download in PDF.
Summary: Spanish
Mejorar la Comunicación entre agente y usuario. Incrementar la Valoración de la atención prestada. Aumentar la Eficiencia en la resolución de incidencias. Usar Dispositivos digitales móviles o navegadores web. Ofrecer nuevas capacidades de Colaboración en línea. Mejorar la Seguridad con la verificación visual de identidad. Eliminar la Numeración telefónica nacional o internacional. Ofrecer una Experiencia del cliente más próxima a la presencial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 most popular blog posts in 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Freepik Creative Commons. Video Real-Time Communications and Voicebot IVR were key themes during this 2020. The most viewed posts in our blog this year are following some important updates of this challenging year. To prepare 2021, we share this TOP 10 list:
1- What is a STUN/TURN server (TOP) The best description of what is a STUN/TURN server you where looking for… https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/
2- Video RTC - Web Browsers support in 2020!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Customer Experience to the Next Level</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/taking-customer-experience-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/taking-customer-experience-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Businesses require to improve CX in a new way. Video has never been so relevant for all of us. Interactive Powers helps businesses bring their human-to-human interactions to the digital world with scalable, flexible and secure video communications. Video RTC with SPLIT technology is a key differentiator for any ACD (Automatic Call Distribuitor) to deliver the best possible voice &amp;amp; video experience with the lowest latency in a Contact Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesland Webinar Event</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Salesland. What if in COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s times, we could sell more? Join us at next 25th November, 16:00 CET at next Salesland 20 years event!
With:
Javier Arellano, Sales Manager and Businesss Development at Salesland Group. Ivan Sixto, Founder and CEO at Interactive Powers. The pandemic crisis caused by Covid-19 has created an acceleration in the digitalization processes of our society, but what about people? Why do we have to do without your sales team when you can reinvent their stall by making use of technology?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Channels for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Build consistent, effective, personalized engagements across Video channels with Voice, Video, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Co-browsing…. The most successful enterprises are defined by their ability to communicate. Today that means meeting consumers where they hangout – online, on multiple platforms like: Skype, FaceTime, WhatsApp, Telegram, Zoom, Microsoft Teams…
There’s no doubt that the name of the game today when we speak of Omnichannel Customer Experience is convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centribot Chatbot with Video Calling integration</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/centribot-chatbot-with-video-calling-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/centribot-chatbot-with-video-calling-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Centribal. Video RTC empowers Centribal chatbot platforms with real-time communications for any business. MIAMI, November. 16, 2020 — Centribal the creators of Centribot and Interactive Powers the creators of Video RTC announce new video real-time communications integration. The Centribal Platform is the conversational tool that allows the possibility of creating various chatbots from a single location, easily, quickly and with simplicity. Centribot will be able to create and train your chatbots in the way that best suits you, to make the most out of the communication management with your customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled Video Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scheduled-video-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scheduled-video-calling/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Scheduled Video Calls that enable the fastest face-to-face commmunication for a Remote Workforce. Imagine all your workforce requires to work from home or from anywhere, imagine you can&amp;rsquo;t connect all of them in unique real-time attention but they require to collaborate everyday each others to support your products and services. At Interactive Powers, we understand that kind of peer-to-peer (P2P) video calls are not just video meetings but something more specific between a call and a video room: we call this kind of interaction, Scheduled Video Calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Streaming with Video Call Queueing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/live-streaming-event-with-video-call-queueing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:21:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/live-streaming-event-with-video-call-queueing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Create a Live Streaming event and face-to-face connect your audiance to your sales team. Live Streaming can be the perfect engaging virtual event for your brand to attract a high number of viewers simulteanously. This is really great power of real-time but you can also do much more with your remote workforce team, if they can join any of this visitors at this big moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landing Page with Video Call Queueing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/landing-web-page-with-video-call-queueing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/landing-web-page-with-video-call-queueing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Enable your landing page or website visitors to join video agents in just one-click. Landing pages or Business Website receive visits from your customers at anytime, you should improve your customer support connecting one-to-one at this moment. A Chatbot, Form, Email is required but it could be not enough to engage a customer with your product or brand. Adding a Video Call Queueing enables that any customer can react and talk face-to-face with one of the sales agents at this moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call switching to Mobile Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-call-switching-to-mobile-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-call-switching-to-mobile-device/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Flip your frontend webcam stream to a mobile device in order move arround during a Video Call without hangup. Specific support or sales interaction could require agents or sales representative to move around a showroom during a video call using their smartphone without hangup.
We recommend to consider this agent side option in SPLIT that enable to switch easily to their mobile device using our QR code in screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scan to Video Call with QR code</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scan-to-videocall-with-qr-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scan-to-videocall-with-qr-code/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Make better and safe local point of sales with Scan-to-Videocall in order to improve social distance and get face-to-face sales online support. You want your customers to directly video call your contact center using their smartphone without any mobile app, registration, pluging or download.
This Video RTC feature is very interesting to connect easily existing local services with a remote sales force team that will provide safe face-to-face support to users or customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC Solutions Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-rtc-solutions-ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-rtc-solutions-ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Extending and empowering your business with Video Interactions out of the Contact Center. The adoption of video communications continues to expand globally. As more businesses are using video to connect with their users or customers remotely and realizing the importance of improving their customer experience, it is more critical than ever for video interactions to be as simple as possible. This is why more and more teams today are choosing our solutions so that callers do not need to download or install any application to connect instantaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling: On Queue</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers edited. Video Calling has to be &amp;ldquo;On Queue&amp;rdquo; to reach the highest effectivity and productivity to ensure the best Customer Experience and ROI. Video RTC for Genesys a unique complementary solutions for Contact Center that allow to handle Video Calling “On Queue” for your Contact Center thanks to SPLIT Forward / SPLIT Reverse a convergent WebRTC / SIP communications integration. Most existing Video powered addons are only working “Off Queue” because these products do not control any ACD event during all digital interactions and obviously cannot manage both inbound / outbound phone calls and video calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How IVR can help to improve your VoIP services?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Most people think that the Digital Revolution in Telephony has already occurred when voice over IP communications has progressively replaced landline connections. Currently, most telephony is digital and IP powered but that’s not the only thing that voice telecommunication requires in order to become more attractive and useful to users. You have to understand that there’s no difference for users in making phone calls via Landline or in a SIP extension, the user calling experience is remains the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why WebRTC makes VoIP services more attractive?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Nowadays telephony is still used under a specific network integration that is not all IP powered like PSTN numbering and specific rules to manage its traffic with operators. Until this day, Voice over IP has disrupted the telephony but still providing the same phone user experience; at the end, users are still dialing to a 9-10 digits number and all the call process is mostly the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Conversational IVR, is the Next Big Thing in Telephony and Internet of Things to connect better your customers with your business. Forget the technology, building the next generation of IVR self-services is more a question of business process to understand how your voice self-service has to manage the conversation. We are please to share this interesting video from Google about DialogFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU for Chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs. We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand in just few minutes: what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Chat vs Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the difference about these two chat modalities, and considerations to have during a text typed business communication? Most existing Contact Centers have added a Chat Channel to connect their agents with online connected users without the help of a phone. Today, It’s really important to understand properly what is the best way to use any Chat modality in order to avoid an integration nightmare in the future or less integration reworks for your business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about your Chat channel automation, extension and integration?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Existing business chat features have to be properly automated, connected and extended to provide a right value for any business application. It’s not just only a question of adding another channel, chat is a really poor conversation modality for humans. Of course, it provide very interesting advantages, because of its simplicity, quick adoption and low bandwidth requirements but it steel being a limited communication feature in a continuous evolution of online customers or consumers requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines Smart IVR and Video RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is a Communications Platform as a Service Company</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The future of communications is driven by the cloud. Interactive Powers was created to help companies embed voice and video communication into the software applications and web applications that are part of their workflow and how they do business with the same communication options and convenience that mobile devices provide for their customers and employees in their person lives. With Interactive Powers, communication becomes more immediate and contextual resulting in better business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How WebRTC improves your Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Now, It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your customer services with modern real-time communication channels. A large number of businesses can benefit from offering WebRTC services to get a better Customer Experience (CX) with their sales, support or any kind of interactions. And both customers and companies can obtain plenty of advantages by using Real-time Communications. Here, we present five of the most visible ones.
Easy Business Integration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration. If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever. Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Store · Europe CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new EU Store - Europe CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Europe and others countries.
Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.
A large number of different businesses could benefit from offering Live Video Chat services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
