<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How IVR can help to improve your VoIP services?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Most people think that the Digital Revolution in Telephony has already occurred when voice over IP communications has progressively replaced landline connections. Currently, most telephony is digital and IP powered but that’s not the only thing that voice telecommunication requires in order to become more attractive and useful to users. You have to understand that there’s no difference for users in making phone calls via Landline or in a SIP extension, the user calling experience is remains the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why WebRTC makes VoIP services more attractive?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Nowadays telephony is still used under a specific network integration that is not all IP powered like PSTN numbering and specific rules to manage its traffic with operators. Until this day, Voice over IP has disrupted the telephony but still providing the same phone user experience; at the end, users are still dialing to a 9-10 digits number and all the call process is mostly the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Conversational IVR, is the Next Big Thing in Telephony and Internet of Things to connect better your customers with your business. Forget the technology, building the next generation of IVR self-services is more a question of business process to understand how your voice self-service has to manage the conversation. We are please to share this interesting video from Google about DialogFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU for Chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs. We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand in just few minutes: what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Chat vs Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the difference about these two chat modalities, and considerations to have during a text typed business communication? Most existing Contact Centers have added a Chat Channel to connect their agents with online connected users without the help of a phone. Today, It’s really important to understand properly what is the best way to use any Chat modality in order to avoid an integration nightmare in the future or less integration reworks for your business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about your Chat channel automation, extension and integration?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Existing business chat features have to be properly automated, connected and extended to provide a right value for any business application. It’s not just only a question of adding another channel, chat is a really poor conversation modality for humans. Of course, it provide very interesting advantages, because of its simplicity, quick adoption and low bandwidth requirements but it steel being a limited communication feature in a continuous evolution of online customers or consumers requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines Smart IVR and Video RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is a Communications Platform as a Service Company</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The future of communications is driven by the cloud. Interactive Powers was created to help companies embed voice and video communication into the software applications and web applications that are part of their workflow and how they do business with the same communication options and convenience that mobile devices provide for their customers and employees in their person lives. With Interactive Powers, communication becomes more immediate and contextual resulting in better business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How WebRTC improves your Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Now, It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your customer services with modern real-time communication channels. A large number of businesses can benefit from offering WebRTC services to get a better Customer Experience (CX) with their sales, support or any kind of interactions. And both customers and companies can obtain plenty of advantages by using Real-time Communications. Here, we present five of the most visible ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration. If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever. Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Store · Europe CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new EU Store - Europe CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Europe and others countries.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>