<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marketing on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Marketing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with you customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information. To best position their companies and to meet necessities of digital customers, marketing departments face a range of challenges, including the extensive use of technologies for managing customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 key benefits of live video chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/key_benefits_videochat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/key_benefits_videochat/</guid>
      <description>Bots can solve a proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.
A large number of different businesses could benefit from offering live video chat services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>