<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videortc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videortc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videortc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videortc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels In 2016, the worldwide revenue for self-paced elearning was $ 46,674.67 Real-Time Video and Voice over the Internet open opportunities for everyone who wants to learn something. Online learning is gaining popularity as more and more students demand more flexibility that new technologies can provide. E-learning broadens the options of programs and degrees, since students can access to educational institutions all over the world. Self-paced learning allows students to arrange a learning schedule that meets their individual needs, at a lower price and without leaving the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works our Datachannel with VideoRTC.js</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how it works our Datachannel with VideoRTC.js and how to use it for a specific purpose.
Introduction First of all you need to know the modules in which we currently have available the Datachannel: These are the Videocall and the SPLIT. In this example we will use the first one, though the operation would be the same in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Physician E-visits. The main advantage of telehealth for patients is convenience. They can save time as it is not necessary for sick patients to travel to his doctor’s office.
Wellness Services. VideoRTC provides the opportunity to attend healthy lifestyle programs from the comfort of home.
Health Monitoring. Patients who need treatment after surgery or due to chronic diseases can be monitored remotely in real time by health professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add a Webphone Button in your Website</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webphonebutton-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:30:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webphonebutton-website/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to add a Webphone button in your website using our customizable webcall widget.
Step one: Installation To install the Webphone Button in your web­page you need to download our webcall widget webcall_widget_noflash.zip and uncompress it in the directory of your website.
To insert it, you first need to add the CSS Stylesheet file to your webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 3.0</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-3-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 11:06:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-3-generation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Whatever your business is, you may require Real-Time Communications to improve your services. The third generation of our flagship RTC product is now released after months and years of continuous improvements. Discover how to integrate live-video, voice, and messaging technology to transform your business processes, and how Video RTC it can help you facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers or employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build your Own Videoconference Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Today we bring you this interesting article on How to build your own videoconference service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step one: Setting up the basic structure As we have explained in previous posts, first of all it is important that you include dependency within your project or web page.
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telehealth Market will reach $1,9 billion by 2018 Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are changing the relations among patients and physicians. On the one hand, telemedicine is an emergent industry which makes it possible to expand services offered by health institutions, while it helps to solve some of the current economic problems faced by hospitals. On the other hand, within minutes, patients will have the opportunity to receive medical care from anywhere and they will avoid spending time in the doctor&amp;rsquo;s waiting room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Transformation: Doors of Opportunity for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:02:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All interactions cannot be managed by bots, since users, when facing with certain problems, need to contact a real agent. If consumer is not allowed to communicate with a person, it leads to frustration and the relation client-company is seriously damaged. At this point, video offers contact centers the possibility of developing a very differential customer experience management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on Safari 11 for Video RTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway, Now ready run with Apple Safari 11 over MacOS computers and iOS devices Interactive Powers is proud to announce Video RTC support for Safari 11 over MacOS and iOS. It was a demand from all the market for a long time, know it becomes a reality past week. Safari 11 works fine on the basis of WebRTC to allow Apple users community to connect most features but with some specific web browser limitations that we will comment shortly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is Transforming Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:04:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Companies must understand that the processes of digital transformation driven by society are inevitable. In the last years, the improvement of customer support services accelerates the pace of adaptation to digital processes. The reason is the good results obtained by companies that have already integrated advanced digital tools, based, for instance, on WebRTC technology for real-time communication via the web or mobile applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses need to Face Digital Challenges</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
The spread of new communication behaviour among users is pushing companies to modify their contact channels with customers. At Interactive Powers we observe that adapting to an increasingly digitized market poses new challenges. However, it also opens one door of opportunity for companies to improve and differentiate themselves.
From our offices in Spain and the United States, we provide solutions that facilitate secure and real-time multimedia interactions over the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does VideoRTC fit in my Contact Center?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:36:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Call Centers have to upgrade their services to the next level implementing new advanced interactions The ever-growing digital world can give new opportunities for existing contact centers to provide a superior customer experience. Nowadays new technologies drive clients to ask for multiple options when looking for support. It is here where VideoRTC can help your contact center to enhance its services.
Save time providing the right channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Mobile Video Application (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you need to install a project Ionic in your system. If you don’t have it, you can download and follow the official guide from the Ionic Framework 2 web site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Complementary Functions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-complementary-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-complementary-functions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes complementary features that you can run according to your business requirements . All of this, is part of capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
SIP Connect. Video Gateway ensures interoperability between WebRTC endpoints and existing telephony systems. It integrates seamlessly advanced web phones or mobile apps into previous infraestructure. Learn more.
Meeting Point. Video Gateway provides an additional OAuth plugin that makes it easier for users to connect to your real-time services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · API Framework</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</guid>
      <description>Provide Core Functions to easily develop any Video RTC application for Web and Mobile. Overview API Framework feature helps to make your job easier, adapting services to your needs and personalizing them. Our platform provides developers with a wide range of possible solutions, through a flexible and powerful toolkit for building Web APIs.
API Framework feature enables developers to design new APIs or edit existing ones. You can also customize all the way down, just using basic regular features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Videocall Service (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:59:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build your videocall service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you will need to include dependency within your project or web page:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.min.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  Next, we connect with the video gateway server:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Industries</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:00:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-industries/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Whatever your business, product, or service is you can require real-time communications technologies. Discover how organizations like yours are integrating live-video, voice, and messaging technology to transform their industries, and how Video RTC can help you facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers or employees.
Call Centers. Contact Centers continue to evolve rapidly as consumers expect a highly personalized and engaging experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video Recording</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Easily record secure Live Video Calls for later playback. Overview Video Recording capability enables to record your video calls in real-time. Files are securely stored and you can immediately access to content following your demands. Call records are directly pushed to your own secure file system storage or any web service, such as Amazon S3, Windows Azure, Google accounts… Enjoy playback with high-quality WebM recordings.
Video Recording functionality includes converter tools to automatically live-convert video streams to MP4 for easy access with no post-processing required on your end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · SIP Connect</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-sip-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-sip-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect WebRTC or RTMP to traditional SIP telephony systems or devices. Overview SIP Connect feature is designed to make traditional calls across web or mobile phones. It enables interoperability between WebRTC endpoints and existing telephony systems, like your current PBX or phone lines. For instance, a Call Center can send and receive SIP-based calls, using SPLIT function as well.
SIP Connect functionality allows you to send Dual-tone multi-frequency signalling (DTMF) or in-band telecommunication signalling system using the voice-frequency band over SIP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Meeting Point</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-meeting-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-meeting-point/</guid>
      <description>Make secure business online meetings with a standard OAuth authentication. Overview Meeting Point feature is an additional OAuth plugin to make easier user authentication for Internet services without retrieving passwords. It includes many tested methods for different social networks like Google, Linkedin or Twitter. However, you can create your own OAuth interface too.
Meeting Point functionality allows to easily connect users to your real-time services without having to add third-party components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Over Printing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-over-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-over-printing/</guid>
      <description>Create Multi-tenant Video Services over WebRTC for your Contact Center. Overview Over Printing feature allows to print a logo inside the remote frame. Instead of specific customisation you can use it to distribute video calls to several services with their own service logo. It’s very useful for a Call Center with many services operated with different profiles.
Over Printing functionality is easy to configure inside our multi-flavor settings without specific coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Snapshot</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-snapshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-snapshot/</guid>
      <description>Take or get pictures dynamically during your remote video conversations. Overview Snapshot feature allows you to take easily a picture within the video. This functionality helps to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. For instance, you can get Jpeg pictures from agents or users frames during a process, retrieving them later or share them to an external application interface.
Snapshot makes it possible to save a picture from the middle of a video, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Voice Calling</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</guid>
      <description>Make advanced Voice Call or Web Phone applications for Real-Time Communications. Overview Voice Calling functionality ensures that no one misses out on the full application experience. It helps to provide an effective customer care, offering the option to hear voices in real-time. Voice Calling keeps interactions as easy, simply and fast as possible.
Voice Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video Calling</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</guid>
      <description>Create amazing Real-Time Communications with Dual-band Voice and Video capabilities Overview Video Calling functionality provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage. Agents or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.
Video Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Secure screen share your desktop or any application in Real-Time Communications. Overview Screen Sharing application allows you to share live screen over the web or mobile instantly. Most business processes can take benefit of using Screen Sharing feature. For instance, it is a very powerful tool to improve online meetings, presentations, remote work or support services.
Screen Sharing functionality makes it easy to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · File Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Send and Receive Files or Documents in Real-Time Communications. Overview File Sharing application helps you to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. It allows you to instantly transfer any file establishing a peer connection all within the context of your website or application. With the file sharing feature you can send and receive unlimited files just dragging them in the chat window.
File Sharing functionality makes it possible to share and receive documents during your voice or video call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Core Features</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes core features that you can activate according to your own business requirements . All of this, is part of the main capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
Video Calling. Video Gateway provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Live Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Manage Smart Text Message interactions in Real-Time Communications. Overview Live Chat supplement your video and voice communication with advanced text chat capabilities using the WebRTC datachannel. Live Chat feature allows to send and receive text messages simultaneously, without any lag at a single click. It is the perfect tool to use for the customer and an agent conversation. Live chat integrates seamlessly into your application, eliminating the need for clunky third-party APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://webclient.ivrpowers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) Roadmap 2017!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons We are pleased to unveil some key elements of our Video RTC (WebRTC) evolution until 2017. Major changes will follow WebRTC’s evolution itself. Our primary goal is to provide improved features to all Special Extensions like SPLIT, Video Calling, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot&amp;hellip; In the next quarter, we will make significant improvements like adding a better Customer Experience with Video Real-Time Communications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video gets more Honest Buyers than other Channels</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 19:11:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons According to a W. Frank Barton School of Business at Wichita State University new research, sending a text message, making a phone call or have a face-to-face conversation leads people to lie often than video conferencing. The study found that buyers were:
 95% more likely to report deception via text messages than if they had interacted via video 31% more likely to report deception when compared to face-to-face communication in person 18% more likely if the interaction was via audio chat or phone call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>