<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elearning on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/elearning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elearning on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 13:30:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/elearning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 13:30:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Learning at convenience. The current pace of life and work prevents us from continuing our learning. Thanks to digital tools and Real-Times Communications improving knowledge is not out of reach anymore. E-learning increases accessibility and reach as e-learning courses are more affordable and fits with students’ timetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Video-based learning. Video use is increasing and video features are critical in e-learning. Video allows students to access lectures, but also share content with their peers and professors, as well as tutoring in live real time interactions.
Mobile Learning. Mobile devices are growing in popularity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels In 2016, the worldwide revenue for self-paced elearning was $ 46,674.67 Real-Time Video and Voice over the Internet open opportunities for everyone who wants to learn something. Online learning is gaining popularity as more and more students demand more flexibility that new technologies can provide. E-learning broadens the options of programs and degrees, since students can access to educational institutions all over the world. Self-paced learning allows students to arrange a learning schedule that meets their individual needs, at a lower price and without leaving the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>