<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products_voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products_voicexml/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response Platform
Our IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/videortc/</guid>
      <description>Video Real Time Communications Platform
Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services.
WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is an API definition drafted by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) that supports browser-to-browser applications for voice calling, video chat, and messaging without the need of either internal or external plugins. RTMP is an open protocol for Adobe Flash Player compliant browsers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>