<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Products on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/products/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Products on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/products/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Video Real Time Communications Platform
Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services.
WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is an API definition drafted by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) that supports browser-to-browser applications for voice calling, video chat, and messaging without the need of either internal or external plugins. RTMP is an open protocol for Adobe Flash Player compliant browsers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response Platform
Our IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR v13.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note
We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 13.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note
We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note
We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>