<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retail on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/retail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retail on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video Kiosks: Integrating the Phygital Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-kiosks-integrating-the-phygital-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-kiosks-integrating-the-phygital-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons Video-based human-centric communication centralized towards every physical point of sale or support. In the realm of business, optimization is the key to success. We constantly seek ways to enhance efficiency, boost productivity, and deliver superior customer service. In this regard, video kiosks emerge as invaluable digital tools across various industries, not only enhancing customer experience but also projecting human-centric attention from a video contact center to multiple points of sale or physical centers across geographies in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scaling &amp; Empowering Sales Teams</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scaling-empowering-sales-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scaling-empowering-sales-teams/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons Harnessing the Power of Transactional Video Calls in Business Processes. In an era increasingly defined by digitalization, businesses are compelled to reimagine their sales strategies to maintain relevance and competitiveness. While traditional face-to-face interactions have long been a cornerstone of sales, harnessing the potential of video calls can profoundly impact the scalability and efficacy of your employee sales force. Transitioning from conventional on-site engagements to transaccional video calls (direct real-time transfer) presents a disruptive opportunity for transformative growth in sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Retail Success through Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Six key reasons to consider adding real-time video calling support to your retail business with or without online store. In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, video calls are not just a means of meetings or scheduled communications; they&amp;rsquo;re a powerful tool for transforming the retail landscape. Here&amp;rsquo;s how integrating video calls can significantly boost the success of retail businesses:
1. More Personalized Customer Service Video calls enable retailers to offer personalized customer service experiences from the comfort of a customer&amp;rsquo;s home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Industries</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons In 2016, two main channels for generating sales were ‘Stores’ at 79% and &amp;lsquo;Website&amp;rsquo; at 73% Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet offers the opportunity to find innovative to ways to respond to consumers’ expectations. This technology provides numerous channels that allow to adapt companies’ assistance to clients’ needs. By integrating features such as live chat, videoconferencing, phone calls or file sharing, you can remarkably improve customer experience and differentiate your store in a highly competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
