<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>retail on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/retail/</link>
    <description>Recent content in retail on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:51:29 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/retail/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Retail Success Through Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/enhancing-retail-success-through-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons 6 Reasons to consider adding video calling support to your retail business with or without online store. In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, video calls are not just a means of meetings or communication; they&amp;rsquo;re a powerful tool for transforming the retail landscape. Here&amp;rsquo;s how integrating video calls can significantly boost the success of retail businesses:
1. Personalized Customer Service Video calls enable retailers to offer personalized customer service experiences from the comfort of a customer&amp;rsquo;s home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Industries</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons In 2016, two main channels for generating sales were ‘Stores’ at 79% and &amp;lsquo;Website&amp;rsquo; at 73% Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet offers the opportunity to find innovative to ways to respond to consumers’ expectations. This technology provides numerous channels that allow to adapt companies’ assistance to clients’ needs. By integrating features such as live chat, videoconferencing, phone calls or file sharing, you can remarkably improve customer experience and differentiate your store in a highly competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
