<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Businessstrategy on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businessstrategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Businessstrategy on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businessstrategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Banking Revolution is coming</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</guid>
      <description>We are increasingly moving on line. And bank customers are not an exception. Financial businesses need to adapt their services to the new life styles and trends. One of the options is live video chat.
Video banking allows to deliver the best possible experience to online customers. Thanks to live video chat technology financial services can offer to their customers face to face experiences without leaving the comfort of their houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to Customer Experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of Video Chat:
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information. To best position their companies and to meet necessities of digital customers, marketing departments face a range of challenges, including the extensive use of technologies for managing customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>