<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>businessstrategy on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businessstrategy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in businessstrategy on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businessstrategy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What’s next for customer behavior?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons The Covid-19 pandemic has changed the way we live, work and shop, it has created a need for new methods of engagement between contact centres and customers. Customers no longer care about the brands that they had been loyal for years, they simply want to shop in a safe, efficient and convenient manner; experience matters now more than ever.
Hyper-personalization This is an incredible opportunity for brands to show up for their customers and provide an extra level of ease and personalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How customer behavior has changed during the pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Customers are no longer caring about the brands that they had been loyal to for years, now they simply want to shop with brands that make their life easier and better, expecting clear and easy options for contacting any post-pandemic customer service.
Remote Working is Required Consumers are now building their whole lifestyles around their homes as centres of gravity where they work and stay healthy, shopping online more and 30% hope to work more from their home in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: Open Standard Technology for Browsers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-standard-technology-noapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-standard-technology-noapp/</guid>
      <description>Enabling embed Business Communications into any Web interface with Video RTC  WebRTC (Web Real Time Communication) enables peer-to-peer communication with desktop and mobile browsers. In other words, WebRTC allows you to exchange any kind of media through the web (such as video, audio and data) without any required plugin or component. All our solutions are now following the #NOAPP approach avoid any requirement to download, install any app or plugin in any device to get live communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Chat vs Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the difference about these two chat modalities, and considerations to have during a text typed business communication?  Most existing Contact Centers have added a Chat Channel to connect their agents with online connected users without the help of a phone. Today, It’s really important to understand properly what is the best way to use any Chat modality in order to avoid an integration nightmare in the future or less integration reworks for your business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about your Chat channel automation, extension and integration?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Existing business chat features have to be properly automated, connected and extended to provide a right value for any business application.  It’s not just only a question of adding another channel, chat is a really poor conversation modality for humans. Of course, it provide very interesting advantages, because of its simplicity, quick adoption and low bandwidth requirements but it steel being a limited communication feature in a continuous evolution of online customers or consumers requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How WebRTC improves your Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Now, It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your customer services with modern real-time communication channels.  A large number of businesses can benefit from offering WebRTC services to get a better Customer Experience (CX) with their sales, support or any kind of interactions. And both customers and companies can obtain plenty of advantages by using Real-time Communications. Here, we present five of the most visible ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Store · Europe CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you!  Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new EU Store - Europe CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Europe and others countries.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you!  Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of CPaaS for Video Real-Time Communications in Businesses</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:46:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers In the next 12 months, up to 49% of Business Cases that will run video services are using a Communication Platform-as-a-Service (CPaaS). Telemedicine and Insurance Professionals. Trends are showing that a leading industry in incorporating video is telehealth with 47% of respondents embedded video into a telehealth application. Video offers numerous advantages to this sector. It allows patients to receive attention at convenience from the comfort of their homes and it helps health institutions to significantly reduce costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79% of Consumers Want the Opportunity to Contact Businesses Online</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:03:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In a recent Enghouse Interactive survey, customers have made it clear that they want online communication channels with companies. 79% of consumers believe that businesses should provide a way for customers to contact them online.
It is also interesting to compare this figure with the responses to the very same question in previous years&#39; surveys. In 2014, only 29% of respondents answered that the possibility to contact a company online was relevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 08:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service  Keep the human touch. It is not only that customers can still chose to interact in person, but thanks to VideoRTC, they have now more options to communicate face-to-face. If clients need help while using self-service, they can contact an agent. Clients can also videochat with their bank advisors through a tablet or a mobile phone from the comfort of their homes, but living an experience similar to an in-person branch visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week  More data for a better service. Data provided by customers about their needs, preferences and individual tastes enable e-commerce businesses to create clients’ profiles and take into account their purchase history to better serve them. Clients should easily have the opportunity to give feedback, so their problems can be solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Integration in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:09:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons The Video Channel is the next level Customer Experience frontier for existing Contact Centers  Video is not a separate solution from the services that contact centers have been providing until now and it is not a substitute for voice calls. The key to the Video in Real-time communications lies in the possibility of offering a new channel, whose use is progressively increasing in customer care services for most industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 10:48:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service  Expert Advice. Video and voice over the internet make it possible to meet current customers’ expectations. More and more clients look for information on line and VideoRTC offers the opportunity to remotely discuss products and receive information from an expert.
ATMs. This technology allows to combine the advantages of self-service, such as rapidity and efficiency, with face-to-face customer service if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 11:06:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 35% of consumers say the smartphone will become their main purchasing tool  In today&amp;rsquo;s market, it is crucial that businesses engage customers the way they communicate. Users are increasingly turning to the Internet for their personal communications, but also to make regular purchases or contract services. As online purchases increase, the success of a modern business depends on the ability to promote its products and services through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week  Pre-sales support. Video options make it possible to show products to customers. They can check its appearance and functionality, making more informed purchase decisions.
Personalized shopping. Video and voice over the Internet allow you to pay the same special, individual attention to online customers as in face-to-face interactions in a more efficient way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing  Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction  Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key Benefits of Interactive Kiosks</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers WebRTC technology has disrupted traditional communications, but we have barely experienced its potential yet. One of the most relevant applications is going to take place at points of sale. Thanks to the latest breakthroughs in video technology, customer experience can be dramatically enhanced. Let’s see the main benefits of an Interactive Kiosk:
Immediate Real-Time Communications. Kiosks enable a personalized and immediate communication between an expert or a salesperson and a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses need to Face Digital Challenges</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
The spread of new communication behaviour among users is pushing companies to modify their contact channels with customers. At Interactive Powers we observe that adapting to an increasingly digitized market poses new challenges. However, it also opens one door of opportunity for companies to improve and differentiate themselves.
From our offices in Spain and the United States, we provide solutions that facilitate secure and real-time multimedia interactions over the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Revolution in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:00:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All of us, as consumers, are becoming increasingly familiar with the use of new channels. We must also take into account that the first generation of digital natives is entering into the market. However, phone continues to be the most widely used channel in customer service and voice over IP technology. This situation is specially extended in the Spanish business landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.
A large number of different businesses could benefit from offering Live Video Chat services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Banking Revolution is coming</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</guid>
      <description>We are increasingly moving on line. And bank customers are not an exception. Financial businesses need to adapt their services to the new life styles and trends. One of the options is live video chat.
Video banking allows to deliver the best possible experience to online customers. Thanks to live video chat technology financial services can offer to their customers face to face experiences without leaving the comfort of their houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number… they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
