<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trend on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/trend/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trend on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/trend/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Technavio: IVR market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The Interactive Voice Response (IVR) market is growing, but what’s driving that growth? Market research analysts from Technavio suggest that the IVR, or Interactive Voice Response market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021. For those who are new to the industry, IVR systems are the solutions that give companies a stronger way of engaging their customers through various customer service solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner: 20 percent of Global Businesses will deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest Global Businesses will implement Video Chat. Time is the new currency for your customers who are looking for painless and informed solutions to their issues. We are also starting, growing and running companies in an &amp;ldquo;attention economy,&amp;rdquo; which is defined by the view that human attention is a scarce commodity. By 2018, according to research from Gartner, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forrester: Voice Channel as Self-service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons 63 percent of US adult callers report to use the voice channel for self-service (IVR) According to a 2016 Forrester Research study, 83 percent of U.S. adult Internet users had a phone conversation with a customer service representative in the past year. Sixty-three percent of them also reported using the voice channel for self-service, such as Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems whose Conversational AI capabilities enable callers to converse with a virtual agent as if there were a human rep on the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economist: Visual Recognition with &#39;Deep Learning&#39; is suparsing Humans for First Time</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Visual Recognition Algorithms reach an accuracy of 96% with &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning&amp;rdquo; The rehabilitation of “AI”, and the current excitement about the field, can be traced back to 2012 and an online contest called the ImageNet Challenge. ImageNet is an online database of millions of images, all labelled by hand. For any given word, such as “balloon” or “strawberry”, ImageNet contains several hundred images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Data: Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons Nearly one-third of Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat to improve Customer Engagement According to a research from Dimension Data, nearly one-third of contact centers expect to deploy video chat for customer engagement. The research says that giving customers the additional option to remotely connect face-to-face, at moments that are important to them (and on their terms), can make their customer experience even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>