<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with you customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 14:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! **Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Voice Calling</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</guid>
      <description>Make advanced Voice Call or Web Phone applications for Real-Time Communications. Overview Voice Calling functionality ensures that no one misses out on the full application experience. It helps to provide an effective customer care, offering the option to hear voices in real-time. Voice Calling keeps interactions as easy, simply and fast as possible.
Voice Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video Calling</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</guid>
      <description>Create amazing Real-Time Communications with Dual-band Voice and Video capabilities Overview Video Calling functionality provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage. Agents or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.
Video Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Secure screen share your desktop or any application in Real-Time Communications. Overview Screen Sharing application allows you to share live screen over the web or mobile instantly. Most business processes can take benefit of using Screen Sharing feature. For instance, it is a very powerful tool to improve online meetings, presentations, remote work or support services.
Screen Sharing functionality makes it easy to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Source: Survey from Ofcom ,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator Children 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · File Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Send and Receive Files or Documents in Real-Time Communications. Overview File Sharing application helps you to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. It allows you to instantly transfer any file establishing a peer connection all within the context of your website or application. With the file sharing feature you can send and receive unlimited files just dragging them in the chat window.
File Sharing functionality makes it possible to share and receive documents during your voice or video call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Core Features</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes core features that you can activate according to your own business requirements . All of this, is part of the main capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Live Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Manage Smart Text Message interactions in Real-Time Communications. Overview Live Chat supplement your video and voice communication with advanced text chat capabilities using the WebRTC datachannel. Live Chat feature allows to send and receive text messages simultaneously, without any lag at a single click. It is the perfect tool to use for the customer and an agent conversation. Live chat integrates seamlessly into your application, eliminating the need for clunky third-party APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s E-commerce become a Better Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Latest Video Real-Time Communications can be decisive to improve e-commerce services. First of all, because they are becoming very accessible and easy to use through web browsers or most of mobile devices. Plugin downloads are no longer required, you just click and your are connected. Secondly, remember that creating a live interaction with your customers like a live chat or video call channels is a proven way to increase your sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) Roadmap 2017!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons We are pleased to unveil some key elements of our Video RTC (WebRTC) evolution until 2017. Major changes will follow WebRTC’s evolution itself. Our primary goal is to provide improved features to all Special Extensions like SPLIT, Video Calling, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot&amp;hellip; In the next quarter, we will make significant improvements like adding a better Customer Experience with Video Real-Time Communications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC built-in Security Features</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:04:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons In essence, any software in the Internet is an inherent risk that your PC may become infected by a virus, malware, spyware or various other ‘bugs’ that threaten the security of your data. As such, the principal solution to combat viruses is to install firewalls and anti-malware software that work to defend your computer against any potential threats.
With WebRTC however, there’s no need to worry about any of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2.0:
## [2.2.0] - 2017-07-27 ### Added - Added interval Watchdog - Added autocall GET parameter to the Webclient URL usecase - Added overprint logo in the Webclient usecase  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: Time-Saver, Better Access and More Services</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 10:26:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interl Free Press. Creative Commons There is no greater need for a personalized customer experience than in healthcare. But, at the same time, busy patients demand new ways to communicate with their doctors to save time. Thanks to technology RTC innovations, telehealth can make healthcare easier for patients.
Why should healthcare industry take advantage and adapt to technology trends? Time-saver Telemedicine allows to save time spent traveling to doctor’s office and waiting for the appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser to SIP Calling?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration How can you call a Desk Phone from any Web Browser? Our both Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) can convert web browser media streams (video - audio - data) to SIP from WebRTC or RTMP peers communications. This interesting feature allows to connect easily web services to existing VoIP telephony channels of your IVR or PBX. We can consider all of this approach like a direct calling webphone or like a WebRTC-DDI or RTMP-DDI in a SIP trunk from an operator service configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70 percent of all Doctor’s Office Visits are Unnecessary</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 10:00:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent study by PricewaterhouseCoopers, one in four people indicate that it takes more than 30 days to get an appointment with their physician. Many of these cases result in an unnecessary visit to the emergency room. Overall, the total cost of unnecessary emergency room visits is just under $14 billion annually. One of the most common reasons for these unnecessary visits include patient convenience, symptoms that occur after hours or on the weekend, or the patient was unable to get a timely appointment with their physician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video gets more Honest Buyers than other Channels</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 19:11:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons According to a W. Frank Barton School of Business at Wichita State University new research, sending a text message, making a phone call or have a face-to-face conversation leads people to lie often than video conferencing. The study found that buyers were:
 95% more likely to report deception via text messages than if they had interacted via video 31% more likely to report deception when compared to face-to-face communication in person 18% more likely if the interaction was via audio chat or phone call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VideoRTC.js for Developers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:30:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers elaboration Since 2015, Interactive Powers has been diligently refining its Video RTC solutions, API Framework and SDKs to make embedded video much more accessible for developers and enterprises who are looking to rapidly integrate reliable video chat into their own applications.
VideoRTC.js library Today, we’re thrilled to officially announce a new VideoRTC.js library – the launch of our self-service API Framework developer tools, which lets developers quickly and easily embed this same enterprise-grade, cloud-hosted, multiparty RTC video collaboration into any web, mobile or native application on virtually any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins. WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR.
Give us a shout out! https://twitter.com/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Banking Revolution is coming</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</guid>
      <description>We are increasingly moving on line. And bank customers are not an exception. Financial businesses need to adapt their services to the new life styles and trends. One of the options is live video chat.
Video banking allows to deliver the best possible experience to online customers. Thanks to live video chat technology financial services can offer to their customers face to face experiences without leaving the comfort of their houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR v1.3</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 1.3 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>