<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Businesstrends on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businesstrends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Businesstrends on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:14:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/businesstrends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/add-voip2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/add-voip2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, will speak about Cloud API’s novelties at VoIP2Day 2017.
Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate. We are experiencing an Internet revolution that begins to affect basic services that we now operate with specific devices or business systems. Some, have already been completely absorbed by the cloud, be it web search, positioning maps or directory services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoIP2Day 2017: 10th Conferences Anniversary</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 10th edition of VOIP2DAY, the major event about Voice over IP of the year in Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at VoIP2DAY 2017: November 15th &amp;amp; 16th at Wanda Metropolitano Stadium, Madrid. We will share latest industry news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all companies and visitors of the main sector of Telephony and Comunications in Europe and Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>