<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ivr on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ivr on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Cloud API for Voice over IP at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate. We are experiencing an Internet revolution that begins to affect basic services that we now operate with specific devices or business systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is Transforming Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:04:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Companies must understand that the processes of digital transformation driven by society are inevitable. In the last years, the improvement of customer support services accelerates the pace of adaptation to digital processes. The reason is the good results obtained by companies that have already integrated advanced digital tools, based, for instance, on WebRTC technology for real-time communication via the web or mobile applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technavio: IVR market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The Interactive Voice Response (IVR) market is growing, but what’s driving that growth? Market research analysts from Technavio suggest that the IVR, or Interactive Voice Response market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021. For those who are new to the industry, IVR systems are the solutions that give companies a stronger way of engaging their customers through various customer service solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forrester: Voice Channel as Self-service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons 63 percent of US adult callers report to use the voice channel for self-service (IVR) According to a 2016 Forrester Research study, 83 percent of U.S. adult Internet users had a phone conversation with a customer service representative in the past year. Sixty-three percent of them also reported using the voice channel for self-service, such as Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems whose Conversational AI capabilities enable callers to converse with a virtual agent as if there were a human rep on the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://webclient.ivrpowers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR v1.3</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 1.3 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>