<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ivr on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ivr on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Standard VoiceXML IVR vs Call Flow Diagram IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/standard-voicexml-vs-call-flow-diagram-powered-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/standard-voicexml-vs-call-flow-diagram-powered-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Comparing Standard VoiceXML and Call Flow Diagram implementation approach for Interactive Voice Response (IVR) Systems. Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems are commonly used in many organizations to enhance customer service, increase efficiency, and reduce costs. There are different types of IVR systems available in the market, such as Standard VoiceXML IVR and Call Flow Diagram IVR. In this post, we will compare these two types of IVR systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.7</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.7.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.7.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.7:
## [2.7.0] - 03-11-2022 ### Added - Parameter start-input-timers to res-speech-unimrcp to disable the default timers initialization in the RECOGNIZE - Channel variable (VOICEDETECTED_TIMEOUT) to select a different timeout to allow speech inputs longer than 10s ### Fixed - A bug during the collection of the next audio sample during the NLU phase Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.6.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.6.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.6.1:
## [2.6.1] - 28-03-2022 ### Fixed - Added a safeguard to the restoring of the readformat of the channel for the cases where it is not present Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.6</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.6.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.6:
## [2.6.0] - 23-03-2022 ### Added - Hability to record the user speech during an ASR session ### Fixed - Applied patch to the speech_create Asterisk function to prevent crashes after lots of ASR sessions Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.5</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.5.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.5:
## [2.5.0] - 29-11-2021 ### Added - Support for recording the NLU user voice and retrieve its contents - Max duration option for the NLU interaction - PJSIP support ### Changed - Improved the NLU with Google for phrases where the user takes breaks between words - Improved NLU session cleanup - Improved the &amp;#34;voicexml hangup session&amp;#34; Asterisk command - Improved the output of the &amp;#34;voicexml show nlu&amp;#34; Asterisk command - Improved the behavior of the Asterisk module for the cases where the connection with the message queue is lost during a long time ### Fixed - The indexing of the output for the command &amp;#34;voicexml show statistics&amp;#34; Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Business Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Leading companies have a wholeness approach about how to communicate better with customers across their processes. Communicate is a top priority for businesses today — but how can you quantify its value to your organization? That’s especially important in these times, with businesses managing the economic impact and uncertainty of disruptive events, and how this will impact both their customers and employees going forward. The History of Business Communications is, of course, closely linked with the histories of Communications itself and that of Business Operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Dialer, Click-to-Call</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-dialer-click-to-call-reloaded-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 00:12:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-dialer-click-to-call-reloaded-copy/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Make calls from any Web Browser. From now, phone numbers are no longer required. In today’s increasingly digital world, customers have come to favor online service options available from the convenience of their screen. From chatbots and self-service features to digitally connecting to a live agent with a simple button click, companies aim to deliver a digital customer experience that is personal, seamless, quick, and efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is ACD?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</guid>
      <description>An automated call distribution system, commonly known as Automatic Call Distributor (ACD), is a telecommunication system that answers incoming phone calls or video calls to distributes them within an organization. ACDs often provide some form of Automatic Customer/Caller Identification (ACIS), such as Direct Inward Dialing (DID), Dialed Number Identification Service (DNIS), Automatic Number Identification (ANI), or Video SPLIT ID (VSID) for use in routing calls based on a series of user-configured rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.4</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.4.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.4:
## [2.4.0] - 04-03-2021 ### Added - Added res_srtp Asterisk module to support RTP over SSL - Added &amp;lt;context&amp;gt; support for the &amp;lt;nlu&amp;gt; recognition ### Changed - General internal updates to the NLU logic ### Fixed - Fixed a couple of scenarios where the NLU result was not properly detected - Properly cleaned the CompletionQueue of the GRPC NLU Google session by performing the needed tasks explicitly- Memory leak on the interpreter engine Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 most popular blog posts in 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Freepik Creative Commons. Video Real-Time Communications and Voicebot IVR were key themes during this 2020. The most viewed posts in our blog this year are following some important updates of this challenging year. To prepare 2021, we share this TOP 10 list:
1- What is a STUN/TURN server (TOP) The best description of what is a STUN/TURN server you where looking for… https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/
2- Video RTC - Web Browsers support in 2020!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Channels for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Build consistent, effective, personalized engagements across Video channels with Voice, Video, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Co-browsing…. The most successful enterprises are defined by their ability to communicate. Today that means meeting consumers where they hangout – online, on multiple platforms like: Skype, FaceTime, WhatsApp, Telegram, Zoom, Microsoft Teams…
There’s no doubt that the name of the game today when we speak of Omnichannel Customer Experience is convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2:
## [2.2.1] - 10-04-2020 ### Fixed - The resizing of the history of recordings files was sometimes crashing the Asterisk. ## [2.2.0] - 30-03-2020 ### Added - New VoiceXML element &amp;lt;nlu&amp;gt; with support for Google GRPC Speech API - New Asterisk command to display current nlu sessions ### Changed - Project build now with c++11 version - Accounts information is now only loaded &amp;amp; displayed if the license loaded successfully ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Phone Calls to DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are main questions about connecting a DialogFlow agent to a telephony system? It’s important to get some important differences between the Google Phone Gateway and our DialogFlow Gateway powered by a Smart IVR platform.
Can I get a Number (PSTN) from any country? 🟢 Phone Gateway = Yes, select a PSTN Number in the list of each available country. 🟢 DialogFlow Gateway = Yes, connect your own DDI Number or any IP PBX extensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect DialogFlow to your PBX?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Build a Voicebot IVR with DialogFlow for your existing PBX and telephony system. Continuing on our quest of better business communications, both old DTMF menus and speech direct dialog are outdated IVR options, we can replace them by the power of a DialogFlow advanced Conversational AI service.
Prerequisities 1- Text-to-Speech API account (TTS) You can connect any TTS according to your language and voice preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR · Speech Recognition Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</guid>
      <description>More and better protocols to improve performance of your interactive phone services. Speech recognition is a key complementary feature for any IVR in order enables the recognition and translation of spoken language into text for your voice application coding. It is also known as automatic speech recognition (ASR) or speech to text (STT). Smart IVR support today three connectors since the last release 2.x and it has the ability to use them in perfect combination for all services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to improve your PBX with Conversational AI?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way In The New Digital Age, standards commons PBX functions used by most companies are weighing down Customer Experience (CX) making tedious to contact their phone services or customer assistance.
Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What most companies still doing…
DTMF Menus. Most PBX use touch tone menus to select departments, services or key an extension. Of course, everybody may knows how to press a key, but it’s not really confortable to do this with hands free, driving or when you don’t get the right option…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1:
## [2.1.0] - 03-02-2020 ### Added - Support for the &amp;lt;data&amp;gt; element - Added noinputtimeout for the &amp;lt;record&amp;gt; element ## [2.0.3] - 03-12-2019 ### Fixed - Removed unnecessary error message when making a TTS request through HTTP - Added verification check for the existance of a cached file before trying to access it to avoid error messages - Fixed the conversion from interpreter value to JSI double numbers on subdialog return ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Smart IVR platforms are designed to run over a Linux CentOS 7 x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.centos.org
Requirement Description Distribution Linux CentOS 7 Linux Kernel x86_64 Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure Installer Minimal Install Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a IVR service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How IVR can help to improve your VoIP services?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Most people think that the Digital Revolution in Telephony has already occurred when voice over IP communications has progressively replaced landline connections. Currently, most telephony is digital and IP powered but that’s not the only thing that voice telecommunication requires in order to become more attractive and useful to users. You have to understand that there’s no difference for users in making phone calls via Landline or in a SIP extension, the user calling experience is remains the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t forget to train your Voicebot</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Like any human performance, your AI powered system requires to be properly trained. Training is the most important thing to consider to make your Voicebot IVR smart enough when it goes in production. Many projects forgot to review continuously learning rules, intents and transactions logs.
When a Voicebot or conversational agent does not understand you, it is because, in reality, he does not have been properly trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTS-API connectors updated!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45+ Languages &amp;amp; 300+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon, Google and Microsoft Cloud TTS-API Integration. Natural Language over the Phone&amp;hellip; All of you know about cognitive services is growing these days, and that&amp;rsquo;s why today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about our new TTS-API for &amp;ldquo;Text to speech&amp;rdquo;. This connector converts text into a dynamic natural voice in just a few milliseconds. There are a lot of Cloud Speech API, but we will focus on the Cloud Services main giants: Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Polly TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 27 Languages &amp;amp; 60+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon Polly Integration About Amazon&amp;hellip; Amazon Polly is a Text-to-Speech (TTS) service that uses advanced deep learning technologies to synthesize speech that sounds like a human voice. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the voice of Alexa and can do much more for your business too.
Amazon has arround 60 voices across 30 languages and variants. Amazon Polly offers Neural Text-to-Speech (NTTS) voices through Machine Learning approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 30+ Languages &amp;amp; 180+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Google TTS Integration About Google&amp;hellip; Google Cloud is one of the major Enterprise Cloud Services in the world, so its API does not fall short. There are a lot of features that are worth of mention, but we don’t have that time so, here are some of main features we consider:
Google has over 180 voices across 30+ languages and variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45 Languages &amp;amp; 75+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Microsoft Azure TTS Integration About Microsoft&amp;hellip; Microsoft Azure like Google Cloud provides his own Text To Speech API. It is quite big and here are some of its main features with more than 75 voices over 45 languages.
Parameters for speed, pitch, volume, pronunciation, and additional pauses Custom voice models for developers and enterprises Neural Voices technology To get more information, you can read Microsoft TTS documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Conversational IVR, is the Next Big Thing in Telephony and Internet of Things to connect better your customers with your business. Forget the technology, building the next generation of IVR self-services is more a question of business process to understand how your voice self-service has to manage the conversation. We are please to share this interesting video from Google about DialogFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-2-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-2-generation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Interactive Voice Response refounded to becomes Conversational IVR. The second generation of our IVR product is now released after months of developments and continuous improvements. Discover how to integrate telephony and voicebots / conversational agents to transform your business processes, and how VoiceXML IVR can help you to facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers, users or employees.
Welcome to VoiceXML IVR 2.0! This new version is the result of teamwork and great IVR experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU for Chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs. We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand in just few minutes: what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.0:
## [2.0] - 2019-02-29 ### New - First release of Smart IVR 2.0 - New PBX-SIP Connect - New TTS-HTTP/MRCP - New ASR-HTTP/MRCP Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR · Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-speech-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-speech-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Convert spoken voice into machine-readable format. Overview VoiceXML IVR runs most existing Cloud Speech API and some MRCP v2 engines. These STT / ASR connectors allow to get a complete development abstraction of all your interactive phone services. In combination with Text-to-Speech, you can develop the most advanced interactive voice experience with the best platform management.
Providers Nuance Speech Recognizer Google Speech API Amazon Lex Microsoft Azure Use Cases Call Stearing, Call Routing, Voice Search&amp;hellip; Support most languanges with several voices Power advanced IVR applications Power Voicebots and Voice Assistants System Requirements Speech Recognition feature requires VoiceXML IVR On Premise or Cloud CPaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR · Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-text-to-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-text-to-speech/</guid>
      <description>Convert text into spoken voice outpout. Overview VoiceXML IVR runs most existing Text-to-Speech engines with many languages and voices powered by a cloud HTTP-API connector. This TTS connector is really fast &amp;amp; dynamic to improve the caller experience. Now, you can develop smart services with a dynamic voice response according to any kind of content: text, numbers, dates,…
Providers Nuance Vocalizer Google Text-to-Speech API Amazon Polly Microsoft Azure Use Cases Enable to generate dynamic voice prompts Support most languanges with several voices Power advanced conversational applications Generate dates, numbers, names&amp;hellip; System Requirements Text-to-Speech feature requires VoiceXML IVR On Premise or Cloud CPaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming VoiceXML IVR 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-ivr-upcoming-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-ivr-upcoming-2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Sometimes, you have to reborn and change all&amp;hellip; Follow our socials and blog; be ready to discover our major release update since the born of Interactive Powers. Forget programming standards, IVR will become smart and conversational.
Keep posted on February 2019!
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines Smart IVR and Video RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Services: IaaS, PaaS, SaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the differences between IaaS, SaaS, and PaaS, the three main Cloud Computing models? IaaS, PaaS, SaaS are three Cloud computing models popular in the market. Depending upon the requirement a company can opt for any of the three models. Here we explain IaaS, PaaS, SaaS model in the best possible way so that anyone can understand and differential among them.
What is IaaS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is a Communications Platform as a Service Company</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The future of communications is driven by the cloud. Interactive Powers was created to help companies embed voice and video communication into the software applications and web applications that are part of their workflow and how they do business with the same communication options and convenience that mobile devices provide for their customers and employees in their person lives. With Interactive Powers, communication becomes more immediate and contextual resulting in better business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Hosting: Turnkey Solutions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Turnkey Solutions are designed to provide a quick startup without any IT requirement for your business. Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Broadcast · Auto Dialer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-auto-dialer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-auto-dialer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Calling all your business contacts at once. Auto Dialer is multi-channel dialing platform to send important alerts, promotions, updates, payment collection, political campaigns, phone surveys or notifications to your customers, employees, voters, and more. it instantly turns your browser into a complete outbound call center with an Intuitive user interface, advanced multi-campaign management and reporting. It can be easily connected to our VoiceXML IVR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Call Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-call-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-call-center/</guid>
      <description>Manage your own Call Center extension for Video RTC without any more technical requirements than just a Web Browser and Internet Access. Sometimes, changing all things doesn’t mean to build something totally new to improve the way you manage your Business Communications. Call Center is a Video RTC extension or standalone Omminchannel Call Center solution that allows to add advanced powers both to your agents and customers getting better and faster interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration. If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever. Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip; Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversational IVR applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Conversational IVR applications to improve your customer experience in phone services. Tradicional IVR systems have been built as limited DTMF and direct IVR dialogs for a long time. Yet it is not a secret that the experience using those solutions has is rather poor. In 70% of those interactions, the end users end up frustrated; at “best” case scenario are rerouted to a human agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Turnkey</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</guid>
      <description>The Turnkey Solutions for your business Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business. Web Dialer. Make Voice Calls from any modern Web Browser
Web Dialer allows all your customers and users to make phone calls directly to your PBX, IVR, Call Center from any desktop web browser (Firefox, Chrome, IE, Safari, Opera,…).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CPaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) is a form of cloud computing that is utilized to deliver communication applications like IVR or RTC to users over the internet. But, unlike SaaS which delivers specific apps and programs, Communication Platform as a Service is a bit closer related to IaaS. So, while IaaS is delivering the infrastructure, like servers and management tools, CPaaS is what delivers the entire communication platform for users to build and develop their own applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Software as a Service (SaaS) Software as a Service (SaaS) directly refers to any software that your business is using just about everyday. SaaS is of course a form of cloud computing, which allows for increase flexibility by relying on a third-party vendor to host and maintain the service — in this case, that service is that software. Since the software is hosted by a cloud provider, your business does not need to install and run applications on their own computers, or host their own servers in expensive data centers, yet still gains access to these powerful tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Google Speech API New Google Cloud Speech API Text-to-Speech for Developers has been released! Google is launching a new AI voice synthesizer as part of its suite of machine learning cloud tools. This new Cloud Speech API behind Google Assistant works really fast and use amazing voices to run your own advanced IVR or RTC services. For now, it’s only available in Beta version for Developers and already includes more than 30+ voices but this first cloud service aproach will probably grow quickly thanks to the AI WaveNet technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Cloud API for Voice over IP at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate. We are experiencing an Internet revolution that begins to affect basic services that we now operate with specific devices or business systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is Transforming Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:04:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Companies must understand that the processes of digital transformation driven by society are inevitable. In the last years, the improvement of customer support services accelerates the pace of adaptation to digital processes. The reason is the good results obtained by companies that have already integrated advanced digital tools, based, for instance, on WebRTC technology for real-time communication via the web or mobile applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technavio: IVR market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The Interactive Voice Response (IVR) market is growing, but what’s driving that growth? Market research analysts from Technavio suggest that the IVR, or Interactive Voice Response market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021. For those who are new to the industry, IVR systems are the solutions that give companies a stronger way of engaging their customers through various customer service solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forrester: Voice Channel as Self-service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons 63 percent of US adult callers report to use the voice channel for self-service (IVR) According to a 2016 Forrester Research study, 83 percent of U.S. adult Internet users had a phone conversation with a customer service representative in the past year. Sixty-three percent of them also reported using the voice channel for self-service, such as Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems whose Conversational AI capabilities enable callers to converse with a virtual agent as if there were a human rep on the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://webclient.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Meeting Point Make secure business online meetings&amp;hellip; · http://meetingpoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v1.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 1.3 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
