<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videocall on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videocall on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Videocall</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Peer-to-Peer Communication has never been so easy to build into a Website, Mobile App or Kiosks. Videocall provides a simpler way for companies to build their own video calling service via web or mobile application. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows, functions and it is easy to manage. Agents, users or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to quickly make your own Videocalling application with VideoRTC.js (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Users have asked us about our post on how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
In this new release we offer you a more detailed explanation of the steps to take, so that you can successfully build your mobile video application.
Introduction. From the moment you established a VideoRTC interaction, by connecting with the video gateway, until the call is finished, library’s range of events are executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works our Datachannel with VideoRTC.js</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post, we will show you how it works with Datachannel using VideoRTC.js and how to code quickly a simple service for a specific purpose.
Introduction First of all you need to know the modules in which we currently have available the Datachannel: These are the Videocall and the SPLIT. In this example we will use the first one, though the operation would be the same in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time for companies to use Web and Mobile RTC Applications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:58:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone bills with voice call minutes have been reduced or even disappeared both at home and in businesses. We communicate at work writing emails, tweets, posts, notifying by Skype, Google Hangout, LinkedIn or Facebook, and get in touch with our friends via Whatsapp or Snapchat, sharing multimedia content in real time. Phone calls are no longer a relevant channel in our personal communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build your Own Videoconference Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Today we bring you this interesting article on How to build your own videoconference service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step one: Setting up the basic structure As we have explained in previous posts, first of all it is important that you include dependency within your project or web page.
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Mobile Video Application (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you need to install an Ionic project in your system. If you don’t have it, you can download and follow the official guide from the Ionic Framework 2 web site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Videocall Service (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:59:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build your videocall service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you will need to include dependency within your project or web page:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.min.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  Next, we connect with the video gateway server:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>