<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videocall on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocall/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videocall on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocall/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calls · Scheduled vs Queued</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-queued/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-queued/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Why most companies have to change their mind about Video Calls productivity and integration? Existing “Video Meeting” solutions are used by most people for teleworking, remote business meeting or friends &amp;amp; family conversations (Zoom, Teams, LifeSize, Google Meet…). All these products are design to build conversations with a scheduled approach one-to-many or one-to-one. Companies that provide support to many customers do not work like this most of the time, they have to react in real-time to a massive inbound and outbound customers requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calls · Scheduled vs Team View</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-team-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-team-view/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Why most companies have to change their mind about Video Calls productivity and integration? Most “Video Meeting” solutions (Zoom, Teams, LifeSize, Google Meet…) used for teleworking, remote business meetings, doctor visits or friends &amp;amp; family conversations are based on scheduled invitation for specific users. A scheduled approach can be one-to-many or one-to-one when you are sending an invite to connect. In real-time processes, you will need to manage quickly the following inbound videocall in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How COVID-19 pandemic is changing doctor visits.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/how-covid19-pandemic-is-changing-doctor-visits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/how-covid19-pandemic-is-changing-doctor-visits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepick Healthcare is turning to video communications to stay connected during COVID-19, with minimal disruption to its operations. Source: Bloomberg News
Video check-up visits has become the norm for most healthcare providers during the coronavirus pandemic. Shelter-in-place orders have forced people into doing video sessions, and many doctors that never or rarely used video now have it as an essential tool. Simply put, video usage has seen a massive surge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 is a Disruptive Event for Telehealth</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels Telemedicine is now a becoming household term both for doctors and patients. If you need to see a doctor any time soon and it&amp;rsquo;s unrelated to COVID-19, chances are that your visit will be a virtual one. Today the people is open to the idea of seeing a doctor virtually instead of an in-person visit, there are a positive momentum and that awareness has increased. When a virus outbreak occurs, diagnosing patients promptly, minimizing travel time, and reducing public exposure helps to curb the rate of infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times and habits have changed. Health and Safety are first. Simplicity and Speed too.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels We understand Telehealth has to be simple and fast, allowing doctors and patients to connect easier than ever during these difficult times! Interactive Powers as a leading video gateway developer has released Virgo Healthcare, a new smart videocall application &amp;ldquo;as a service&amp;rdquo; in response to the overwhelming increase virtual visits sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. This accessible and secure solution with hyper customization offers the greater doctor and patient experience for a such critical digital interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine is changing the face of Healthcare delivery during the Pandemic.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels The COVID-19 global pandemic has both rocked the economy and tested the limits of already-stretched healthcare systems. The COVID-19 / Coronavirus is quickly spreading its tentacles across the globe. This pandemic has brought out the best in people as new partnerships form to combat a common enemy. While the pandemic tears across the globe, so to do the unprecedented and innovative changes in pharma, manufacturing, and care delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build memorable responsive Real-Time Communications Widgets.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</guid>
      <description>There’s no question that live chat is getting huge. More and more, websites in every corner of the web are featuring that inviting little widget in the corner of their screens. Live chat support is a huge opportunity for businesses to add a powerful, customer-loved channel to their customer service strategy.
We do not understand Live Chat just for texting. From the beginning, our Live Chat Widgets have been designed to provide Text, Voice and Video at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Dialer · Escalating Text, Voice, Video.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons In the Digital Age, any business has to create the most advanced interactions with their customers. Add text, voice, and video chat to your business without reinventing communications and complexity. At Interactive powers, we understand business communications in real-time with a flexible, multi-channel and convergent approach that has to work on any device, any modern browser, any location or Internet access.
Text Chat Some online businesses requires to make the first step enabling a text chat conversation for any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Tips for Live Chat integration in your Website.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/8-tips-for-livechat-integration-in-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/8-tips-for-livechat-integration-in-your-website/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons All good businesses seek to have amazing interactions with their customers. The quality of client relations is a sure indicator of the success of any company, no matter what industry or size. If you make your clients feel valued, communicate with them easily, faster and make available to answer all questions or concerns, you are more likely to build brand loyalty, and they are more likely to recommend your product or service to others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Videocall</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Peer-to-Peer Communication has never been so easy to build into a Website, Mobile App or Kiosks. Videocall provides a simpler way for companies to build their own video calling service via web or mobile application. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows, functions and it is easy to manage. Agents, users or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to quickly make your own Videocalling application with VideoRTC.js (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Users have asked us about our post on how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
In this new release we offer you a more detailed explanation of the steps to take, so that you can successfully build your mobile video application.
Introduction. From the moment you established a VideoRTC interaction, by connecting with the video gateway, until the call is finished, library’s range of events are executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works our Datachannel with VideoRTC.js</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post, we will show you how it works with Datachannel using VideoRTC.js and how to code quickly a simple service for a specific purpose.
Introduction First of all you need to know the modules in which we currently have available the Datachannel: These are the Videocall and the SPLIT. In this example we will use the first one, though the operation would be the same in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time for companies to use Web and Mobile RTC Applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:58:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone bills with voice call minutes have been reduced or even disappeared both at home and in businesses. We communicate at work writing emails, tweets, posts, notifying by Skype, Google Hangout, LinkedIn or Facebook, and get in touch with our friends via Whatsapp or Snapchat, sharing multimedia content in real time. Phone calls are no longer a relevant channel in our personal communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build your Own Videoconference Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Today we bring you this interesting article on How to build your own videoconference service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step one: Setting up the basic structure As we have explained in previous posts, first of all it is important that you include dependency within your project or web page.
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Mobile Video Application (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you need to install an Ionic project in your system. If you don’t have it, you can download and follow the official guide from the Ionic Framework 2 web site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Videocall Service (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:59:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build your videocall service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you will need to include dependency within your project or web page:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.min.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  Next, we connect with the video gateway server:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>