<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contactcenter on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/contactcenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contactcenter on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/contactcenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! **Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>