<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>contactcenter on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/contactcenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in contactcenter on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/contactcenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HD Quality / Video Recording</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires scalable HD quality and powerful video recording for any size professional service.  No one wants laggy audio or pixelated video quality in a meeting, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re meeting with clients or prospects. Interactive Powers comes with crystal-clear HD video and the most advanced video recording storage system for any size Video Call / Contact Centers deployment.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Centric / Unified Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires powerful real-time communications where Video is a top priority integrated channel.  Beyond video calls, what if your team also communicates through phone calls and text chat? Interactive Powers lets you consolidate all those tools into one. Talk, message, and meet all from one convenient channel. That makes for fewer software to pay for and manage and less time wasted on context-switching for all your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust Security Setting</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC Privacy and Security are key mandatory questions for your business and customers.  Keep your meetings secure with strong 256-bit encrypted real-time communications and session tokenization. Interactive Powers&#39; settings allow the host to mute participants, process biometrics API, lock file sharing, limit screen sharing, encode parameters and much more.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.0 features to get the best Video CC experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Control / Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 15:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires at least the same transactional call functions as Voice to ensure agents performance.  In our agent side, all the call controls you need are easily in reach. Adjust your call settings, start a screen share, mute and unmute yourself, or start and pause yourself or video recording. It&amp;rsquo;s all in a clean, video first, easy-to-use interface that lays out all these options for you right on the screen and our flap button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual Screen Sharing / CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC without advanced web collaborative tools, is like a Call / Contact Center without call management.  Need to zoom in on a design mockup or run through a contract approval? Interactive Powers dual screen sharing feature lets double share contents from agent and user at the same time. By the way, you choose between sharing a specific window or tab or your whole desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Responsive based Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers No Apps, No Downloads, No Register is a must be, not an option for your Video CC deployment.  Some video conferencing software will make you download the desktop or mobile app to host and join video calls. But Interactive Powers solutions are browser-based, which means it won’t force you or your clients to download an app. Host and join meetings from a web browser using your computer or mobile device, and get it all running with No Apps, No Downloads, No Register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call / Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 12:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Delivering real human interactions and unified collaboration in your Digital Space.  Need to meet face-to-face virtually your clients? Start managing unlimited transactional video calls for your team. It isn&amp;rsquo;t always practical to have every single meeting in person. Even if there are lots of video meeting apps that are designed more for hangouts with colleagues and chatting with loved ones. Today, any Call / Contact Center should be turned into a Video CC to improve its inbound/outbound processes and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s next for customer behavior?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons The Covid-19 pandemic has changed the way we live, work and shop, it has created a need for new methods of engagement between contact centres and customers. Customers no longer care about the brands that they had been loyal for years, they simply want to shop in a safe, efficient and convenient manner; experience matters now more than ever.
Hyper-personalization This is an incredible opportunity for brands to show up for their customers and provide an extra level of ease and personalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How customer behavior has changed during the pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Customers are no longer caring about the brands that they had been loyal to for years, now they simply want to shop with brands that make their life easier and better, expecting clear and easy options for contacting any post-pandemic customer service.
Remote Working is Required Consumers are now building their whole lifestyles around their homes as centres of gravity where they work and stay healthy, shopping online more and 30% hope to work more from their home in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowered Omnichannel with Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Traditional Omnichannel is not enough to provide a complete Digital Experience.  Video RTC solutions provide many integrations to enable an Empowered Omnichannel over your existing channels and services keeping your existing Contact Center platform. Video RTC is ready to be connect to any CC handling a SIP connectivity interface that mean most of on premise or cloud based products.
Traditional Omnichannel Traditional Omnichannel use to include following features:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Transferring Interoperability</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: FreePik. Creative Commons Interoperability becomes the key requirement: a seamless video transfer integration between all software contact center solutions.  Contact centers, like the rest of the communications industry, are experiencing a rapidly changing landscape. These changes in technology are spurring changes in human behaviors and customer expectations. The post-COVID19 situation is making the Customer Experience (CX) a key factor in the consumer decision-making process.
It’s no longer a world of call centers, today’s contact center has to be prepared to handle omnichannel communications: video calls, calls, emails, online chat, and text messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling: On Queue</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers edited. Video Calling has to be &amp;ldquo;On Queue&amp;rdquo; to reach the highest effectivity and productivity to ensure the best Customer Experience and ROI.  Video RTC for Genesys a unique complementary solutions for Contact Center that allow to handle Video Calling “On Queue” for your Contact Center thanks to SPLIT Forward / SPLIT Reverse a convergent WebRTC / SIP communications integration. Most existing Video powered addons are only working “Off Queue” because these products do not control any ACD event during all digital interactions and obviously cannot manage both inbound / outbound phone calls and video calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect your Website to a Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way  Outdated technologies are weighing companies down by limiting their view of customers and making it more difficult to connect with them in the new digital age interactions over IP.
 Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons  What others still doing…
 Click-to-Call &amp;amp; Callback. This option requires to get the user phone number in oder to make a call; remember all new digital customers don’t like to give up a cell or landline number anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration.  If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever.  Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip;  Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Video RTC to your existing Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Whatever your contact center is, we can make it interoperable with videocalls and advanced online interactions.  Many companies fear that the integration of video in their contact centers will involve a large investment of human and economic resources. Because companies think they will be forced to change the entire contact center solution, they may ignore video integration and, therefore, the opportunity to significantly improve their services and customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers and Customer Experience in 2018</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 20:23:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Companies must recognize CX as a key competitive differentiator and make sweeping changes in Channels to keep up this year.  In the last years, digital technologies have changed the way we work and relate to each other. These changes have also impacted on customers’ expectations. Clients increasingly demand a more personalized, accessible and comfortable attention.
Daily Business Communications. Clients expect from companies the possibility of contacting them through the same variety of channels they use in their everyday life communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. By 2030, AI solutions will surpass the services provided by agents.  Just a few years ago, talking about Artificial Intelligence (AI) meant talking about a futuristic scenario. Today, AI is everywhere and, directly or indirectly, we are starting to use it almost every day. The rapid evolution of AI allows it to be increasingly applied to more sophisticated processes which require a high precision like customer services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat  Omnichannel experience. Omnichanneling opens the opportunity for call centers to take a significant step in improving customer services and surpassing clients’ growing expectations. It is one of the key for businesses to implement an integral strategy. Clients perceive the advantages as they can engage when needed and through the most convenient channel: chat, phone call, self-service or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat  Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Transformation: Doors of Opportunity for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:02:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All interactions cannot be managed by bots, since users, when facing with certain problems, need to contact a real agent. If consumer is not allowed to communicate with a person, it leads to frustration and the relation client-company is seriously damaged. At this point, video offers contact centers the possibility of developing a very differential customer experience management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does VideoRTC fit in my Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:36:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Call Centers have to upgrade their services to the next level implementing new advanced interactions  The ever-growing digital world can give new opportunities for existing contact centers to provide a superior customer experience. Nowadays new technologies drive clients to ask for multiple options when looking for support. It is here where VideoRTC can help your contact center to enhance its services.
Save time providing the right channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Revolution in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:00:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All of us, as consumers, are becoming increasingly familiar with the use of new channels. We must also take into account that the first generation of digital natives is entering into the market. However, phone continues to be the most widely used channel in customer service and voice over IP technology. This situation is specially extended in the Spanish business landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
