<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cx on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cx on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Chatbots NLU?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs. We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand it in few minutes, what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Chat vs Live Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the difference about these two chat modalities, and considerations to have during a text typed business communication? Most existing Contact Centers have added a Chat Channel to connect their agents with online connected users without the help of a phone. Today, It’s really important to understand properly what is the best way to use any Chat modality in order to avoid an integration nightmare in the future or less integration reworks for your business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about your Chat channel automation, extension and integration?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Existing business chat features have to be properly automated, connected and extended to provide a right value for any business application. It’s not just only a question of adding another channel, chat is a really poor conversation modality for humans. Of course, it provide very interesting advantages, because of its simplicity, quick adoption and low bandwidth requirements but it steel being a limited communication feature in a continuous evolution of online customers or consumers requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines IVR and RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>