<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cx on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cx on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>