<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videoconferencing on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoconferencing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videoconferencing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoconferencing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 59% of consumers want Real-Time personal offers designed especially for them Direct Communications. Integration of Real-Time voice and video helps to establish easy and seamless communications between customers and sellers. Sales increase if clients can solve their questions immediately, when they access the catalogue of products and services. By just clicking on a button, customers can ask about a product, a contract or the delivery time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 13:30:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Learning at convenience. The current pace of life and work prevents us from continuing our learning. Thanks to digital tools and Real-Times Communications improving knowledge is not out of reach anymore. E-learning increases accessibility and reach as e-learning courses are more affordable and fits with students’ timetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 12:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, 70% of mobile workers will use a tablet or a hybrid device that has tablet-like characteristics Expert Cooperation. The technician can contact remotely experts in real time. This option allows them to have the support they need to finish the job in the first visit.
Field to Office Connection. Real-Time Communications enable field workers to immediately share data, photos or videos with the teams in the office, all without leaving the work site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Video-based learning. Video use is increasing and video features are critical in e-learning. Video allows students to access lectures, but also share content with their peers and professors, as well as tutoring in live real time interactions.
Mobile Learning. Mobile devices are growing in popularity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video ID · Facial Recognition Plugins</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:28:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pexels. Creative Commons Facial recognition is a biometric method of identifying an individual by comparing live capture or digital image data with the stored record for that person. Facial recognition systems are commonly used for security purposes but they are increasingly applied in a wide variety of fields, like in mobile technology, online to shopping, even in medicine.
In a previous post we talked about secure identification API integrations and some of their uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 11:06:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 59% of consumers want real-time personal offers designed especially for them Legal Services. RTC technologies enable to provide your clients an alternative solution to traditional legal services. You can offer an immediate answer, interact through the most appropriate channel and share documents, including pictures or videos.
Marketing and Design. You can offer exciting interactions, where your customers have the opportunity to see real examples in interactive experiences and contract services after trying your products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 08:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service Keep the human touch. It is not only that customers can still chose to interact in person, but thanks to VideoRTC, they have now more options to communicate face-to-face. If clients need help while using self-service, they can contact an agent. Clients can also videochat with their bank advisors through a tablet or a mobile phone from the comfort of their homes, but living an experience similar to an in-person branch visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 12:45:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, 70% of mobile workers will use a tablet or a hybrid device that has tablet-like characteristics Faster Resolution Times. RTC technology enables peer interactions and collaborative experiences. It allows the field worker to count on immediate assistance from the office workers or experts to help solve technical problems in the work site. Combined with the wide variety of features available, which make it possible to send documents, photos or videos in real time, resolution times are accelerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:45:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons 41% of consumers state that a great customer experience, including convenience, is decisive in their loyalty to a brand Immediate assistance. One of the most valued elements for customers is having assistance when they need it. Real-time communications allow to significantly improve customer service, by offering an instant assistance. Clients no longer need to travel to the store, as they can interact with an agent in person, immediately and through different channels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week More data for a better service. Data provided by customers about their needs, preferences and individual tastes enable e-commerce businesses to create clients’ profiles and take into account their purchase history to better serve them. Clients should easily have the opportunity to give feedback, so their problems can be solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 10:48:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service Expert Advice. Video and voice over the internet make it possible to meet current customers’ expectations. More and more clients look for information on line and VideoRTC offers the opportunity to remotely discuss products and receive information from an expert.
ATMs. This technology allows to combine the advantages of self-service, such as rapidity and efficiency, with face-to-face customer service if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 12:44:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Collaboration tools improve team efficiency by 20% One of the keys of technical assistance success is effectiveness. Voice and video over the internet in real time provide tools to field professionals that make a noticeable difference in results. Real-time video, voice and messaging applications enable mobile workforces to get immediate additional support by sharing photos, data or videos with other experts. By improving communication, resolution times are speeded up and, therefore, costs are reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 13:45:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons 41% of consumers state that a great customer experience, including convenience, is decisive in their loyalty to a brand Live chat assistance. Advanced communications must take into account what is the most appropriate solution. Live chat is the ideal channel when customers need support for basic questions. It is easy and a time-saver.
See the product. Thanks to video and file sharing, you can show your products to your clients, through photos or videoconference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 11:06:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 35% of consumers say the smartphone will become their main purchasing tool In today&amp;rsquo;s market, it is crucial that businesses engage customers the way they communicate. Users are increasingly turning to the Internet for their personal communications, but also to make regular purchases or contract services. As online purchases increase, the success of a modern business depends on the ability to promote its products and services through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Omnichannel experience. Omnichanneling opens the opportunity for call centers to take a significant step in improving customer services and surpassing clients’ growing expectations. It is one of the key for businesses to implement an integral strategy. Clients perceive the advantages as they can engage when needed and through the most convenient channel: chat, phone call, self-service or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Industries</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons In 2016, two main channels for generating sales were ‘Stores’ at 79% and &amp;lsquo;Website&amp;rsquo; at 73% Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet offers the opportunity to find innovative to ways to respond to consumers’ expectations. This technology provides numerous channels that allow to adapt companies’ assistance to clients’ needs. By integrating features such as live chat, videoconferencing, phone calls or file sharing, you can remarkably improve customer experience and differentiate your store in a highly competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Improved Workflows and Processes. Patients can contact their doctor directly via mobile phone or tablet. In this way, it is their usual doctor who decides if the patient needs to go to the medical center to receive care. In cases of urgent care, their doctor guides the patient through teleconference until the arrival of a health team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week Pre-sales support. Video options make it possible to show products to customers. They can check its appearance and functionality, making more informed purchase decisions.
Personalized shopping. Video and voice over the Internet allow you to pay the same special, individual attention to online customers as in face-to-face interactions in a more efficient way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels In 2016, the worldwide revenue for self-paced elearning was $ 46,674.67 Real-Time Video and Voice over the Internet open opportunities for everyone who wants to learn something. Online learning is gaining popularity as more and more students demand more flexibility that new technologies can provide. E-learning broadens the options of programs and degrees, since students can access to educational institutions all over the world. Self-paced learning allows students to arrange a learning schedule that meets their individual needs, at a lower price and without leaving the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Physician E-visits. The main advantage of telehealth for patients is convenience. They can save time as it is not necessary for sick patients to travel to his doctor’s office.
Wellness Services. VideoRTC provides the opportunity to attend healthy lifestyle programs from the comfort of home.
Health Monitoring. Patients who need treatment after surgery or due to chronic diseases can be monitored remotely in real time by health professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telehealth Market will reach $1,9 billion by 2018 Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are changing the relations among patients and physicians. On the one hand, telemedicine is an emergent industry which makes it possible to expand services offered by health institutions, while it helps to solve some of the current economic problems faced by hospitals. On the other hand, within minutes, patients will have the opportunity to receive medical care from anywhere and they will avoid spending time in the doctor&amp;rsquo;s waiting room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>