<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videoconferencing on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoconferencing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videoconferencing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videoconferencing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Omnichannel experience. Omnichanneling opens the opportunity for call centers to take a significant step in improving customer services and surpassing clients’ growing expectations. It is one of the key for businesses to implement an integral strategy. Clients perceive the advantages as they can engage when needed and through the most convenient channel: chat, phone call, self-service or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Industries</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons In 2016, two main channels for generating sales were ‘Stores’ at 79% and &amp;lsquo;Website&amp;rsquo; at 73% Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet offers the opportunity to find innovative to ways to respond to consumers’ expectations. This technology provides numerous channels that allow to adapt companies’ assistance to clients’ needs. By integrating features such as live chat, videoconferencing, phone calls or file sharing, you can remarkably improve customer experience and differentiate your store in a highly competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 11:06:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 35% of consumers say the smartphone will become their main purchasing tool In today&amp;rsquo;s market, it is crucial that businesses engage customers the way they communicate. Users are increasingly turning to the Internet for their personal communications, but also to make regular purchases or contract services. As online purchases increase, the success of a modern business depends on the ability to promote its products and services through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Improved Workflows and Processes. Patients can contact their doctor directly via mobile phone or tablet. In this way, it is their usual doctor who decides if the patient needs to go to the medical center to receive care. In cases of urgent care, their doctor guides the patient through teleconference until the arrival of a health team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week Pre-sales support. Video options make it possible to show products to customers. They can check its appearance and functionality, making more informed purchase decisions.
Personalized shopping. Video and voice over the Internet allow you to pay the same special, individual attention to online customers as in face-to-face interactions in a more efficient way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels In 2016, the worldwide revenue for self-paced elearning was $ 46,674.67 Real-Time Video and Voice over the Internet open opportunities for everyone who wants to learn something. Online learning is gaining popularity as more and more students demand more flexibility that new technologies can provide. E-learning broadens the options of programs and degrees, since students can access to educational institutions all over the world. Self-paced learning allows students to arrange a learning schedule that meets their individual needs, at a lower price and without leaving the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Physician E-visits. The main advantage of telehealth for patients is convenience. They can save time as it is not necessary for sick patients to travel to his doctor’s office.
Wellness Services. VideoRTC provides the opportunity to attend healthy lifestyle programs from the comfort of home.
Health Monitoring. Patients who need treatment after surgery or due to chronic diseases can be monitored remotely in real time by health professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telehealth Market will reach $1,9 billion by 2018 Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are changing the relations among patients and physicians. On the one hand, telemedicine is an emergent industry which makes it possible to expand services offered by health institutions, while it helps to solve some of the current economic problems faced by hospitals. On the other hand, within minutes, patients will have the opportunity to receive medical care from anywhere and they will avoid spending time in the doctor&amp;rsquo;s waiting room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>