<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Call Center on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/call-center/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Call Center on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:18:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/call-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Reasons why you should add Video channels to your Contact Center (ES)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-contact-center-infographic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-contact-center-infographic/</guid>
      <description>Infographic source: Interactive Powers. Download in PDF.
Summary: Spanish
 Mejorar la Comunicación entre agente y usuario. Incrementar la Valoración de la atención prestada. Aumentar la Eficiencia en la resolución de incidencias. Usar Dispositivos digitales móviles o navegadores web. Ofrecer nuevas capacidades de Colaboración en línea. Mejorar la Seguridad con la verificación visual de identidad. Eliminar la Numeración telefónica nacional o internacional. Ofrecer una Experiencia del cliente más próxima a la presencial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Call Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-call-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-call-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Video RTC enables to transfer any video call by simply dialing the extension of a queue or agent. Video Call Transferring, or Video Call forwarding, is a process of relocating an inbound video call to another agent. Video Call Transfer is very useful for video agents and internally for contact center teams. Video agents use call transferring to instantly route incoming calls throughout the Contact Center or Organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>