<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biometrics on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/biometrics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biometrics on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:28:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/biometrics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video ID · Facial Recognition Plugins</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:28:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pexels. Creative Commons Facial recognition is a biometric method of identifying an individual by comparing live capture or digital image data with the stored record for that person. Facial recognition systems are commonly used for security purposes but they are increasingly applied in a wide variety of fields, like in mobile technology, online to shopping, even in medicine.
In a previous post we talked about secure identification API integrations and some of their uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>