<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Healthcare on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/healthcare/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Healthcare on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:10:39 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/healthcare/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine at School</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/pediatrics-telemedicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:10:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/pediatrics-telemedicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons One of the leading sectors among advanced solutions is Real-Time Communications technology. Communication through voice, video or messaging in real time is opening up endless applications for many businesses, including telemedicine. Until now, telehealth has focused on hospitals and adults, but new opportunities start being considered.
Don&amp;rsquo;t skip classes anymore. When children need to see a doctor, not only do they miss school, but parents have to leave work for appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: Time-Saver, Better Access and More Services</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 10:26:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interl Free Press. Creative Commons There is no greater need for a personalized customer experience than in healthcare. But, at the same time, busy patients demand new ways to communicate with their doctors to save time. Thanks to technology RTC innovations, telehealth can make healthcare easier for patients.
Why should healthcare industry take advantage and adapt to technology trends? Time-saver Telemedicine allows to save time spent traveling to doctor’s office and waiting for the appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70 percent of all Doctor’s Office Visits are Unnecessary</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 10:00:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent study by PricewaterhouseCoopers, one in four people indicate that it takes more than 30 days to get an appointment with their physician. Many of these cases result in an unnecessary visit to the emergency room. Overall, the total cost of unnecessary emergency room visits is just under $14 billion annually. One of the most common reasons for these unnecessary visits include patient convenience, symptoms that occur after hours or on the weekend, or the patient was unable to get a timely appointment with their physician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>