<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voip2day on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voip2day/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voip2day on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voip2day/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2018!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2018, 11th Anniversary Freak Conferences, on November 14th &amp;amp; 15th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about CPaaS for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “Communications Platform as a Service”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation.
We would like to thank our partners, USA-VOIP and Avanzada7, and all the people who were involved in organizing the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us at VoIP2Day to talk about Communications Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Communications Platform as a Service at next VoIP2DAY2018 11th Freak Conferences edition:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
 Keynote: Communications Platform as a Service Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 14th, 2018 Time: 12:30pm  Synopsis The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2017!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:12:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2017, 10th Anniversary Conferences, on November 16th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “The Cloud API revolution is coming.”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in voice integration APIs exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP at next VoIP2DAY2017 10th Anniversary Conferences:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
 Keynote: The Cloud API Revolution is coming to VoIP Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 16th, 2017 Time: 10:00am  Synopsis Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>