<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Industries on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/industries/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Industries on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/industries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center 路 Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce 路 Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services 路 Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare 路 Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telehealth Market will reach $1,9 billion by 2018 Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are changing the relations among patients and physicians. On the one hand, telemedicine is an emergent industry which makes it possible to expand services offered by health institutions, while it helps to solve some of the current economic problems faced by hospitals. On the other hand, within minutes, patients will have the opportunity to receive medical care from anywhere and they will avoid spending time in the doctor&amp;rsquo;s waiting room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>