<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>whatsapp on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/whatsapp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in whatsapp on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/whatsapp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT WhatsApp?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>SPLIT WhatsApp: Enhancing Contact Center Communication with Voice and Video Calls. SPLIT WhatsApp offers a powerful feature that allows users to seamlessly transition from a standard WhatsApp conversation to a full-fledged video call. This functionality provides a smooth and efficient way to escalate communication when needed, enhancing the overall user experience. By enabling this scale-up capability, SPLIT WhatsApp bridges the gap between text-based messaging and face-to-face interaction, all within the familiar WhatsApp environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Click-to-Call into WhatsApp conversations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/click-to-call-into-whatsapp-conversations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/click-to-call-into-whatsapp-conversations/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik Make a Voice or Video Call from WhatsApp conversations WhatsApp business conversations with contact centers or bots face significant limitations. They primarily rely on text-based communication, lacking real-time, voice-to-voice interaction. These constraints often result in misunderstandings, slower problem resolution, and a less personal customer experience (CX). Without immediate vocal communication, the natural flow of conversation is impeded, making it challenging to convey tone, urgency, or complex information effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling for WhatsApp</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-for-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-for-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik Make video calls from WhatsApp conversations Have you ever found yourself in a situation where you needed to seamlessly transition from a WhatsApp text conversation between a user and an agent to a direct call or video call? Unfortunately, WhatsApp&amp;rsquo;s default functionality does not provide direct call trunking capabilities to enable Voice over IP (VOIP) calls within a conversation. This limitation significantly hampers the potential for enhancing user support experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dangers of Instant Messaging apps for businesses: WhatsApp, Messenger, TikTok...</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dangers-of-instant-messaging-apps-for-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dangers-of-instant-messaging-apps-for-businesses/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers In the current digital context, companies are increasingly accustomed to and promoting buttons the use of Instant Messaging or similar social media tools on their websites such as Meta ones: WhatsApp, Messenger, Instagram, or TikTok to chat with their customers openly. However, these channels are not completely secure or private, which can be dangerous for both companies and customers. Although it is tempting to use these options because they are very popular and familiar among consumers, it is important to consider all risks involved.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
