<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>callcenter on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/callcenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in callcenter on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/callcenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Average Handle Time  Score (AHT)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/average-handle-time-score-aht/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/average-handle-time-score-aht/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does AHT differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center?  What is a Average Handle Time Score (AHT)? When you work in customer support, you know how important it is to optimize your handle times. But while it’s clearly important to reduce average handling time at a Call / Contact Center, it’s not always that simple. Average handle time (AHT) is, as you’ve probably guessed, the average amount of time that a customer call takes from start to finish a process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Call Resolution Score (FCR)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/first-call-resolution-score-fcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/first-call-resolution-score-fcr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does FCR differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center?  What is a First Call Resolution Score (FCR)? First Call Resolution (FCR) can come in handy as one of many important metrics to keep track of in the pursuit of exceptional customer service. Furthermore, FCR measures a company&amp;rsquo;s ability to resolve phone calls, chats, emails, video calls, and website customer interactions resolved on the first contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Satisfaction Score (CSAT)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-satisfaction-score-csat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-satisfaction-score-csat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does CSAT differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center?  What is a Customer Satisfaction Score (CSAT)? A big strength of Customer Satisfaction Score (CSTA) is an easy way to close the loop on a customer interaction and determine whether or not it was effective in producing happiness. If for some reason the experience wasn&amp;rsquo;t satisfactory, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to pinpoint that moment and take actions to remedy the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Web ACD platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 10.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux Debian 10    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in an ACD service.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
