<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>support on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in support on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC for Genesys / Demo Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/demo-center-video-rtc-for-genesys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/demo-center-video-rtc-for-genesys/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Getting started&amp;hellip; Demo Center is only available for Customers and Partners that are deploying or running our platforms, if you are not registred please contact our Sales Team to get all information and partnerships.
Ask for your Live Demo, register and login at: https://support.ivrpowers.com
Frontend portal integrations:
 Click-to-Video (Button) Scan-to-Video (Widget) Chat-to-Video (Live Chat)  Click-to-Video Click-to-Video is powered by our responsive desktop/mobile widget.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Web ACD platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 10.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux Debian 10    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in an ACD service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Connectivity Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Freepik. Creative Commons The following article outlines Video RTC and Mobile SDKs’ requirements for network connectivity. It lists the Interactive Powers CPaaS servers’ ports and IP addresses that the Widgets, Webclients or SDKs must be able to reach, and the bandwidth required for quality audio &amp;amp; video. As shown in the diagram below, two types of connections are required, Signalling and Media for Users and Agents sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Device &amp; Web Browser Detection</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-browser-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-browser-detection/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Check your Mobile Device and Web Browser Many modern devices and web browsers are fully compliant with a WebRTC connection&amp;hellip;
https://webrtc.demo.ivrpowers.com/poc/detection/
Please contact us, if you get specific device data that you need to black-list or white-list.
Dump Sample:
Browser: Firefox 76 76.0 OS: Mac OS X 10.15 1.4.0 Chrome check: undefined Microphone: true Speakers: false Webcam: true isApplyConstraintsSupported: true isCreateMediaStreamSourceSupported: true isGetUserMediaSupported: true isMobileDevice: false isPromisesSupported: true isRtpDataChannelsSupported: false isVideoSupportsStreamCapturing: true isWebRTCSupported: true isWebSocketsSupported: true isWebsiteHasMicrophonePermissions: false isWebsiteHasWebcamPermissions: false Please, contact our support for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Smart IVR platforms are designed to run over a Linux CentOS 7 x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.centos.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux CentOS 7    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a IVR service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Video RTC platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 11.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux Debian 9-11    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a RTC service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Getting started&amp;hellip; Help Center is only available for Customers and Partners that are deploying or running our platforms, if you are not registred please contact our Sales Team to get all information and partnerships.
Register and Login at: https://support.ivrpowers.com
Service Desk Portals:
 Smart IVR Video RTC Cloud Hosting Solutions  Get support with our team in a single place Channels available:
 Email Web Portal, when logged in at: https://support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 4.0: Ready for Debian 9</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-upgrade-debian9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-upgrade-debian9/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Here’s how to go from Debian 8 to Debian 9  If you running a Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) since 2017 or 2018, then your operating system is on Debian 8. To move up to the next update or version 4.0 you will have to upgrade to Linux OS Debian 9 (Stretch) x86 64-bit.
Our next binary packages or CPaaS instances will now includes an installer script to automatically take you to Debian 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s E-commerce become a Better Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Latest Video Real-Time Communications can be decisive to improve e-commerce services. First of all, because they are becoming very accessible and easy to use through web browsers or most of mobile devices. Plugin downloads are no longer required, you just click and your are connected. Secondly, remember that creating a live interaction with your customers like a live chat or video call channels is a proven way to increase your sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
