<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>customerengagement on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/customerengagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in customerengagement on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/customerengagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>101 Reasons Why You Need To Embrace Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/101-reasons-to-embrace-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/101-reasons-to-embrace-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: WebBuilder Live chat is the way to go! You are undoubtedly aware of the importance of customer service on your online business’ road to success. But, what you may not know is that customers’ expectations have now reached new heights, demanding instant support and fast acting. In order to keep up with the latest trends, it is essential to improve customer experience. If you cannot think of an innovative way to do so – we have the answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
