<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Livechat on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/livechat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Livechat on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/livechat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Banking Revolution is coming</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</guid>
      <description>We are increasingly moving on line. And bank customers are not an exception. Financial businesses need to adapt their services to the new life styles and trends. One of the options is live video chat.
Video banking allows to deliver the best possible experience to online customers. Thanks to live video chat technology financial services can offer to their customers face to face experiences without leaving the comfort of their houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to Customer Experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of Video Chat:
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>