<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ia on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ia on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How IVR can help to improve your VoIP services?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Most people think that the Digital Revolution in Telephony has already occurred when voice over IP communications has progressively replaced landline connections. Currently, most telephony is digital and IP powered but that’s not the only thing that voice telecommunication requires in order to become more attractive and useful to users. You have to understand that there’s no difference for users in making phone calls via Landline or in a SIP extension, the user calling experience is remains the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip; Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>