<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketing on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketing on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Our Brand &amp; Media Kit</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The Interactive Powers brand is an expression of our team, culture and the solutions we create. To tell our story and represent our brand, here are our brand assets. We’d like to keep our brand consistent. If you have questions about how to use the Interactive Powers brand correctly, reach out to us.
Our Story Interactive Powers provides Smart IVR and Video RTC platforms to reimagine enterprise customer service to deliver standout experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with your customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2022/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Wishing you a wonderful holiday season. We are grateful for the opportunity to collaborate and celebrate with our community. We hope that you are able to cherish these holidays and enjoy a truly remarkable gift - the gift of togetherness. With our partners and clients, we venture into a new year filled with opportunity.
Merry Christmas 2022 and hope you to your loved ones.
God bless you all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2022!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2022/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, inspiration and happiness be yours throughout New Year 2022! Hard work, creativity, and commitment to excellence has been invaluable to us this 2021. As we step into another year, I wish you confidence and courage to accept new challenges and work further towards your goals!
Happy New Year! Wishing all the best to you and your family as we head into 2022! 🍾 🥂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Wishing you a wonderful holiday season. The year 2021 has also been a year of growth for Interactive Powers and impresive video adoption, in many industries. We are proud enabling businesses to stay connected to their customers growing and improving their business communication services.
From all our team at Interactive Powers, we want to express sincere gratitude for our amazing clients, partners, and all people who give us meaning and drive us forward every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplah, Creative Commons Celebrate your blessings and cherish the memories that you&amp;rsquo;ve shared, with happiness and cheer. Interactive Powers wants to give special thanks to every customer and business for all the support you have given us through the years!
We wish every one a wonderful and happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🎉
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What’s next for customer behavior?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/whats-next-for-customer-behavior/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons The Covid-19 pandemic has changed the way we live, work and shop, it has created a need for new methods of engagement between contact centres and customers. Customers no longer care about the brands that they had been loyal for years, they simply want to shop in a safe, efficient and convenient manner; experience matters now more than ever.
Hyper-personalization This is an incredible opportunity for brands to show up for their customers and provide an extra level of ease and personalization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How customer behavior has changed during the pandemic?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Oct 2021 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/how-customer-behavior-has-changed-during-the-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Customers are no longer caring about the brands that they had been loyal to for years, now they simply want to shop with brands that make their life easier and better, expecting clear and easy options for contacting any post-pandemic customer service.
Remote Working is Required Consumers are now building their whole lifestyles around their homes as centres of gravity where they work and stay healthy, shopping online more and 30% hope to work more from their home in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: Open Standard Technology for Browsers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-standard-technology-noapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2021 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-standard-technology-noapp/</guid>
      <description>Enabling embed Business Communications into any Web interface with Video RTC WebRTC (Web Real Time Communication) enables peer-to-peer communication with desktop and mobile browsers. In other words, WebRTC allows you to exchange any kind of media through the web (such as video, audio and data) without any required plugin or component. All our solutions are now following the #NOAPP approach avoid any requirement to download, install any app or plugin in any device to get live communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 most popular blog posts in 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Freepik Creative Commons. Video Real-Time Communications and Voicebot IVR were key themes during this 2020. The most viewed posts in our blog this year are following some important updates of this challenging year. To prepare 2021, we share this TOP 10 list:
1- What is a STUN/TURN server (TOP) The best description of what is a STUN/TURN server you where looking for… https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/
2- Video RTC - Web Browsers support in 2020!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2021!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, inspiration and happiness be yours throughout New Year 2021! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our clients, partners, employees, providers, and friends for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.
We gratefully want to wish you a better New Year 2021! 🍾 🥂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Sending our best wishes to you and yours. The year 2020 has been a strange, hard and challenging year for everyone, but one that has forever cemented the importance of digital connection in our personal and business lives when safety or social distancing is required. It has also been a year of growth for Interactive Powers and video adoption, in general. We are proud of the part we are playing in enabling businesses to stay connected to their customers growing and elevating their services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Miami-Dade County!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Very honoured to have been presented with the key of Miami by Miami-Dade Beacon Council &amp;amp; Mayor Carlos Gimenez. A trully wonderful and welcoming city.
Es un gran honor que Miami-Dade Beacon Council y el alcalde Carlos Giménez nos hayan entregado la llave de Miami. Una ciudad verdaderamente maravillosa y acogedora.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik, Creative Commons Celebrate your blessings and cherish the memories that you&amp;rsquo;ve shared, with happiness and cheer. Interactive Powers wants to give special thanks to every customer and business for all the support you have given us through the years!
We wish every one a wonderful and happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🎉
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39;, it&#39;s a must have.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Now, It&amp;rsquo;s won’t be an option. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of business survival in post-COVID-19 society. Just one year ago, we had annouced that Video was no longer &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; for Call Centers, now it will change the entire world market.
Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications
As you may read in the research analyts reports, Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications according to &amp;ldquo;more optimistics&amp;rdquo; predictions published past year as usual&amp;hellip; Even, if video was much better than voice for any digital real time human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers at next eMerge Americas 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us next days 30th - 31h March at eMerge Americas event at Miami Beach, Florida For the first time, Interactive Powers (ivrpowers.com) will be attending eMerge Americas, March 30 – 31, 2019 in Miami Beach - Convention Center. eMerge Americas is the premier technology event connecting the Americas. eMerge Americas is not just an event- it’s an ecosystem that is transforming Miami into the Tech Hub of the Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next days 11th - 14th February at next ITEXPO 2020 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida If you are attending ITEXPO and would like to discuss how to get enhance your business and opportunities with Cloud Communications for Conversational IVR, WebRTC gateways and CPaaS. Let&amp;rsquo;s set up some time to sit down and discover how we are helping all our partners with our Video RTC and Smart IVR solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are moving to a new Office!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are excited to announce that Interactive Powers has moved to a new location in the fast growing city of Alcobendas in Madrid (Spain). We spent the previous three years in Madrid Downtown &amp;ndash; our old office served us well, and we made great memories there, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more excited about our new modern space.
The new office is actually in Alcobendas business park, putting us in a really nice place for growing and looking toward the Madrid&amp;rsquo;s Skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39; for Call Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers It&amp;rsquo;s not Fashion, it&amp;rsquo;s a question of Evolution. Companies and brands that are not yet concidering a progresive transition of their phone channel to Real-Time Communications (RTC) within the next years for their customer care, sales or support will quickly become old fashioned and irrelevant for new consumers. The next customers generation is no longer accepting to downgrade their daily high speed interactions and expectations on advanced devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video calls are not an annoying feature for younger generations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Children feel more confortable having video calls than phone calls. If you have the opportunity to check how children understand Live Communications, you will quickly realise that phone is absolutly not a priority for them. They will never ask you about using a phone number and never want to remember just what it is. This new generation is born under a full digital world&amp;rsquo;s devices with high speed Internet and they absolutly are not aware about using limited or poor interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and Christmas season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners, employees, providers, friends and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and happy holiday season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 11:06:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 35% of consumers say the smartphone will become their main purchasing tool In today&amp;rsquo;s market, it is crucial that businesses engage customers the way they communicate. Users are increasingly turning to the Internet for their personal communications, but also to make regular purchases or contract services. As online purchases increase, the success of a modern business depends on the ability to promote its products and services through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky Halloween night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
