<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.
Our blog will allow us to leverage social technologies to engage in two-way communication with our community and to take your feedback into consideration as we create new content, tools and resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with you customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>