<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Brand &amp; Media Kit</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The Interactive Powers brand is an expression of our team, culture and the solutions we create. To tell our story and represent our brand, here are our brand assets. We’d like to keep our brand consistent. If you have questions about how to use the Interactive Powers brand correctly, reach out to us.
Our Story Interactive Powers provides Smart IVR and Video RTC platforms to reimagine enterprise customer service to deliver standout experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with your customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowered Omnichannel with Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Traditional Omnichannel is not enough to provide a complete Digital Experience. Video RTC solutions provide many integrations to enable an Empowered Omnichannel over your existing channels and services keeping your existing Contact Center platform. Video RTC is ready to be connect to any CC handling a SIP connectivity interface that mean most of on premise or cloud based products.
Traditional Omnichannel Traditional Omnichannel use to include following features:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 most popular blog posts in 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/top-10-blog-posts-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Freepik Creative Commons. Video Real-Time Communications and Voicebot IVR were key themes during this 2020. The most viewed posts in our blog this year are following some important updates of this challenging year. To prepare 2021, we share this TOP 10 list:
1- What is a STUN/TURN server (TOP) The best description of what is a STUN/TURN server you where looking for… https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/
2- Video RTC - Web Browsers support in 2020!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2021!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, inspiration and happiness be yours throughout New Year 2021! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our clients, partners, employees, providers, and friends for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.
We gratefully want to wish you a better New Year 2021! 🍾 🥂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Flip Camera</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-flip-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-flip-camera/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Switching all cameras during any video call for your services on Video RTC We are pleased to announce a new feature called Flip Camera ready for all Video RTC widgets that enables switch to next available camera inside your device. In case you’re using a smartphone or tablet, this feature switch from front to back camera. In desktop web browsers, this feature will change to the next camera until you make a complete loop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Background Blur</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-blackground-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-blackground-blur/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Defocusing agents background without any plugin. We are pleased to announce Background Blur powered by JS inside your web browser for all Video RTC agents without any plugin or software installation. This new feature is now available for projects under special conditions according to your web browser performance and devices deployed in the agent side.
Unretouched Screenshots:
System Requirements. This feature do now require specific hardware and run real-time video processing on the top of WebRTC, we recommend to use it only on desktop web browsers with enough CPU/RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Geolocation</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-geolocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-geolocation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Enable user geolocation detection for your business communications and video calls Knowing where your video callers location is a useful feature, that can help you provide a better support or customer service. For instance, you can show them results that are tailored to their location or display their location on the map or convert latitude/longitude to a street address.
What is IP geolocation? IP geolocation is the mapping of an IP address to the geographic location of the internet from the connected device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Sending our best wishes to you and yours. The year 2020 has been a strange, hard and challenging year for everyone, but one that has forever cemented the importance of digital connection in our personal and business lives when safety or social distancing is required. It has also been a year of growth for Interactive Powers and video adoption, in general. We are proud of the part we are playing in enabling businesses to stay connected to their customers growing and elevating their services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Widgets</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</guid>
      <description>Deploy full web responsive widgets with a single script or URL in your website or apps. Today we are excited to announce that we are open sourcing a new Widget for Video RTC to handle incoming or outgoing video calls and prompt users for input, record calls, connect callers to agents, and more.
Main features:
 FAB Button enabled Flip Camera (new) Mute Camera Mute Audio Live Chat File Sharing Dual / Single Screen Sharing Snapshot (optional) Overprint Logo  More options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo · Stats</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-stats/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Getting key analytics to follow Virgo Solution data usage: Emails, SMS, Calls&amp;hellip; Interactive Powers has released a new update for Virgo Business and Virgo Healthcare in response to the overwhelming increase virtual interactions sparked by the global pandemic. Now, administrators can check stats and export main account usage data.
Virgo Solutions are the simplest, accessible and secure scheduled video calling solution that offers easy and immediate coverage of a telework process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the user experience of any business visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Miami-Dade County!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers  Very honoured to have been presented with the key of Miami by Miami-Dade Beacon Council &amp;amp; Mayor Carlos Gimenez. A trully wonderful and welcoming city.
  Es un gran honor que Miami-Dade Beacon Council y el alcalde Carlos Giménez nos hayan entregado la llave de Miami. Una ciudad verdaderamente maravillosa y acogedora.
 Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik, Creative Commons Celebrate your blessings and cherish the memories that you&amp;rsquo;ve shared, with happiness and cheer. Interactive Powers wants to give special thanks to every customer and business for all the support you have given us through the years!
We wish every one a wonderful and happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🎉
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Customer Experience to the Next Level</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/taking-customer-experience-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Nov 2020 00:21:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/taking-customer-experience-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Businesses require to improve CX in a new way. Video has never been so relevant for all of us. Interactive Powers helps businesses bring their human-to-human interactions to the digital world with scalable, flexible and secure video communications. Video RTC with SPLIT technology is a key differentiator for any ACD (Automatic Call Distribuitor) to deliver the best possible voice &amp;amp; video experience with the lowest latency in a Contact Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Connectivity Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Freepik. Creative Commons The following article outlines Video RTC and Mobile SDKs’ requirements for network connectivity. It lists the Interactive Powers CPaaS servers’ ports and IP addresses that the Widgets, Webclients or SDKs must be able to reach, and the bandwidth required for quality audio &amp;amp; video. As shown in the diagram below, two types of connections are required, Signalling and Media for Users and Agents sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesland Webinar Event</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Salesland. What if in COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s times, we could sell more? Join us at next 25th November, 16:00 CET at next Salesland 20 years event!
With:
 Javier Arellano, Sales Manager and Businesss Development at Salesland Group. Ivan Sixto, Founder and CEO at Interactive Powers.  The pandemic crisis caused by Covid-19 has created an acceleration in the digitalization processes of our society, but what about people?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Channels for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Build consistent, effective, personalized engagements across Video channels with Voice, Video, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Co-browsing…. The most successful enterprises are defined by their ability to communicate. Today that means meeting consumers where they hangout – online, on multiple platforms like: Skype, FaceTime, WhatsApp, Telegram, Zoom, Microsoft Teams…
There’s no doubt that the name of the game today when we speak of Omnichannel Customer Experience is convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centribot Chatbot with Video Calling integration</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/centribot-chatbot-with-video-calling-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/centribot-chatbot-with-video-calling-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Centribal. Video RTC empowers Centribal chatbot platforms with real-time communications for any business. MIAMI, November. 16, 2020 — Centribal the creators of [Centribot]() and Interactive Powers the creators of Video RTC announce new video real-time communications integration. The Centribal Platform is the conversational tool that allows the possibility of creating various chatbots from a single location, easily, quickly and with simplicity. Centribot will be able to create and train your chatbots in the way that best suits you, to make the most out of the communication management with your customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scheduled Video Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scheduled-video-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scheduled-video-calling/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Scheduled Video Calls that enable the fastest face-to-face commmunication for a Remote Workforce. Imagine all your workforce requires to work from home or from anywhere, imagine you can&amp;rsquo;t connect all of them in unique real-time attention but they require to collaborate everyday each others to support your products and services. At Interactive Powers, we understand that kind of peer-to-peer (P2P) video calls are not just video meetings but something more specific between a call and a video room: we call this kind of interaction, Scheduled Video Calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Streaming with Video Call Queueing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/live-streaming-event-with-video-call-queueing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:21:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/live-streaming-event-with-video-call-queueing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Create a Live Streaming event and face-to-face connect your audiance to your sales team. Live Streaming can be the perfect engaging virtual event for your brand to attract a high number of viewers simulteanously. This is really great power of real-time but you can also do much more with your remote workforce team, if they can join any of this visitors at this big moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landing Page with Video Call Queueing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/landing-web-page-with-video-call-queueing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/landing-web-page-with-video-call-queueing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Enable your landing page or website visitors to join video agents in just one-click. Landing pages or Business Website receive visits from your customers at anytime, you should improve your customer support connecting one-to-one at this moment. A Chatbot, Form, Email is required but it could be not enough to engage a customer with your product or brand. Adding a Video Call Queueing enables that any customer can react and talk face-to-face with one of the sales agents at this moment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Call Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-call-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-call-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Video RTC enables to transfer any video call by simply dialing the extension of a queue or agent. Video Call Transferring, or Video Call forwarding, is a process of relocating an inbound video call to another agent. Video Call Transfer is very useful for video agents and internally for contact center teams. Video agents use call transferring to instantly route incoming calls throughout the Contact Center or Organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Transferring Interoperability</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: FreePik. Creative Commons Interoperability becomes the key requirement: a seamless video transfer integration between all software contact center solutions. Contact centers, like the rest of the communications industry, are experiencing a rapidly changing landscape. These changes in technology are spurring changes in human behaviors and customer expectations. The post-COVID19 situation is making the Customer Experience (CX) a key factor in the consumer decision-making process.
It’s no longer a world of call centers, today’s contact center has to be prepared to handle omnichannel communications: video calls, calls, emails, online chat, and text messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · REC Storage</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/rec-storage-for-video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/rec-storage-for-video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Securely archive all your audio / video streams in MP4 blended file or as RAW separate files. Get elastic cloud storage for Video RTC recordings with enterprise-grade capabilities, reliability, and security that is as simple as one, two, three. Just log into secure S3 Sockets, pick the Gigabytes or Terabytes you need, and select the AWS region to use. That’s it. Then sit back and enjoy call center-grade cloud recording with no compromises.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Image in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</guid>
      <description>Allows you o display an image as your background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls replacing your background by a nice picture removes all your surroundings so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can change your background, or add a background image during your video call sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call switching to Mobile Device</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-call-switching-to-mobile-device/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-call-switching-to-mobile-device/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Flip your frontend webcam stream to a mobile device in order move arround during a Video Call without hangup. Specific support or sales interaction could require agents or sales representative to move around a showroom during a video call using their smartphone without hangup.
We recommend to consider this agent side option in SPLIT that enable to switch easily to their mobile device using our QR code in screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scan to Video Call with QR code</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scan-to-videocall-with-qr-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/scan-to-videocall-with-qr-code/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Make better and safe local point of sales with Scan-to-Videocall in order to improve social distance and get face-to-face sales online support. You want your customers to directly video call your contact center using their smartphone without any mobile app, registration, pluging or download.
This Video RTC feature is very interesting to connect easily existing local services with a remote sales force team that will provide safe face-to-face support to users or customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Blur in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</guid>
      <description>Allows you to blur the background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls blurring your background makes your surroundings appear out of focus so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can blur your background during your meeting, event, or training session.
Unretouched Screenshots:
Need to add it right now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Tester</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Add a Four Steps Tester for your Video RTC services to improve Customer Experience and QoS. Most users are not aware about their communications and hardware conditions to make video calls over an Internet access. If you don&amp;rsquo;t take care about this, some of them will be disappointed of been rejected by technical issues. In order to improve your Customer Journey and Experience, add a simple testing four steps process in front of your Video RTC communications services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.2.1:
## [4.2.1] - 2020-08-13 ### Fixed - Fixed usrsctp vulnerability in SCTP module  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · PIN Access</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/pin-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/pin-access/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Connect easily any real-time session from any device or browser with a PIN code. If you wish to utilize Video RTC / Solutions as part of your support efforts, a custom PIN access, where your customers can enter a unique pin code to connect with an agent is another way to start co-browsing, screen sharing or voice &amp;amp; video calling. You only have to redirects your customers to a landing page like our new one: https://pwrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Device &amp; Web Browser Detection</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-browser-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2020 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-browser-detection/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Check your Mobile Device and Web Browser Many modern devices and web browsers are fully compliant with a WebRTC connection&amp;hellip;
https://webrtc.demo.ivrpowers.com/poc/detection/
Please contact us, if you get specific device data that you need to black-list or white-list.
Dump Sample:
Browser: Firefox 76 76.0 OS: Mac OS X 10.15 1.4.0 Chrome check: undefined Microphone: true Speakers: false Webcam: true isApplyConstraintsSupported: true isCreateMediaStreamSourceSupported: true isGetUserMediaSupported: true isMobileDevice: false isPromisesSupported: true isRtpDataChannelsSupported: false isVideoSupportsStreamCapturing: true isWebRTCSupported: true isWebSocketsSupported: true isWebsiteHasMicrophonePermissions: false isWebsiteHasWebcamPermissions: false  Please, contact our support for more information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons Securely share and browse in your web pages simultaneously with your customers. The Cobrowsing humanises the online sales and support experience, enabling your contact center agents to interact with your customers and assist them via a shared browser. Thanks to the use of the Cobrowsing, the communication becomes far more natural, effective, and efficient, bringing the customer-agent exchange closer to that of an in-store, in-person interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calls · Scheduled vs Queued</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-queued/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-queued/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Why most companies have to change their mind about Video Calls productivity and integration? Existing “Video Meeting” solutions are used by most people for teleworking, remote business meeting or friends &amp;amp; family conversations (Zoom, Teams, LifeSize, Google Meet…). All these products are design to build conversations with a scheduled approach one-to-many or one-to-one. Companies that provide support to many customers do not work like this most of the time, they have to react in real-time to a massive inbound and outbound customers requests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calls · Scheduled vs Team View</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-team-view/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 11:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-calls-scheduled-vs-team-view/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Why most companies have to change their mind about Video Calls productivity and integration? Most “Video Meeting” solutions (Zoom, Teams, LifeSize, Google Meet…) used for teleworking, remote business meetings, doctor visits or friends &amp;amp; family conversations are based on scheduled invitation for specific users. A scheduled approach can be one-to-many or one-to-one when you are sending an invite to connect. In real-time processes, you will need to manage quickly the following inbound videocall in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC Solutions Ecosystem</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-rtc-solutions-ecosystem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-rtc-solutions-ecosystem/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Extending and empowering your business with Video Interactions out of the Contact Center. The adoption of video communications continues to expand globally. As more businesses are using video to connect with their users or customers remotely and realizing the importance of improving their customer experience, it is more critical than ever for video interactions to be as simple as possible. This is why more and more teams today are choosing our solutions so that callers do not need to download or install any application to connect instantaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling: On Queue</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jul 2020 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-calling-on-queue/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers edited. Video Calling has to be &amp;ldquo;On Queue&amp;rdquo; to reach the highest effectivity and productivity to ensure the best Customer Experience and ROI. Video RTC for Genesys a unique complementary solutions for Contact Center that allow to handle Video Calling “On Queue” for your Contact Center thanks to SPLIT Forward / SPLIT Reverse a convergent WebRTC / SIP communications integration. Most existing Video powered addons are only working “Off Queue” because these products do not control any ACD event during all digital interactions and obviously cannot manage both inbound / outbound phone calls and video calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Ubox: No Touch Kiosks &amp; Screens</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Gesture controlled Kiosks &amp;amp; Screens with Video RTC to enable new customer experiences. MIAMI, July. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies the creators of UBOX and Interactive Powers the creators of Video RTC announce new phygital experiences joining gesture and video real-time communications. UBOX is also a marketplace of experiences where hardware and software developers, designers, artists and data scientists can collaborate in projects together from different parts of the world easily, thus providing end-to-end​ ​solutions to consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Video calling has become a major part of the new normal. Simplicity and Speed too. Interactive Powers has released Virgo Business in response to the overwhelming increase virtual interactions sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. The simplest, accessible and secure video calling solution offers easy and immediate coverage of a telework process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the user experience of any business visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How COVID-19 pandemic is changing doctor visits.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/how-covid19-pandemic-is-changing-doctor-visits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/how-covid19-pandemic-is-changing-doctor-visits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepick Healthcare is turning to video communications to stay connected during COVID-19, with minimal disruption to its operations. Source: Bloomberg News
Video check-up visits has become the norm for most healthcare providers during the coronavirus pandemic. Shelter-in-place orders have forced people into doing video sessions, and many doctors that never or rarely used video now have it as an essential tool. Simply put, video usage has seen a massive surge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Technologies and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Joining amazing eLearning Xlices tool with real-time experiences interactions MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies a pioneer in the field of elearning slide sharing Xlices, announces partnership with Interactive Powers to improve user experiences with real-time communications. In coming weeks, Xlices will be offered with advanced web voice calling features over web responsive service as well as over the phone.
Through this partnership, we will establish a framework for cooperation and work together to develop better software solutions, explore amazing Digital Transformation opportunities and amplify the impact along the eLearning on the customer journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers announces Video RTC integration with Genesys Cloud™</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 12:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Genesys - Interactive Powers Interactive Powers solutions combines with Genesys platforms to provide scalable Video Communications to Call Centers MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Interactive Powers has announced Video RTC is now available on the Genesys AppFoundry®, the industry&amp;rsquo;s largest dedicated marketplace focused on customer experience solutions. The AppFoundry allows Genesys customers from all market segments to discover and rapidly deploy a broad range of solutions that make it easier to interact with consumers, engage employees and optimize their workforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo Healthcare</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Times and habits have changed. Health and Safety are first. Simplicity and Speed too. Interactive Powers has released Virgo Healthcare solution in response to the overwhelming increase virtual visits sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. The simplest, accessible and secure Telehealth solution offers easy and immediate coverage of the consultation process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the patient experience of the visit.
Powered by Video RTC (WebRTC) - Interactive Powers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 is a Disruptive Event for Telehealth</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels Telemedicine is now a becoming household term both for doctors and patients. If you need to see a doctor any time soon and it&amp;rsquo;s unrelated to COVID-19, chances are that your visit will be a virtual one. Today the people is open to the idea of seeing a doctor virtually instead of an in-person visit, there are a positive momentum and that awareness has increased. When a virus outbreak occurs, diagnosing patients promptly, minimizing travel time, and reducing public exposure helps to curb the rate of infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times and habits have changed. Health and Safety are first. Simplicity and Speed too.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels We understand Telehealth has to be simple and fast, allowing doctors and patients to connect easier than ever during these difficult times! Interactive Powers as a leading video gateway developer has released Virgo Healthcare, a new smart videocall application &amp;ldquo;as a service&amp;rdquo; in response to the overwhelming increase virtual visits sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. This accessible and secure solution with hyper customization offers the greater doctor and patient experience for a such critical digital interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine is changing the face of Healthcare delivery during the Pandemic.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels The COVID-19 global pandemic has both rocked the economy and tested the limits of already-stretched healthcare systems. The COVID-19 / Coronavirus is quickly spreading its tentacles across the globe. This pandemic has brought out the best in people as new partnerships form to combat a common enemy. While the pandemic tears across the globe, so to do the unprecedented and innovative changes in pharma, manufacturing, and care delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altitude Software and Interactive Powers celebrate more than 5 years of Video interactions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/altitude-software-xperience-hub-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/altitude-software-xperience-hub-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Altitude Software - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions for Altitude Xperience Hub! MIAMI, May 2, 2020 — Interactive Powers and Altitude Software work together in complementary solutions since more than 5 years. That’s why we’re really excited to increase Altitude Software and Interactive Powers collaboration to offer the most complete Omnichannel Contact Center that powers limitless, continuous CX conversations that cross boundaries while raising the bar on real-time visibility and control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2:
## [2.2.1] - 10-04-2020 ### Fixed - The resizing of the history of recordings files was sometimes crashing the Asterisk. ## [2.2.0] - 30-03-2020 ### Added - New VoiceXML element &amp;lt;nlu&amp;gt; with support for Google GRPC Speech API - New Asterisk command to display current nlu sessions ### Changed - Project build now with c++11 version - Accounts information is now only loaded &amp;amp; displayed if the license loaded successfully ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39;, it&#39;s a must have.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Now, It&amp;rsquo;s won’t be an option. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of business survival in post-COVID-19 society. Just one year ago, we had annouced that Video was no longer &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; for Call Centers, now it will change the entire world market.
 Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications
 As you may read in the research analyts reports, Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications according to &amp;ldquo;more optimistics&amp;rdquo; predictions published past year as usual&amp;hellip; Even, if video was much better than voice for any digital real time human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.3.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.0:
## [3.3.0] - 2020-03-25 ### Added - Added a new event `onSipMessage` on the SPLIT Client to receive SIP Messages - Added a new streamOption `resolution` in all modules where video is used - Added a new className `is-local-video` in all local video elements  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes specific improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.2.0:
## [4.2.0] - 2020-03-25 ### Added - Enabled ScreenSharing in the WebClient for Chrome and Opera browsers - Added possibility to send links via chat - Added SPLIT reverse feature in the SPLIT Agent usecase - Added possibility to configure the autoclose option in &#39;forced&#39; mode for SPLIT usecases - Added a new URL parameter called `from` on the Webclient and Escalating usecases - Added a new theme parameter `resolution` in all usecases where video is used ### Updated - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers at next eMerge Americas 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us next days 30th - 31h March at eMerge Americas event at Miami Beach, Florida For the first time, Interactive Powers (ivrpowers.com) will be attending eMerge Americas, March 30 – 31, 2019 in Miami Beach - Convention Center. eMerge Americas is the premier technology event connecting the Americas. eMerge Americas is not just an event- it’s an ecosystem that is transforming Miami into the Tech Hub of the Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Phone Calls to DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are main questions about connecting a DialogFlow agent to a telephony system? It’s important to get some important differences between the Google Phone Gateway and our DialogFlow Gateway powered by a Smart IVR platform.
Can I get a Number (PSTN) from any country?  🟢 Phone Gateway = Yes, select a PSTN Number in the list of each available country. 🟢 DialogFlow Gateway = Yes, connect your own DDI Number or any IP PBX extensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect DialogFlow to your PBX?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Build a Voicebot IVR with DialogFlow for your existing PBX and telephony system. Continuing on our quest of better business communications, both old DTMF menus and speech direct dialog are outdated IVR options, we can replace them by the power of a DialogFlow advanced Conversational AI service.
Prerequisities 1- Text-to-Speech API account (TTS) You can connect any TTS according to your language and voice preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.1.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.1.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix a vulnerability in usrsctplib that has already been fixed, so make sure you pull this latest release if you&amp;rsquo;re using data channels. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.1.1:
## [4.1.1] - 2020-02-28 ### Fixed - Fixed critical vulnerability in `usrsctp` library  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR · Speech Recognition Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</guid>
      <description>More and better protocols to improve performance of your interactive phone services. Speech recognition is a key complementary feature for any IVR in order enables the recognition and translation of spoken language into text for your voice application coding. It is also known as automatic speech recognition (ASR) or speech to text (STT). Smart IVR support today three connectors since the last release 2.x and it has the ability to use them in perfect combination for all services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to improve your PBX with Conversational AI?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way In The New Digital Age, standards commons PBX functions used by most companies are weighing down Customer Experience (CX) making tedious to contact their phone services or customer assistance.
 Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons  What most companies still doing…
 DTMF Menus. Most PBX use touch tone menus to select departments, services or key an extension. Of course, everybody may knows how to press a key, but it’s not really confortable to do this with hands free, driving or when you don’t get the right option…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next days 11th - 14th February at next ITEXPO 2020 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida If you are attending ITEXPO and would like to discuss how to get enhance your business and opportunities with Cloud Communications for Conversational IVR, WebRTC gateways and CPaaS. Let&amp;rsquo;s set up some time to sit down and discover how we are helping all our partners with our Video RTC and Smart IVR solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a Video Channel to your existing Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Transform your existing call center into a more engaging, customizable, and interactive solution with video calls. In today’s competitive market, companies need call center software to connect in real-time cross web browsers and mobile devices. Adding advanced video interactions such web call, video call, live chat, file sharing, co-browsing, screen sharing… give your clients and agents the option to communicate better than ever with your brand.
 The Empowered Omnichannel: What any Contact Center in the Digital Age should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer-to-Peer?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</guid>
      <description>Make and Receive Video Calls between Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to manage and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) between two peers. This connection is based on a WebRTC communication session running voice, video and data.
 The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.
 How does Peer-to-Peer work? Peer-to-Peer (WebRTC) enables to connect many Web Browsers or Mobile Devices with Real-Time Communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Web Browsers support in 2020!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-web-browser-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-web-browser-2020/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration Video RTC Gateways are now ready to run most modern Web Browsers and Operating Systems for your Business. We can observe the success of WebRTC Technology through the evolution of web browsers. Increasingly more and more browsers are WebRTC-enabled, having incorporated the possibility of making video calls. In most of them users do not need even to install special applications or plugins. Let’s see what four of the most important web browsers on the market currently offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC-to-SIP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</guid>
      <description>Receive Audio Calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to control all media streams (video - audio - data) on any communication between users and a SIP softswitch or PBX/ACD. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice and data.
 Connect a Web Widget for any existing Call Centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1:
## [2.1.0] - 03-02-2020 ### Added - Support for the &amp;lt;data&amp;gt; element - Added noinputtimeout for the &amp;lt;record&amp;gt; element ## [2.0.3] - 03-12-2019 ### Fixed - Removed unnecessary error message when making a TTS request through HTTP - Added verification check for the existance of a cached file before trying to access it to avoid error messages - Fixed the conversion from interpreter value to JSI double numbers on subdialog return ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Reverse?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Make Video calls from your Contact Center to Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
 The Video Channel (Outbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Microsoft Edge support for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-microsoft-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-microsoft-edge/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway is now ready to run with Edge Browser over Windows computers and devices. At Interactive Powers, we are really excited that Video RTC platforms and API Framework / Mobile SDK are now supporting Microsoft’s new Chromium based Edge Browser aka Edgium. From now, your real-time applications will work on Microsoft’s latest Edge browser released without any changes or updates in your existing code / services already deployed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Forward?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</guid>
      <description>Receive Video calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
 The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect your Website to a Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way Outdated technologies are weighing companies down by limiting their view of customers and making it more difficult to connect with them in the new digital age interactions over IP.
 Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons  What others still doing…
 Click-to-Call &amp;amp; Callback. This option requires to get the user phone number in oder to make a call; remember all new digital customers don’t like to give up a cell or landline number anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build memorable responsive Real-Time Communications Widgets.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/responsive-real-time-communications-widget/</guid>
      <description>There’s no question that live chat is getting huge. More and more, websites in every corner of the web are featuring that inviting little widget in the corner of their screens. Live chat support is a huge opportunity for businesses to add a powerful, customer-loved channel to their customer service strategy.
We do not understand Live Chat just for texting. From the beginning, our Live Chat Widgets have been designed to provide Text, Voice and Video at any time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Dialer · Escalating Text, Voice, Video.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/webdialer-text-voice-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons In the Digital Age, any business has to create the most advanced interactions with their customers. Add text, voice, and video chat to your business without reinventing communications and complexity. At Interactive powers, we understand business communications in real-time with a flexible, multi-channel and convergent approach that has to work on any device, any modern browser, any location or Internet access.
Text Chat Some online businesses requires to make the first step enabling a text chat conversation for any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 Tips for Live Chat integration in your Website.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/8-tips-for-livechat-integration-in-your-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/8-tips-for-livechat-integration-in-your-website/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons All good businesses seek to have amazing interactions with their customers. The quality of client relations is a sure indicator of the success of any company, no matter what industry or size. If you make your clients feel valued, communicate with them easily, faster and make available to answer all questions or concerns, you are more likely to build brand loyalty, and they are more likely to recommend your product or service to others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Storage · Video Recording</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Securely archive all your audio / video streams in MP4 blended file or as RAW separate files. Video RTC (WebRTC) platforms enable to record all audio and video streams of your services to a secure, scalable Cloud Storage. Video Recording is connected to the SPLIT Forward / Reverse in order to process all video calls of your Contact Center.
Service Conditions This cloud recording service is available for CPaaS / SaaS on AWS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Smart IVR platforms are designed to run over a Linux CentOS 7 x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.centos.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux CentOS 7    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a IVR service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Video RTC platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 9.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux Debian 9    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a RTC service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Getting started&amp;hellip; Help Center is only available for Customers and Partners that are deploying or running our platforms, if you are not registred please contact our Sales Team to get all information and partnerships.
Register and Login at: https://support.ivrpowers.com
Service Desk Portals:
 Smart IVR Video RTC Cloud Hosting Solutions  Get support with our team in a single place Channels available:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.2.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.0:
## [3.2.0] - 2019-11-28 ### Added - Added new events on the Videocall and SPLIT modules to detect slow links with the remote video  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How IVR can help to improve your VoIP services?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-ivr-can-help-to-improve-your-voip-services/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Most people think that the Digital Revolution in Telephony has already occurred when voice over IP communications has progressively replaced landline connections. Currently, most telephony is digital and IP powered but that’s not the only thing that voice telecommunication requires in order to become more attractive and useful to users. You have to understand that there’s no difference for users in making phone calls via Landline or in a SIP extension, the user calling experience is remains the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why WebRTC makes VoIP services more attractive?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2019 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/why-webrtc-makes-voip-services-more-attractive/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash - Interactive Powers Nowadays telephony is still used under a specific network integration that is not all IP powered like PSTN numbering and specific rules to manage its traffic with operators. Until this day, Voice over IP has disrupted the telephony but still providing the same phone user experience; at the end, users are still dialing to a 9-10 digits number and all the call process is mostly the same.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.1.0:
## [4.1.0] - 2019-10-21 ### Added - Added support for Safari &amp;gt;= 12.1 - Added possibility to choose the default quality of the Webclient through theme configuration - Added autocall, autoclose and hangup button in the Escalating - Added a new config param in the Webclient and Escalating usecases to redirect when a call ends (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.1.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.1.0:
## [3.1.0] - 2019-10-21 ### Added - Added device field in the Opaque ID object - Added support for Safari &amp;gt;= 12.1 ### Changed - Aligned to the new VideoGateway `v4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t forget to train your Voicebot</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Like any human performance, your AI powered system requires to be properly trained. Training is the most important thing to consider to make your Voicebot IVR smart enough when it goes in production. Many projects forgot to review continuously learning rules, intents and transactions logs.
When a Voicebot or conversational agent does not understand you, it is because, in reality, he does not have been properly trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTS-API connectors updated!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45+ Languages &amp;amp; 300+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon, Google and Microsoft Cloud TTS-API Integration. Natural Language over the Phone&amp;hellip; All of you know about cognitive services is growing these days, and that&amp;rsquo;s why today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about our new TTS-API for &amp;ldquo;Text to speech&amp;rdquo;. This connector converts text into a dynamic natural voice in just a few milliseconds. There are a lot of Cloud Speech API, but we will focus on the Cloud Services main giants: Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Polly TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 27 Languages &amp;amp; 60+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon Polly Integration About Amazon&amp;hellip; Amazon Polly is a Text-to-Speech (TTS) service that uses advanced deep learning technologies to synthesize speech that sounds like a human voice. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the voice of Alexa and can do much more for your business too.
 Amazon has arround 60 voices across 30 languages and variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 30+ Languages &amp;amp; 180+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Google TTS Integration About Google&amp;hellip; Google Cloud is one of the major Enterprise Cloud Services in the world, so its API does not fall short. There are a lot of features that are worth of mention, but we don’t have that time so, here are some of main features we consider:
 Google has over 180 voices across 30+ languages and variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45 Languages &amp;amp; 75+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Microsoft Azure TTS Integration About Microsoft&amp;hellip; Microsoft Azure like Google Cloud provides his own Text To Speech API. It is quite big and here are some of its main features with more than 75 voices over 45 languages.
 Parameters for speed, pitch, volume, pronunciation, and additional pauses Custom voice models for developers and enterprises Neural Voices technology  To get more information, you can read Microsoft TTS documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Security improvement for WebRTC in Firefox 68</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/firefox68-requires-https-in-all-sources/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jul 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/firefox68-requires-https-in-all-sources/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Creative Commons Firefox 68 will now only expose camera and microphone in secure contexts. As of Firefox 68 — releasing past weeks — WebRTC camera and microphone will require an https connection to work. Access from insecure http will cease to work, matching how Chrome works. Camera and microhone are powerful features, and Firefox will now only expose them in secure contexts, a security and privacy improvement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are moving to a new Office!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are excited to announce that Interactive Powers has moved to a new location in the fast growing city of Alcobendas in Madrid (Spain). We spent the previous three years in Madrid Downtown &amp;ndash; our old office served us well, and we made great memories there, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more excited about our new modern space.
The new office is actually in Alcobendas business park, putting us in a really nice place for growing and looking toward the Madrid&amp;rsquo;s Skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39; for Call Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers It&amp;rsquo;s not Fashion, it&amp;rsquo;s a question of Evolution. Companies and brands that are not yet concidering a progresive transition of their phone channel to Real-Time Communications (RTC) within the next years for their customer care, sales or support will quickly become old fashioned and irrelevant for new consumers. The next customers generation is no longer accepting to downgrade their daily high speed interactions and expectations on advanced devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video calls are not an annoying feature for younger generations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Children feel more confortable having video calls than phone calls. If you have the opportunity to check how children understand Live Communications, you will quickly realise that phone is absolutly not a priority for them. They will never ask you about using a phone number and never want to remember just what it is. This new generation is born under a full digital world&amp;rsquo;s devices with high speed Internet and they absolutly are not aware about using limited or poor interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Escalating</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videortc-escalating/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2019 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videortc-escalating/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons Lastest 4.0 developments of RTC technology gives now companies the possibility to offer their customers a wide variety of channels and tools to contact them. Voice, Chat, Messaging, Video, Documents and Shared Screen, Instant Photos&amp;hellip; but, how can all these services improve your customer&amp;rsquo;s experience with your business?
Escalating Communications: Text, Voice &amp;amp; Video. In many websites it is already possible to access advanced services in real time, such as chat or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-4-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-4-generation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Whatever your business, Real-Time Communications can improve your services. The fourth generation of our flagship RTC product is now released after months of developments and continuous improvements. Discover how to integrate live-video, voice, and messaging technology to transform your business processes, and how Video RTC it can help you facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers or employees.
Welcome to Video RTC 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.0.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.0.0:
## [4.0.0] - 2019-03-12 ### Added - Added Escalating usecase - Added Tester usecase - Added Remote Viewer usecase ### Changed - Web developments have been created with a modern tech stack using Webpack, Vue and Bulma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.0.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.0.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Conversational IVR, is the Next Big Thing in Telephony and Internet of Things to connect better your customers with your business. Forget the technology, building the next generation of IVR self-services is more a question of business process to understand how your voice self-service has to manage the conversation. We are please to share this interesting video from Google about DialogFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-2-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-2-generation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Interactive Voice Response refounded to becomes Conversational IVR. The second generation of our IVR product is now released after months of developments and continuous improvements. Discover how to integrate telephony and voicebots / conversational agents to transform your business processes, and how VoiceXML IVR can help you to facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers, users or employees.
Welcome to VoiceXML IVR 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU for Chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs. We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand in just few minutes: what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 4.0: Ready for Debian 9</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-upgrade-debian9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/video-rtc-upgrade-debian9/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Here’s how to go from Debian 8 to Debian 9 If you running a Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) since 2017 or 2018, then your operating system is on Debian 8. To move up to the next update or version 4.0 you will have to upgrade to Linux OS Debian 9 (Stretch) x86 64-bit.
Our next binary packages or CPaaS instances will now includes an installer script to automatically take you to Debian 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.0:
## [2.0] - 2019-02-29 ### New - First release of Smart IVR 2.0 - New PBX-SIP Connect - New TTS-HTTP/MRCP - New ASR-HTTP/MRCP  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 4.0 Nightly!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-4-nightly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-4-nightly/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons The future of Video RTC is coming soon! The fourth generation of our flagship RTC is the result of a engineering teamwork and great user experience. Video RTC 4.0 will provides more features, better performance with an upgrade of the best embedded WebRTC technology. We are currently enjoying tests of all new functions to generate our ultimate 4.0 packgage!
What about all new Widgets 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR · Speech Recognition</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-speech-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-speech-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Convert spoken voice into machine-readable format. Overview VoiceXML IVR runs most existing Cloud Speech API and some MRCP v2 engines. These STT / ASR connectors allow to get a complete development abstraction of all your interactive phone services. In combination with Text-to-Speech, you can develop the most advanced interactive voice experience with the best platform management.
Providers  Nuance Speech Recognizer Google Speech API Amazon Lex Microsoft Azure  Use Cases  Call Stearing, Call Routing, Voice Search&amp;hellip; Support most languanges with several voices Power advanced IVR applications Power Voicebots and Voice Assistants   System Requirements Speech Recognition feature requires VoiceXML IVR On Premise or Cloud CPaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoiceXML IVR · Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-text-to-speech/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr-text-to-speech/</guid>
      <description>Convert text into spoken voice outpout. Overview VoiceXML IVR runs most existing Text-to-Speech engines with many languages and voices powered by a cloud HTTP-API connector. This TTS connector is really fast &amp;amp; dynamic to improve the caller experience. Now, you can develop smart services with a dynamic voice response according to any kind of content: text, numbers, dates,…
Providers  Nuance Vocalizer Google Text-to-Speech API Amazon Polly Microsoft Azure  Use Cases  Enable to generate dynamic voice prompts Support most languanges with several voices Power advanced conversational applications Generate dates, numbers, names&amp;hellip;   System Requirements Text-to-Speech feature requires VoiceXML IVR On Premise or Cloud CPaaS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming Video RTC 4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-rtc-upcoming-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-rtc-upcoming-4/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Innovate. Rebuild your customer interactions&amp;hellip; Follow our socials and blog; be ready to discover our major release update about Video Real-Time Communications. We will pleased to show you soon our 4th generation of our Video Gateway platforms.
Keep posted on February 2019!
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Upcoming VoiceXML IVR 2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-ivr-upcoming-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Feb 2019 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/2019-02-ivr-upcoming-2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Sometimes, you have to reborn and change all&amp;hellip; Follow our socials and blog; be ready to discover our major release update since the born of Interactive Powers. Forget programming standards, IVR will become smart and conversational.
Keep posted on February 2019!
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Unified Plan SDP format released in Chrome 72&#43; </title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/chrome72-sdp-phase3-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/chrome72-sdp-phase3-update/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Chrome goes into Unified Plan SDP (Phase 3) for its WebRTC implementation Google is planning to change the WebRTC implementation from the current SDP format called &amp;ldquo;Plan B&amp;rdquo; to a standards format &amp;ldquo;Unified Plan&amp;rdquo; over 4 phases.
Chrome M72 version will be the first release to apply phase 3, and will require to upgrade sonn our Video RTC platform to run properly all this new SDP format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us at our Spanish Website!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Interactive Powers in Spanish: Interacciones Digitales Interactive Powers is pleased to announce the release of our new spanish website called &amp;ldquo;Interacciones Digitales&amp;rdquo;, designed with a fresh new look and user-friendly responsive navigation, updated with the latest information about our products. We hope you will enjoy our new site in spanish. Our goal with new website is to provide our spanish speaker visitors and customers an easier way to learn about our solutions and cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.5.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.5.1 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.5.1:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Gateway: RTMP &amp; WebRTC comparison</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-vs-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-vs-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers What are the main differences between RTMP and WebRTC gateway models? Currently, Video RTC is our flagship product line for any RTC project&amp;rsquo;s deployments. We have prepared this summary to clarify what are the main features and how to move forward for your business.
Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. RTMP is an open protocol for Adobe Flash Player that allows to connect flash compliant browsers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on &amp;ldquo;Communication Platform as a Service&amp;rdquo; or CPaaS at last year 2018 VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
CPaaS is the new cloud&amp;rsquo;s Game Changer The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge moves to Chromium in 2019</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/microsoft-edge-chromium-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/microsoft-edge-chromium-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration Microsoft annonces officialy that Edge will become a Chromium-based browser in early 2019! Microsoft is reworking its Edge browser on Windows 10 so that it will based on the Chromium open source project. Microsoft CVP Joe Belfiore made a big announcement and explained that it was all about creating “better web compatibility for our customers and less fragmentation of the web for all web developers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and Christmas season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners, employees, providers, friends and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Chat vs Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/web-chat-vs-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the difference about these two chat modalities, and considerations to have during a text typed business communication? Most existing Contact Centers have added a Chat Channel to connect their agents with online connected users without the help of a phone. Today, It’s really important to understand properly what is the best way to use any Chat modality in order to avoid an integration nightmare in the future or less integration reworks for your business processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What about your Chat channel automation, extension and integration?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/chat-channel-automation-extension-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Existing business chat features have to be properly automated, connected and extended to provide a right value for any business application. It’s not just only a question of adding another channel, chat is a really poor conversation modality for humans. Of course, it provide very interesting advantages, because of its simplicity, quick adoption and low bandwidth requirements but it steel being a limited communication feature in a continuous evolution of online customers or consumers requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines Smart IVR and Video RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Services: IaaS, PaaS, SaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the differences between IaaS, SaaS, and PaaS, the three main Cloud Computing models? IaaS, PaaS, SaaS are three Cloud computing models popular in the market. Depending upon the requirement a company can opt for any of the three models. Here we explain IaaS, PaaS, SaaS model in the best possible way so that anyone can understand and differential among them.
What is IaaS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2018!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2018, 11th Anniversary Freak Conferences, on November 14th &amp;amp; 15th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about CPaaS for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “Communications Platform as a Service”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation.
We would like to thank our partners, USA-VOIP and Avanzada7, and all the people who were involved in organizing the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mozilla Firefox 63&#43; fix for SDP format</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/firefox63-spd-format-fix/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/firefox63-spd-format-fix/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Mozilla Foundation Avoiding the Datachannel breaking in Firefox 63+ Nowadays, it is common for web browsers to make updates and changes to their implementations. This is even more common when we talk about modern technologies like WebRTC. A new web browser update that confirms this theory is the last change on Firefox 63 when negotiating the Datachannel.
If you are negotiating a Datachannel with a Firefox version lower than 63, the Session Description Protocol (SDP) will looks something like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.3.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.3.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.1:
## [3.3.1] - 2018-11-13 ### Added - If the Videoplayer only finds one record, it&#39;s preselected ### Fixed - Resized calling message for mobile devices - Fixed SDP negotiations from Firefox 63+  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videobots are coming…</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>Video AI agents with an human like behaviour are closer than you may think… Today, Xinhua, China’s state-run press agency, has unveiled new “AI anchors” — digital composites created from footage of human hosts that read the news using synthesised voices.
The news anchor, based on the latest AI technology, has a male image with a voice, facial expressions and actions of a real person. &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rdquo; learns from live broadcasting videos by himself and can read texts as naturally as a human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us at VoIP2Day to talk about Communications Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Communications Platform as a Service at next VoIP2DAY2018 11th Freak Conferences edition:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
 Keynote: Communications Platform as a Service Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 14th, 2018 Time: 12:30pm  Synopsis The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is a Communications Platform as a Service Company</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The future of communications is driven by the cloud. Interactive Powers was created to help companies embed voice and video communication into the software applications and web applications that are part of their workflow and how they do business with the same communication options and convenience that mobile devices provide for their customers and employees in their person lives. With Interactive Powers, communication becomes more immediate and contextual resulting in better business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, Exevi!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended itSMF VISION18, Conferences, on October 25th, at LA NAVE del Ayuntamiento de Madrid. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Voicebots for OTRS in the presentation entitled “OTRS and Voicebots: First Steps for the IA Automation of the Service Desk”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in Voicebots exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoIP2Day 2018: 11th Freak Conferences</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2018/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 11th edition of VOIP2DAY, the major event about Voice over IP of the year in Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at VoIP2DAY 2018: November 14th &amp;amp; 15th at Wanda Metropolitano Stadium, Madrid. We will share latest industry news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all companies and visitors of the main sector of Telephony and Comunications in Europe and Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Cost of Ownership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/total-cost-of-ownership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/total-cost-of-ownership/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons. TCO is particularly important when you’re deploying Video RTC solutions, and it allows companies to gain substantial cost advantages in implementation, training, maintenance, and system management. Most analysts agree that on-premises will cost you less up front. You pay a one-time license fee, along with a maintenance subscription covering things like vendor support. These are far cheaper than the cost of your cloud subscription over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Premise vs Cloud</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons. There is many reasons to consider replacing an on-premises infrastructure with a cloud-based video real-time communication platform as a service. If your communication infrastructure don’t supports modern video communications or faces end-of-life, you need to plan your migration strategy now to avoid pitfalls down the road. Also consider the seasonality of your business and the best time to be upgraded. For reference, on-premises solutions typically require more time to procure, generally weeks or months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Add easily CoBrowsing to your Customer Interactions and better connect in real-time your agents and remote support teams. CoBrowsing, can help you transform the way you interact with your customers in real-time. CoBrowsing is a Video RTC extension that allows to add advanced powers both to your agents and users getting better and faster online interactions. Improve your customer care or any support interactions, time spend during phone calls or your support performance and confidence?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VISION18: 13th edition itSMF National Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itsmf-vision18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itsmf-vision18/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 13th edition of the &amp;ldquo;Congreso Nacional VISION18&amp;rdquo;, the major IT &amp;amp; Digital Transformation event from itSMF Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at Vision18 congress October 25th at Centro de Innovación LA NAVE del Ayuntamiento de Madrid - Calle Cifuentes, 5, 28021 Madrid. We will share latest technologies news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all startups, companies and visitors.
We are really pleased to be at itSMF - VISION18 with our partner Exevi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Oct 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Cobrowsing enables agents to assist users when they are browsing on your web page. Overview CoBrowsing allows you to share your browser in real-time with another remote peer. Most business processes can take benefit of using CoBrowsing feature. For instance, it is a very powerful tool to improve online shopping, telesales, remote work or support services.
CoBrowsing functionality makes it easy to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of a web browsing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Hosting: Turnkey Solutions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Turnkey Solutions are designed to provide a quick startup without any IT requirement for your business. Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Broadcast · Auto Dialer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-auto-dialer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-auto-dialer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Calling all your business contacts at once. Auto Dialer is multi-channel dialing platform to send important alerts, promotions, updates, payment collection, political campaigns, phone surveys or notifications to your customers, employees, voters, and more. it instantly turns your browser into a complete outbound call center with an Intuitive user interface, advanced multi-campaign management and reporting. It can be easily connected to our VoiceXML IVR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.3.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.0:
## [3.3.0] - 2018-09-14 ### Added - Added Log rotation utility ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.js library (v2.5.0) - Updated Videocall usecase (UX improvement) - Updated the webrtc-gateway internal core  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.5.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.5.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.5.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Call Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-call-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-call-center/</guid>
      <description>Manage your own Call Center extension for Video RTC without any more technical requirements than just a Web Browser and Internet Access. Sometimes, changing all things doesn’t mean to build something totally new to improve the way you manage your Business Communications. Call Center is a Video RTC extension or standalone Omminchannel Call Center solution that allows to add advanced powers both to your agents and customers getting better and faster interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Videocall</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Peer-to-Peer Communication has never been so easy to build into a Website, Mobile App or Kiosks. Videocall provides a simpler way for companies to build their own video calling service via web or mobile application. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows, functions and it is easy to manage. Agents, users or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How WebRTC improves your Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/how-webrtc-can-improves-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Now, It&amp;rsquo;s time to upgrade your customer services with modern real-time communication channels. A large number of businesses can benefit from offering WebRTC services to get a better Customer Experience (CX) with their sales, support or any kind of interactions. And both customers and companies can obtain plenty of advantages by using Real-time Communications. Here, we present five of the most visible ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Web Panel</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-gateway-web-panel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-gateway-web-panel/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Jon Flobrant on Unsplash. Manage all logs and adjust easily main settings of your Video RTC Gateway. At Interactive Powers, we have spent many months making all our solutions better than ever, and one of our products at the very heart of our customers is our Video RTC Gateway. We have made significant improvements on visualizing all information in the Console. We’d love any and all feedback you have on this new monitoring experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logging with Log Rotation</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-log-rotation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-log-rotation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Improve your Video RTC debugging tasks and platform monitoring for all your applications Logging takes place in the execution of your Video RTC applications to provide an audit trail that can be used to understand the activity of the system and to diagnose problems to find and fix bugs. We are pleased to talk a bout a very useful tool for managing log files called Log Rotation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Sharing or Co-Browsing?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Discover Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing advantages, the secure new ‘no download’ complementary interactions improving phone calls for onboarding, sales and support. Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing (or Collaborative Browsing) are a relatively new technologies for Call Centers propelled by a Cloud evolution. However, customer experience professionals seem to think that CoBrowsing and Screen Sharing are one and the same when in reality, they’re not. So what is the difference between these two features and how does adapting your VideoRTC solution improve the overall customer experience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.4.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.4.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers and GDPR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-gdpr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-gdpr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers At Interactive Powers we have always taken care of your data with the seriousness it deserves and having the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) becoming effective on May 25th 2018, we have revised our internal operations, security, and legal documents to ensure we are compliant with this new set of rules.
Policy Updates  Terms of Service: were updated to reflect GDPR requirements. Privacy Policy: added data we collect and how we use it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Meeting Point</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-conference-meeting-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-conference-meeting-point/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Unsplash · Interactive Powers. Creative Commons. Make secure business online meetings with a standard OAuth authentication. Communications can be a critical part of your own business and cannot be outsourced to any kind of OTT or public cloud service. Meeting Point is a new Video RTC Use Case and solution that allows to create Video Conferences from any modern browser and your own mobile app (on demand).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McKinsey: Banks branch in the Digital Age</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/mckinsey-bank-branch-digital-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/mckinsey-bank-branch-digital-age/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Smart-branch in the digital age will dedicated 70% of services areas to self-services thank to advanced technologies.  Digital technology holds the key to the branch of the future.
 Changing customer behavior and the emergence of new technologies spell not the end of the branch but rather the advent of the “smart branch.” Smart branches use technology to boost sales and improve customer experience significantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration. If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever. Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Mobile SDK</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-mobile-sdk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-mobile-sdk/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Build easily WebRTC-powered video calling into your mobile app with a simple JavaScript library for our Video RTC communication platforms. With our Video RTC · Mobile SDK, you can easily add real-time video calling over a data connection or WiFi from your website or app. Interactive Powers offers high quality video communication and seamless integration into any existing app.
Add Real-Time Communications to your app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Successful Combination for Business: IVR &#43; RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jul 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/successfull-combination-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Improve customer experience (CX), while reducing telecommunication costs and increasing customer satisfaction. Our Vision for your Business Communications. Interactive Powers vision is to streamline your business communications with the help of our two core technologies called IVR (Interactive Voice Response) and RTC (Real-Time Communications). Our platforms embrace open standards like SIP (Session Initialization Protocol), VoiceXML (Voice eXtended Meta Language), RTMP (Real-Time Messaging Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communications) allowing businesses to directly embed audio-only or audio &amp;amp; video conversations and collaboration functionality within their website or mobile customer care apps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Web Dialer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-dialer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-dialer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Unsplash · Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Make calls from any Web Browser and easily connect your Call Center or PBX to improve your business communications. Click-to-call converts your website&amp;rsquo;s users into engaged customers by creating an easy way for your customers to contact your sales and support teams right on your website without using their phone. Today&amp;rsquo;s sales and support teams expect to be able to make calls directly from their modern web browser, and their efficiency improves when they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip; Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a STUN/TURN Server?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay · Interactive Powers Creative Commons. WebRTC communications in real-world connectivity require to handle multi-party calls and interact with STUN and TURN servers. Our Video Gateway (WebRTC) platform offers all customers an advanced video real-time communications solution through all audio/video/data streams are transmitted. Generally, a Video Gateway has to be deployed over a public Internet so any user must connect and send media fragments over RTP (Real-time Transport Protocol) ports without specific network issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Communications applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/real-time-communications-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 20:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/real-time-communications-applications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Real-time Communications applications to streamline your online business. Video RTC platforms are changing the way real-time communications are developed and delivered. It is fast becoming the platform of choice for rapidly building enterprise class real-time voice and video applications. Our communications platform is 100% cloud ready, offering continuous evolution, scalability and high availability.
 Video chat is a clearer and modern way to communicate for online businesses</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to configure and customise your Webclient</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-webclient-configuration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-webclient-configuration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Pexels Creative Commons Webclient (WebRTC) provides a user-friendly webphone that allows all your customers and users to make phone calls directly from a website to your business IVR or PBX from any desktop native WebRTC compliant web browser (Firefox, Chrome, Opera,…). In this post we will show you how to customize the Webclient using the different configuration options at flavour/theme level.
The design of our webclient is composed by a logo and a main default color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Store · Europe CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new EU Store - Europe CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Europe and others countries.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversational IVR applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Conversational IVR applications to improve your customer experience in phone services. Tradicional IVR systems have been built as limited DTMF and direct IVR dialogs for a long time. Yet it is not a secret that the experience using those solutions has is rather poor. In 70% of those interactions, the end users end up frustrated; at “best” case scenario are rerouted to a human agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Turnkey</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</guid>
      <description>The Turnkey Solutions for your business Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business. Web Dialer.  Make Voice Calls from any modern Web Browser
 Web Dialer allows all your customers and users to make phone calls directly to your PBX, IVR, Call Center from any desktop web browser (Firefox, Chrome, IE, Safari, Opera,…).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes some improvements and a crital &amp;ldquo;hot fix&amp;rdquo; for Firefox 6+ Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.1:
## [3.2.1] - 2018-06-08 ### Fixed - Fixed compatibility of all modules with Firefox 60+ ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CPaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) is a form of cloud computing that is utilized to deliver communication applications like IVR or RTC to users over the internet. But, unlike SaaS which delivers specific apps and programs, Communication Platform as a Service is a bit closer related to IaaS. So, while IaaS is delivering the infrastructure, like servers and management tools, CPaaS is what delivers the entire communication platform for users to build and develop their own applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Software as a Service (SaaS) Software as a Service (SaaS) directly refers to any software that your business is using just about everyday. SaaS is of course a form of cloud computing, which allows for increase flexibility by relying on a third-party vendor to host and maintain the service — in this case, that service is that software. Since the software is hosted by a cloud provider, your business does not need to install and run applications on their own computers, or host their own servers in expensive data centers, yet still gains access to these powerful tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.0:
## [3.2.0] - 2018-05-15 ### Added - Added Remote Viewer usecase as extension - Added WebRTC communication verification functions - Added possibility to transfer a call using the SPLIT usecases - Added a GET parameter to set the CallerID from the URL in the Webclient usecase ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xenialab and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: XCally - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions! Customer Experience and new channels integration is a key factor for any company inside the digital world. Thank to Open Channel and Interactive Powers you can connect better and improve your interaction processes with customers and prospects. Xenialab and Interactive Powers are pleased to announce the integration between the Xenialab&amp;rsquo;s XCally (Open Channel) system and Video RTC technologies from Interactive Powers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to insert a Webphone into an iFrame</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webclient-website-iframe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webclient-website-iframe/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In a previous post we explained how to include a Webphone button to launch our Webclient (Webphone) in a popup window. In this case, we want to include the Webclient directly in a website as an iFrame and not in an external page.
Including an iFrame element First of all, you need to include an iFrame HTML5 element in your website like this:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Remote Viewer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-remote-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-remote-viewer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock · Interactive Powers. Dramatically improves Customer Experience (CX) extending phone calls with Live Chat, Dual File Sharing, Dual Screen Sharing… Sometime, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to change all things to build something new and really better to improve your existing Business Communications. Remote Viewer is a new Video RTC Use Case and solution that allows to add advanced powers both to your call center agents and phone callers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Web Browser Standard for an universal Password-free sign-in</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A new web standard makes it possible to sign into virtually any web service without needing a password! This Authentication standard from W3C will use your fingerprint reader or inside camera in a wide variety of web browsers. That, in turn, lets you access virtually any online service in a PC or mobile device through password-free FIDO Authentication, not just specific services. You can continue to use familiar biometrics methods like fingerprint readers, cameras and USB keys, and it can serve both in place of and in addition to passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Google Speech API New Google Cloud Speech API Text-to-Speech for Developers has been released! Google is launching a new AI voice synthesizer as part of its suite of machine learning cloud tools. This new Cloud Speech API behind Google Assistant works really fast and use amazing voices to run your own advanced IVR or RTC services. For now, it’s only available in Beta version for Developers and already includes more than 30+ voices but this first cloud service aproach will probably grow quickly thanks to the AI WaveNet technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling with WebRTC on Android</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-android/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Make direct voice and video calls from Android devices thanks to VideoRTC.js and its native WebRTC based tecnology In previous posts, we have looked at some key considerations for building apps for video calling on web browsers and mobile devices, and some of the features you can include to make sure your users have a great experience.
Now any modern Android works with all compliant Smartphone, TV and Tablet devices which is an important component for creating frictionless, delightful apps, especially voice &amp;amp; video calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of CPaaS for Video Real-Time Communications in Businesses</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:46:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers In the next 12 months, up to 49% of Business Cases that will run video services are using a Communication Platform-as-a-Service (CPaaS). Telemedicine and Insurance Professionals. Trends are showing that a leading industry in incorporating video is telehealth with 47% of respondents embedded video into a telehealth application. Video offers numerous advantages to this sector. It allows patients to receive attention at convenience from the comfort of their homes and it helps health institutions to significantly reduce costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Video RTC to your existing Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Whatever your contact center is, we can make it interoperable with videocalls and advanced online interactions. Many companies fear that the integration of video in their contact centers will involve a large investment of human and economic resources. Because companies think they will be forced to change the entire contact center solution, they may ignore video integration and, therefore, the opportunity to significantly improve their services and customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling with WebRTC on iOS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-ios/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Make direct voice calls from Apple iOS devices thanks to VideoRTC.js and its native WebRTC based tecnology In previous posts, we have looked at some key considerations for building apps for video calling on web browsers and mobile devices, and some of the features you can include to make sure your users have a great experience.
Now iOS 11 works with all compliant Apple iPhone and iPad devices which is an important component for creating frictionless, delightful apps, especially voice calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.1.0:
## [3.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added the possibility of configuring different SPLIT scenarios at Flavour level - Added `autoRecording` option in the SPLIT Agent usecase - Added texts option in the SPLIT usecase - Added FileSharing in the Webclient usecase - Added ScreenSharing in the Webclient usecase - Added possibility to show a message until the Video agent is accepted - Added `split_id_strategy` in the VideoGateway - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five Steps to quickly make your own Videocalling application with VideoRTC.js (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/five-steps-build-mobile-application/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Users have asked us about our post on how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
In this new release we offer you a more detailed explanation of the steps to take, so that you can successfully build your mobile video application.
Introduction. From the moment you established a VideoRTC interaction, by connecting with the video gateway, until the call is finished, library’s range of events are executed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers and Customer Experience in 2018</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 20:23:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Companies must recognize CX as a key competitive differentiator and make sweeping changes in Channels to keep up this year. In the last years, digital technologies have changed the way we work and relate to each other. These changes have also impacted on customers’ expectations. Clients increasingly demand a more personalized, accessible and comfortable attention.
Daily Business Communications. Clients expect from companies the possibility of contacting them through the same variety of channels they use in their everyday life communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 59% of consumers want Real-Time personal offers designed especially for them Direct Communications. Integration of Real-Time voice and video helps to establish easy and seamless communications between customers and sellers. Sales increase if clients can solve their questions immediately, when they access the catalogue of products and services. By just clicking on a button, customers can ask about a product, a contract or the delivery time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.3.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3.0:
## [1.3.0] - 2018-01-08 ### Added - Favicon in Split Use Case (Webclient and Agent) ### Changed - The default look for the agent webphone is now &#39;agent&#39; - Removed extra HTML code that was in the index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
 Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>101 Reasons Why You Need To Embrace Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/101-reasons-to-embrace-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/101-reasons-to-embrace-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: WebBuilder Live chat is the way to go! You are undoubtedly aware of the importance of customer service on your online business’ road to success. But, what you may not know is that customers’ expectations have now reached new heights, demanding instant support and fast acting. In order to keep up with the latest trends, it is essential to improve customer experience. If you cannot think of an innovative way to do so – we have the answer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. By 2030, AI solutions will surpass the services provided by agents. Just a few years ago, talking about Artificial Intelligence (AI) meant talking about a futuristic scenario. Today, AI is everywhere and, directly or indirectly, we are starting to use it almost every day. The rapid evolution of AI allows it to be increasingly applied to more sophisticated processes which require a high precision like customer services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and happy holiday season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 13:30:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Learning at convenience. The current pace of life and work prevents us from continuing our learning. Thanks to digital tools and Real-Times Communications improving knowledge is not out of reach anymore. E-learning increases accessibility and reach as e-learning courses are more affordable and fits with students’ timetables.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Cloud API for Voice over IP at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate. We are experiencing an Internet revolution that begins to affect basic services that we now operate with specific devices or business systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to detect if your Browser is WebRTC compliant?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/browser-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 10:18:15 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/browser-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons WebRTC is currently supported by Mozilla Firefox, Google Chrome and Opera, in both desktop and Android versions. Microsoft Internet Explorer and Edge and Apple Safari still have to add support for WebRTC. Currently, support in these browsers is provided by third-party plug-ins, which are not an ideal solution.
Here, we provide you with an easy javascript code to check if your browser is supported by WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2017 12:45:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, 70% of mobile workers will use a tablet or a hybrid device that has tablet-like characteristics Expert Cooperation. The technician can contact remotely experts in real time. This option allows them to have the support they need to finish the job in the first visit.
Field to Office Connection. Real-Time Communications enable field workers to immediately share data, photos or videos with the teams in the office, all without leaving the work site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is it Possible to Enhance In-store Experiences?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/kiosk-custexp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2017 12:08:43 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/kiosk-custexp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Kazuhisa OTSUBO. Creative Commons WebRTC is a transformative technology. It means a shift in the way we think about communications. WebRTC makes it possible a real-time engagement by integrating voice, video, data, messaging and more. Applications of WebRTC are endless and they can play a major role in the way businesses operate.
The in-store customer experience In-store experiences are not always perceived by clients as satisfactory ones.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 70% of people use their own smartphone to learn and 52% prefer to learn at the point of need Video-based learning. Video use is increasing and video features are critical in e-learning. Video allows students to access lectures, but also share content with their peers and professors, as well as tutoring in live real time interactions.
Mobile Learning. Mobile devices are growing in popularity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video ID · Facial Recognition Plugins</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:28:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pexels. Creative Commons Facial recognition is a biometric method of identifying an individual by comparing live capture or digital image data with the stored record for that person. Facial recognition systems are commonly used for security purposes but they are increasingly applied in a wide variety of fields, like in mobile technology, online to shopping, even in medicine.
In a previous post we talked about secure identification API integrations and some of their uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 11:06:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 59% of consumers want real-time personal offers designed especially for them Legal Services. RTC technologies enable to provide your clients an alternative solution to traditional legal services. You can offer an immediate answer, interact through the most appropriate channel and share documents, including pictures or videos.
Marketing and Design. You can offer exciting interactions, where your customers have the opportunity to see real examples in interactive experiences and contract services after trying your products.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79% of Consumers Want the Opportunity to Contact Businesses Online</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:03:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In a recent Enghouse Interactive survey, customers have made it clear that they want online communication channels with companies. 79% of consumers believe that businesses should provide a way for customers to contact them online.
It is also interesting to compare this figure with the responses to the very same question in previous years&amp;rsquo; surveys. In 2014, only 29% of respondents answered that the possibility to contact a company online was relevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 08:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service Keep the human touch. It is not only that customers can still chose to interact in person, but thanks to VideoRTC, they have now more options to communicate face-to-face. If clients need help while using self-service, they can contact an agent. Clients can also videochat with their bank advisors through a tablet or a mobile phone from the comfort of their homes, but living an experience similar to an in-person branch visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2017 12:45:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, 70% of mobile workers will use a tablet or a hybrid device that has tablet-like characteristics Faster Resolution Times. RTC technology enables peer interactions and collaborative experiences. It allows the field worker to count on immediate assistance from the office workers or experts to help solve technical problems in the work site. Combined with the wide variety of features available, which make it possible to send documents, photos or videos in real time, resolution times are accelerated.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Steps on Escalating Real-Time Communications: Text, Voice and Video</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/escalating-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 11:35:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/escalating-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Current developments of RTC technology gives companies the possibility to offer their customers a wide variety of channels and tools to contact them. Voice, Chat, Messaging, Video, Documents and Shared Screen, Instant Photos&amp;hellip; but, how can all these services and tools be integrated?
Escalating Real-Time Communications to improve Customer Engagement. In many websites it is already possible to access advanced services in real time, such as chat or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2017 09:45:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons 41% of consumers state that a great customer experience, including convenience, is decisive in their loyalty to a brand Immediate assistance. One of the most valued elements for customers is having assistance when they need it. Real-time communications allow to significantly improve customer service, by offering an instant assistance. Clients no longer need to travel to the store, as they can interact with an agent in person, immediately and through different channels.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Web Browsers for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-desktop-web-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-desktop-web-browser/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway, is ready to run with most modern Web Browsers and Desktop Operating Systems. We can observe the success of WebRTC Technology through the evolution of web browsers. Increasingly more and more browsers are WebRTC-enabled, having incorporated the possibility of making video calls. In most of them users do not need even to install special applications or plugins. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what four of the most important web browsers on the market currently offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week More data for a better service. Data provided by customers about their needs, preferences and individual tastes enable e-commerce businesses to create clients’ profiles and take into account their purchase history to better serve them. Clients should easily have the opportunity to give feedback, so their problems can be solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine at School</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/pediatrics-telemedicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:10:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/pediatrics-telemedicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons One of the leading sectors among advanced solutions is Real-Time Communications technology. Communication through voice, video or messaging in real time is opening up endless applications for many businesses, including telemedicine. Until now, telehealth has focused on hospitals and adults, but new opportunities start being considered.
Don&amp;rsquo;t skip classes anymore. When children need to see a doctor, not only do they miss school, but parents have to leave work for appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Integration in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:09:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons The Video Channel is the next level Customer Experience frontier for existing Contact Centers Video is not a separate solution from the services that contact centers have been providing until now and it is not a substitute for voice calls. The key to the Video in Real-time communications lies in the possibility of offering a new channel, whose use is progressively increasing in customer care services for most industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 10:48:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 80% of banks are planning to offer a video banking service Expert Advice. Video and voice over the internet make it possible to meet current customers’ expectations. More and more clients look for information on line and VideoRTC offers the opportunity to remotely discuss products and receive information from an expert.
ATMs. This technology allows to combine the advantages of self-service, such as rapidity and efficiency, with face-to-face customer service if needed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Real-Time Communications Endpoints</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/videortc-endpoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 18:01:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/videortc-endpoints/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Real-Time communication technology represents a qualitative leap in any communication process. One of the most outstanding advantages is VideoRTC. But what platforms can we use to benefit from this innovative technology? Web browsers, mobile devices and interactive kiosks are the main endpoints from which to interact in real time.
Web Browsers. Browsers are still the most important terminals from which to access the Internet when it comes to everyday work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Field Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 12:44:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-field/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Collaboration tools improve team efficiency by 20% One of the keys of technical assistance success is effectiveness. Voice and video over the internet in real time provide tools to field professionals that make a noticeable difference in results. Real-time video, voice and messaging applications enable mobile workforces to get immediate additional support by sharing photos, data or videos with other experts. By improving communication, resolution times are speeded up and, therefore, costs are reduced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2017!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:12:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2017, 10th Anniversary Conferences, on November 16th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “The Cloud API revolution is coming.”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in voice integration APIs exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Kiosks: RTC Technology to Boost your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/businesses-kiosk-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 09:14:56 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/businesses-kiosk-2/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Mk2010. Creative Commons Video calls are being very well received by users. Minutes dedicated to video calls grow on social networks and more and more companies include this feature. It&amp;rsquo;s just a matter of time before the video becomes a predominant tool in customer services. The video allows to establish communications in a more natural way, with the human touch of the in-person visits and making communications clearer and more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Nov 2017 13:45:09 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons 41% of consumers state that a great customer experience, including convenience, is decisive in their loyalty to a brand Live chat assistance. Advanced communications must take into account what is the most appropriate solution. Live chat is the ideal channel when customers need support for basic questions. It is easy and a time-saver.
See the product. Thanks to video and file sharing, you can show your products to your clients, through photos or videoconference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2017 11:06:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-professional/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 35% of consumers say the smartphone will become their main purchasing tool In today&amp;rsquo;s market, it is crucial that businesses engage customers the way they communicate. Users are increasingly turning to the Internet for their personal communications, but also to make regular purchases or contract services. As online purchases increase, the success of a modern business depends on the ability to promote its products and services through the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Omnichannel experience. Omnichanneling opens the opportunity for call centers to take a significant step in improving customer services and surpassing clients’ growing expectations. It is one of the key for businesses to implement an integral strategy. Clients perceive the advantages as they can engage when needed and through the most convenient channel: chat, phone call, self-service or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Public Cloud API Services</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-api-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-api-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers The public cloud computing market is raising earnings for Internet&amp;rsquo;s giants Google, Amazon, Microsoft&amp;hellip; One of the major trend that is working behind the scenes and driving many of the most successful businesses these past few years is: Cloud Application Programming Interfaces (API). APIs are a technology that allow firms to interact and share information with other firms at an unprecedented scale, taking advantage of the far-reaching progress in digitization and the rising influence of software in our day-to-day lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP at next VoIP2DAY2017 10th Anniversary Conferences:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
 Keynote: The Cloud API Revolution is coming to VoIP Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 16th, 2017 Time: 10:00am  Synopsis Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Sharing reloaded for Firefox</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/screensharing-firefox/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 11:46:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/screensharing-firefox/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Screen Sharing: now, without installing any plugin for all Firefox Web Browsers! Screen Sharing is a very powerful feature that allows users to share in a screen or a window of any documents or application including images, videos, forms… among other capabilities. However, in order to build screen sharing capabilities, first, it is necessary to build screen capture. Until now, it was only supported in one browser, Chrome, which gives access to screen capture by writing an extension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Retail · Industries</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 13:44:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-retail/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons In 2016, two main channels for generating sales were ‘Stores’ at 79% and &amp;lsquo;Website&amp;rsquo; at 73% Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet offers the opportunity to find innovative to ways to respond to consumers’ expectations. This technology provides numerous channels that allow to adapt companies’ assistance to clients’ needs. By integrating features such as live chat, videoconferencing, phone calls or file sharing, you can remarkably improve customer experience and differentiate your store in a highly competitive market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Services Revolution</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/cloud-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/cloud-apis/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Recent promotion of Cloud API services by the dominant Internet service providers can lead to a substantial change in the use of legacy systems and technologies. Cloud-based services, which enable high-value-added interactions with voice, natural language, artificial intelligence, etc., will make it possible to leave existing solutions behind.
More Efficient and Cost-Saving. Google, Amazon, Apple and Microsoft are starting to provide amazing cloud-based services to enterprises, which were just available to developers until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoIP2Day 2017: 10th Conferences Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 10th edition of VOIP2DAY, the major event about Voice over IP of the year in Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at VoIP2DAY 2017: November 15th &amp;amp; 16th at Wanda Metropolitano Stadium, Madrid. We will share latest industry news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all companies and visitors of the main sector of Telephony and Comunications in Europe and Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-beneficts/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Improved Workflows and Processes. Patients can contact their doctor directly via mobile phone or tablet. In this way, it is their usual doctor who decides if the patient needs to go to the medical center to receive care. In cases of urgent care, their doctor guides the patient through teleconference until the arrival of a health team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week Pre-sales support. Video options make it possible to show products to customers. They can check its appearance and functionality, making more informed purchase decisions.
Personalized shopping. Video and voice over the Internet allow you to pay the same special, individual attention to online customers as in face-to-face interactions in a more efficient way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky Halloween night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Which Businesses could benefit more from Interactive Kiosks?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/businesses-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Oct 2017 12:07:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/businesses-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Metropolitan Transportation Authority, NY. Creative Commons Interactive Kiosks are changing consumer experience thanks to WebRTC technology. They allow immediate connections between advisers and customers, sharing documents and paying for products or services, among other different applications. Let’s see which businesses can remarkably improve their customer services through Interactive Kiosks:
Retail Stores. Interactive Kiosks can critically enhance efficiency and customer retention in retail stores. They allow clients to talk to a salesperson immediately in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-learning · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-elearning/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels In 2016, the worldwide revenue for self-paced elearning was $ 46,674.67 Real-Time Video and Voice over the Internet open opportunities for everyone who wants to learn something. Online learning is gaining popularity as more and more students demand more flexibility that new technologies can provide. E-learning broadens the options of programs and degrees, since students can access to educational institutions all over the world. Self-paced learning allows students to arrange a learning schedule that meets their individual needs, at a lower price and without leaving the comfort of their homes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How it Works our Datachannel with VideoRTC.js</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/datachannel-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post, we will show you how it works with Datachannel using VideoRTC.js and how to code quickly a simple service for a specific purpose.
Introduction First of all you need to know the modules in which we currently have available the Datachannel: These are the Videocall and the SPLIT. In this example we will use the first one, though the operation would be the same in both.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 38% of in person visits to their physician could have been replaced with Telemedicine Physician E-visits. The main advantage of telehealth for patients is convenience. They can save time as it is not necessary for sick patients to travel to his doctor’s office.
Wellness Services. VideoRTC provides the opportunity to attend healthy lifestyle programs from the comfort of home.
Health Monitoring. Patients who need treatment after surgery or due to chronic diseases can be monitored remotely in real time by health professionals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time for companies to use Web and Mobile RTC Applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:58:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone bills with voice call minutes have been reduced or even disappeared both at home and in businesses. We communicate at work writing emails, tweets, posts, notifying by Skype, Google Hangout, LinkedIn or Facebook, and get in touch with our friends via Whatsapp or Snapchat, sharing multimedia content in real time. Phone calls are no longer a relevant channel in our personal communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Things you have to know about WebRTC on Apple Safari 11</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-3-things-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-3-things-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration After years, Apple has officially released a new version of Safari with support for WebRTC!
These are the three essential things to know:
Interoperability with other web browsers. Basics work fine. If you run a simple peer-to-peer call between any of the 4 browsers, you’ll get a call going. Voice and video work over the lowest common denominator Opus+H.264 in Safari. Although Opus+VP8 will be also a possibility in the future, it is not right now with the current release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Add a Webphone Button in your Website</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webphonebutton-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:30:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/webphonebutton-website/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to add a Webphone button in your website using our customizable webcall widget.
Step one: Installation To install the Webphone Button in your web­page you need to download our webcall widget webcall_widget_noflash.zip and uncompress it in the directory of your website.
To insert it, you first need to add the CSS Stylesheet file to your webpage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial Services · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 11:00:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-financial/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons 90% of bankers expect video banking to positively impact customer satisfaction Video-based service helps financial businesses to improve customer experience but it also broadens business opportunities. They make it possible to combine digital technology with the human element as well. Video and voice Real-Time Communications over the Internet offer more convenient ways for clients to contact their banks, while in person interactions are still an option.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key Benefits of Interactive Kiosks</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers WebRTC technology has disrupted traditional communications, but we have barely experienced its potential yet. One of the most relevant applications is going to take place at points of sale. Thanks to the latest breakthroughs in video technology, customer experience can be dramatically enhanced. Let’s see the main benefits of an Interactive Kiosk:
Immediate Real-Time Communications. Kiosks enable a personalized and immediate communication between an expert or a salesperson and a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC 3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-3-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 11:06:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-3-generation/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Whatever your business is, you may require Real-Time Communications to improve your services. The third generation of our flagship RTC product is now released after months and years of continuous improvements. Discover how to integrate live-video, voice, and messaging technology to transform your business processes, and how Video RTC it can help you facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers or employees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Real-Time Communications the Phone won&#39;t be the King anymore</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 10:45:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article5/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone dominated customer attention services of companies over any other channel, since its popularization during the first half of the twentieth century. The invention of the mobile phone did not particularly harm its leadership, as far as at first it was simply mobile phone handsets. Today, the mobile phone is a widespread device that has supplanted the use of fixed terminals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.0.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.0.0:
## [3.0.0] - 2017-10-03 ### Added - Added a new usecase: Videocall - Added return button inside the usecases - Added list of platform extensions in the landing page ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build your Own Videoconference Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Oct 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videoconference/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Today we bring you this interesting article on How to build your own videoconference service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step one: Setting up the basic structure As we have explained in previous posts, first of all it is important that you include dependency within your project or web page.
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.0.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.0.0 · 2.0.0:
# Change Log All notable changes to this project will be documented in this file. ## [1.0.0] - 2017-02-10 ### First release ## [1.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added VoiceProcessor feature in the Videoroom module - Added `disconnect()` method for destroy a session with the VideoGateway - Added `closeUsecase()` method for close a use case with the VideoGateway (All usecases) - Added download link of VideoRTC Screensharing extension for Chrome - Added `videoRate` and `screenRate` parameters in the `call()` method (Split Client) - Added timestamp in Videomail messages to achieve multiple records with the same id/name ### Changed - Updated `webrtc-adapter` version release to `3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Healthcare · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-healthcare/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telehealth Market will reach $1,9 billion by 2018 Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are changing the relations among patients and physicians. On the one hand, telemedicine is an emergent industry which makes it possible to expand services offered by health institutions, while it helps to solve some of the current economic problems faced by hospitals. On the other hand, within minutes, patients will have the opportunity to receive medical care from anywhere and they will avoid spending time in the doctor&amp;rsquo;s waiting room.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC on Safari11 for MacOS and iOS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration At past WWDC 2017 in San Jose, California, Apple announced that it will include support for WebRTC in Safari 11 and WebKit for all iOS 11 and MacOS Sierra devices. Until now, 80% of all browsers supported WebRTC including Firefox and Chrome. Regarding Safari it grows to 95%. Apple’s announcement gives companies that use WebRTC applications and tools, such as our VideoRTC solutions, a broader range for choice and flexibility over which browser their rich multimedia communications services are delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Transformation: Doors of Opportunity for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:02:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All interactions cannot be managed by bots, since users, when facing with certain problems, need to contact a real agent. If consumer is not allowed to communicate with a person, it leads to frustration and the relation client-company is seriously damaged. At this point, video offers contact centers the possibility of developing a very differential customer experience management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest VoiceXML IVR features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of main features (VoiceXML):
 Dashboard VoiceXML editor Applications SIP Connectivity Speech Connectors CDR Reporting Settings Logs  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Kiosk?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:05:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Mattes. Creative Commons An interactive kiosk is a computer terminal that is placed in a public setting. The aim of a kiosk is to provide information to customers and users. They have an integrated touch screen, usually with a user-friendly interface to facilitate interactions. Thanks to computing technology it is possible to offer a wide range of functions and applications, from brand information, to product catalogues or real-time interactions with sales consultants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on Safari 11 for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway, Now ready run with Apple Safari 11 over MacOS computers and iOS devices Interactive Powers is proud to announce Video RTC support for Safari 11 over MacOS and iOS. It was a demand from all the market for a long time, know it becomes a reality past week. Safari 11 works fine on the basis of WebRTC to allow Apple users community to connect most features but with some specific web browser limitations that we will comment shortly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is Transforming Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:04:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Companies must understand that the processes of digital transformation driven by society are inevitable. In the last years, the improvement of customer support services accelerates the pace of adaptation to digital processes. The reason is the good results obtained by companies that have already integrated advanced digital tools, based, for instance, on WebRTC technology for real-time communication via the web or mobile applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Communications: The Security Factor</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-factor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 12:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-factor/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay, Creative Commons Communications Security is more important ever than ever to handle properly any business. Security tops the list on concerns about RTC. Considering the risks of new exposed system vulnerabilities and the increasing scope and scale of breaches, security is more important than ever. In fact, uncertainty about which device provides privacy and security has become a hindrance to purchasing an IoT device. But despite the increasing concerns among consumers, researches show that security is still one of the major challenges that companies need to deal with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (RTMP)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 15:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (RTMP) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (RTMP):
 SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Playground (Flash Configurator) Click-to-call (Webclient) Documentation  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons to embrace Cloud Hosting</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:50:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. Upgrade your business communications to the Cloud to deliver more value with less costs Computing based on the internet is booming business. The global cloud communication market is projected to reach $4.45 by 2021. Why are more and more companies turning to the cloud for their business communications needs?
Communications solutions at a lower cost. Cloud computing is a cost saver since it can reduce or even eliminate the need for a company to buy an expensive hardware and software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses need to Face Digital Challenges</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
The spread of new communication behaviour among users is pushing companies to modify their contact channels with customers. At Interactive Powers we observe that adapting to an increasingly digitized market poses new challenges. However, it also opens one door of opportunity for companies to improve and differentiate themselves.
From our offices in Spain and the United States, we provide solutions that facilitate secure and real-time multimedia interactions over the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does VideoRTC fit in my Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:36:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Call Centers have to upgrade their services to the next level implementing new advanced interactions The ever-growing digital world can give new opportunities for existing contact centers to provide a superior customer experience. Nowadays new technologies drive clients to ask for multiple options when looking for support. It is here where VideoRTC can help your contact center to enhance its services.
Save time providing the right channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Revolution in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:00:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All of us, as consumers, are becoming increasingly familiar with the use of new channels. We must also take into account that the first generation of digital natives is entering into the market. However, phone continues to be the most widely used channel in customer service and voice over IP technology. This situation is specially extended in the Spanish business landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (WebRTC):
 Videoroom (multi-conference) Private room (ID/password) SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Click-to-call (Webclient) Videomail (post a video message) Videoplayer (play single and dual video records) Meeting Point (OAuth Authentication Meetings)  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Mobile Video Application (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 10:45:24 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-mobile-app/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build a video call service in your mobile by using the Ionic Framework 2 and VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you need to install an Ionic project in your system. If you don’t have it, you can download and follow the official guide from the Ionic Framework 2 web site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technavio: IVR market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The Interactive Voice Response (IVR) market is growing, but what’s driving that growth? Market research analysts from Technavio suggest that the IVR, or Interactive Voice Response market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021. For those who are new to the industry, IVR systems are the solutions that give companies a stronger way of engaging their customers through various customer service solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Complementary Functions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-complementary-functions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Sep 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-complementary-functions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes complementary features that you can run according to your business requirements . All of this, is part of capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
SIP Connect. Video Gateway ensures interoperability between WebRTC endpoints and existing telephony systems. It integrates seamlessly advanced web phones or mobile apps into previous infraestructure. Learn more.
Meeting Point. Video Gateway provides an additional OAuth plugin that makes it easier for users to connect to your real-time services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Pop-up Agent</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-pop-up-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-pop-up-agent/</guid>
      <description>Extend Existing Call Centers with advanced Video RTC Capabilities. Overview Pop-up Agent is a specific peer component designed to add Video RTC services to an existing Call Center. It can operate over full WebRTC options or RTMP with limited functions. Pop-up Agent works with standard web browser or with an MS Windows executable application.
Pop-up Agent functionality is easily configurable with a set of buttons and toolkit. Main options are Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · API Framework</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</guid>
      <description>Provide Core Functions to easily develop any Video RTC application for Web and Mobile. Overview API Framework feature helps to make your job easier, adapting services to your needs and personalizing them. Our platform provides developers with a wide range of possible solutions, through a flexible and powerful toolkit for building Web APIs.
API Framework feature enables developers to design new APIs or edit existing ones. You can also customize all the way down, just using basic regular features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Build a Videocall Service (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 11:59:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/coding/videortc-build-videocall/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In this post we will show you how to build your videocall service based on HTML5 technology by using our API Framework with VideoRTC.js.
Step 1: Setting up the basic structure Firstly, you will need to include dependency within your project or web page:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  You can insert a minimized version if you prefer so:
&amp;lt;script type=&amp;quot;text/javascript&amp;quot; src=&amp;quot;videortc.min.js&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;  Next, we connect with the video gateway server:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video ID</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 09:52:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-id/</guid>
      <description>Protect your Real-Time Communications with Secure Identification API integrations. Overview Video ID feature helps you to improve security in your real-time communication services. Our solutions include partner options for ID Verification through an external provider certified API. This capability enables to comply with identity verification processes required, for instance, by banks, insurances, e-commerces or telemedicine.
Video ID functionality captures and validates users’ information, whilst conducting a real-time check. Video ID capability is a set of API, which can optionally include Facial Recognition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Industries</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-industries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 11:00:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-industries/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Whatever your business, product, or service is you can require real-time communications technologies. Discover how organizations like yours are integrating live-video, voice, and messaging technology to transform their industries, and how Video RTC can help you facilitate more engaging interactions with your customers or employees.
Call Centers. Contact Centers continue to evolve rapidly as consumers expect a highly personalized and engaging experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner: 20 percent of Global Businesses will deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest Global Businesses will implement Video Chat. Time is the new currency for your customers who are looking for painless and informed solutions to their issues. We are also starting, growing and running companies in an &amp;ldquo;attention economy,&amp;rdquo; which is defined by the view that human attention is a scarce commodity. By 2018, according to research from Gartner, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video Recording</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Easily record secure Live Video Calls for later playback. Overview Video Recording capability enables to record your video calls in real-time. Files are securely stored and you can immediately access to content following your demands. Call records are directly pushed to your own secure file system storage or any web service, such as Amazon S3, Windows Azure, Google accounts… Enjoy playback with high-quality WebM recordings.
Video Recording functionality includes converter tools to automatically live-convert video streams to MP4 for easy access with no post-processing required on your end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forrester: Voice Channel as Self-service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons 63 percent of US adult callers report to use the voice channel for self-service (IVR) According to a 2016 Forrester Research study, 83 percent of U.S. adult Internet users had a phone conversation with a customer service representative in the past year. Sixty-three percent of them also reported using the voice channel for self-service, such as Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems whose Conversational AI capabilities enable callers to converse with a virtual agent as if there were a human rep on the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · SIP Connect</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-sip-connect/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-sip-connect/</guid>
      <description>Connect WebRTC or RTMP to traditional SIP telephony systems or devices. Overview SIP Connect feature is designed to make traditional calls across web or mobile phones. It enables interoperability between WebRTC endpoints and existing telephony systems, like your current PBX or phone lines. For instance, a Call Center can send and receive SIP-based calls, using SPLIT function as well.
SIP Connect functionality allows you to send Dual-tone multi-frequency signalling (DTMF) or in-band telecommunication signalling system using the voice-frequency band over SIP.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economist: Visual Recognition with &#39;Deep Learning&#39; is suparsing Humans for First Time</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Visual Recognition Algorithms reach an accuracy of 96% with &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning&amp;rdquo; The rehabilitation of “AI”, and the current excitement about the field, can be traced back to 2012 and an online contest called the ImageNet Challenge. ImageNet is an online database of millions of images, all labelled by hand. For any given word, such as “balloon” or “strawberry”, ImageNet contains several hundred images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Meeting Point</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-meeting-point/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-meeting-point/</guid>
      <description>Make secure business online meetings with a standard OAuth authentication. Overview Meeting Point feature is an additional OAuth plugin to make easier user authentication for Internet services without retrieving passwords. It includes many tested methods for different social networks like Google, Linkedin or Twitter. However, you can create your own OAuth interface too.
Meeting Point functionality allows to easily connect users to your real-time services without having to add third-party components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Data: Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons Nearly one-third of Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat to improve Customer Engagement According to a research from Dimension Data, nearly one-third of contact centers expect to deploy video chat for customer engagement. The research says that giving customers the additional option to remotely connect face-to-face, at moments that are important to them (and on their terms), can make their customer experience even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Over Printing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-over-printing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-over-printing/</guid>
      <description>Create Multi-tenant Video Services over WebRTC for your Contact Center. Overview Over Printing feature allows to print a logo inside the remote frame. Instead of specific customisation you can use it to distribute video calls to several services with their own service logo. It’s very useful for a Call Center with many services operated with different profiles.
Over Printing functionality is easy to configure inside our multi-flavor settings without specific coding.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Snapshot</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-snapshot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-snapshot/</guid>
      <description>Take or get pictures dynamically during your remote video conversations. Overview Snapshot feature allows you to take easily a picture within the video. This functionality helps to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. For instance, you can get Jpeg pictures from agents or users frames during a process, retrieving them later or share them to an external application interface.
Snapshot makes it possible to save a picture from the middle of a video, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Voice Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-voice-calling/</guid>
      <description>Make advanced Voice Call or Web Phone applications for Real-Time Communications. Overview Voice Calling functionality ensures that no one misses out on the full application experience. It helps to provide an effective customer care, offering the option to hear voices in real-time. Voice Calling keeps interactions as easy, simply and fast as possible.
Voice Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Video Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-video-calling/</guid>
      <description>Create amazing Real-Time Communications with Dual-band Voice and Video capabilities Overview Video Calling functionality provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage. Agents or customers can communicate instantly over video without downloading software or installing plugins. It also enables multi-party calls for team collaboration.
Video Calling application makes it easy to create real-time communications (RTC) for your business applications and processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Sharing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Secure screen share your desktop or any application in Real-Time Communications. Overview Screen Sharing application allows you to share live screen over the web or mobile instantly. Most business processes can take benefit of using Screen Sharing feature. For instance, it is a very powerful tool to improve online meetings, presentations, remote work or support services.
Screen Sharing functionality makes it easy to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · File Sharing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Send and Receive Files or Documents in Real-Time Communications. Overview File Sharing application helps you to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. It allows you to instantly transfer any file establishing a peer connection all within the context of your website or application. With the file sharing feature you can send and receive unlimited files just dragging them in the chat window.
File Sharing functionality makes it possible to share and receive documents during your voice or video call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Core Features</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes core features that you can activate according to your own business requirements . All of this, is part of the main capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
Video Calling. Video Gateway provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Live Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Manage Smart Text Message interactions in Real-Time Communications. Overview Live Chat supplement your video and voice communication with advanced text chat capabilities using the WebRTC datachannel. Live Chat feature allows to send and receive text messages simultaneously, without any lag at a single click. It is the perfect tool to use for the customer and an agent conversation. Live chat integrates seamlessly into your application, eliminating the need for clunky third-party APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://webclient.ivrpowers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s E-commerce become a Better Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Latest Video Real-Time Communications can be decisive to improve e-commerce services. First of all, because they are becoming very accessible and easy to use through web browsers or most of mobile devices. Plugin downloads are no longer required, you just click and your are connected. Secondly, remember that creating a live interaction with your customers like a live chat or video call channels is a proven way to increase your sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) Roadmap 2017!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons We are pleased to unveil some key elements of our Video RTC (WebRTC) evolution until 2017. Major changes will follow WebRTC’s evolution itself. Our primary goal is to provide improved features to all Special Extensions like SPLIT, Video Calling, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot&amp;hellip; In the next quarter, we will make significant improvements like adding a better Customer Experience with Video Real-Time Communications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC built-in Security Features</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:04:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons In essence, any software in the Internet is an inherent risk that your PC may become infected by a virus, malware, spyware or various other ‘bugs’ that threaten the security of your data. As such, the principal solution to combat viruses is to install firewalls and anti-malware software that work to defend your computer against any potential threats.
With WebRTC however, there’s no need to worry about any of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2.0:
## [2.2.0] - 2017-07-27 ### Added - Added interval Watchdog - Added autocall GET parameter to the Webclient URL usecase - Added overprint logo in the Webclient usecase  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: Time-Saver, Better Access and More Services</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2017 10:26:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-time-saver/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interl Free Press. Creative Commons There is no greater need for a personalized customer experience than in healthcare. But, at the same time, busy patients demand new ways to communicate with their doctors to save time. Thanks to technology RTC innovations, telehealth can make healthcare easier for patients.
Why should healthcare industry take advantage and adapt to technology trends? Time-saver Telemedicine allows to save time spent traveling to doctor’s office and waiting for the appointment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser to SIP Calling?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration How can you call a Desk Phone from any Web Browser? Our both Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) can convert web browser media streams (video - audio - data) to SIP from WebRTC or RTMP peers communications. This interesting feature allows to connect easily web services to existing VoIP telephony channels of your IVR or PBX. We can consider all of this approach like a direct calling webphone or like a WebRTC-DDI or RTMP-DDI in a SIP trunk from an operator service configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>70 percent of all Doctor’s Office Visits are Unnecessary</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2017 10:00:53 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/70-percent-doctor-office-visits-are-unnecessary/</guid>
      <description>According to a recent study by PricewaterhouseCoopers, one in four people indicate that it takes more than 30 days to get an appointment with their physician. Many of these cases result in an unnecessary visit to the emergency room. Overall, the total cost of unnecessary emergency room visits is just under $14 billion annually. One of the most common reasons for these unnecessary visits include patient convenience, symptoms that occur after hours or on the weekend, or the patient was unable to get a timely appointment with their physician.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video gets more Honest Buyers than other Channels</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 19:11:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons According to a W. Frank Barton School of Business at Wichita State University new research, sending a text message, making a phone call or have a face-to-face conversation leads people to lie often than video conferencing. The study found that buyers were:
 95% more likely to report deception via text messages than if they had interacted via video 31% more likely to report deception when compared to face-to-face communication in person 18% more likely if the interaction was via audio chat or phone call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VideoRTC.js for Developers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:30:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers elaboration Since 2015, Interactive Powers has been diligently refining its Video RTC solutions, API Framework and SDKs to make embedded video much more accessible for developers and enterprises who are looking to rapidly integrate reliable video chat into their own applications.
VideoRTC.js library Today, we’re thrilled to officially announce a new VideoRTC.js library – the launch of our self-service API Framework developer tools, which lets developers quickly and easily embed this same enterprise-grade, cloud-hosted, multiparty RTC video collaboration into any web, mobile or native application on virtually any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins. WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR.
Give us a shout out! https://twitter.com/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Banking Revolution is coming</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:02:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-banking/</guid>
      <description>We are increasingly moving on line. And bank customers are not an exception. Financial businesses need to adapt their services to the new life styles and trends. One of the options is live video chat.
Video banking allows to deliver the best possible experience to online customers. Thanks to live video chat technology financial services can offer to their customers face to face experiences without leaving the comfort of their houses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v1.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 1.3 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>