<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>event on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in event on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Salesland Webinar Event</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Salesland. What if in COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s times, we could sell more? Join us at next 25th November, 16:00 CET at next Salesland 20 years event!
With:
Javier Arellano, Sales Manager and Businesss Development at Salesland Group. Ivan Sixto, Founder and CEO at Interactive Powers. The pandemic crisis caused by Covid-19 has created an acceleration in the digitalization processes of our society, but what about people? Why do we have to do without your sales team when you can reinvent their stall by making use of technology?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers at next eMerge Americas 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us next days 30th - 31h March at eMerge Americas event at Miami Beach, Florida For the first time, Interactive Powers (ivrpowers.com) will be attending eMerge Americas, March 30 – 31, 2019 in Miami Beach - Convention Center. eMerge Americas is the premier technology event connecting the Americas. eMerge Americas is not just an event- it’s an ecosystem that is transforming Miami into the Tech Hub of the Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, Exevi!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended itSMF VISION18, Conferences, on October 25th, at LA NAVE del Ayuntamiento de Madrid. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Voicebots for OTRS in the presentation entitled “OTRS and Voicebots: First Steps for the IA Automation of the Service Desk”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in Voicebots exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
