<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>video on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/video/</link>
    <description>Recent content in video on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/video/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons to use Background Effects for Video Contact Center services</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-reasons-to-use-background-effects-for-video-contact-center-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-reasons-to-use-background-effects-for-video-contact-center-services/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Improving Video Calling performance and Customer Experience with professional Background Effects: Solid, Picture or Blur In recent years, video contact center services have become increasingly popular as more and more businesses realize the benefits of being able to connect with customers face-to-face, even if they&amp;rsquo;re not in the same physical location. With the pandemic accelerating the shift to remote work, the use of video calls has become a critical part of providing customer support, sales, and other services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Key Benefits of Building a Conversational IVR with Natural Language in VoiceXML</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-key-benefits-of-building-a-conversational-ivr-with-natural-language-in-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-key-benefits-of-building-a-conversational-ivr-with-natural-language-in-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers In recent years, there has been a growing trend towards the use of conversational IVR systems with natural language interaction. This type of IVR system allows users to interact with the system in a more natural and conversational way, which can improve the overall user experience and increase customer satisfaction. When it comes to building a conversational IVR system, VoiceXML is a popular technology that offers a number of advantages over other technologies like Voice API or legacy IVR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of Video Call Recording for online customer support</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/the-importance-of-video-call-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/the-importance-of-video-call-recording/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Why getting video recordings is key for a successful video contact center? Benefits, Implementation Considerations, and Recommendations Currently, many companies are looking for implementing a video contact center as a way to improve the customer experience. However, not all of these companies are fully taking advantage of the potential of this tool. One of the most important features to consider when implementing a video contact center is the ability to record customer interactions on video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Background Effects</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-background-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-background-effects/</guid>
      <description>Live streaming complementary software packed with powerful features to enhance Video RTC. Simply add Manycam Lite CC as a webcam/video source for our Video RTC platforms and get access many interesting features to enhance your video call center: add IP cameras to show different angles, virtual backgrounds and chroma key, up to 24 video sources, switch between computer screens, screencast, draw &amp;amp; text board mode.
Manycam Lite CC is able to manage CPU or GPU optimization in local processing to ensure the best performance for your video agents and without any other dependence on the your desktop PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Resolution</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screen-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screen-resolution/</guid>
      <description>Deploying High Quality and fully Bandwidth adaptative Video Communications Services Resolution is the number of pixels on a specific screen. A single pixel, the smallest unit to measure the video resolutions, is a tiny dot on the screen often no visible individually to the naken human eye. The more the number of pixels, the higher the sharpness of the video streaming.
Resolution Settings Video RTC gateways manage the following resolution modes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salesland Webinar Event</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 00:18:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/salesland-webinar/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Salesland. What if in COVID-19&amp;rsquo;s times, we could sell more? Join us at next 25th November, 16:00 CET at next Salesland 20 years event!
With:
Javier Arellano, Sales Manager and Businesss Development at Salesland Group. Ivan Sixto, Founder and CEO at Interactive Powers. The pandemic crisis caused by Covid-19 has created an acceleration in the digitalization processes of our society, but what about people? Why do we have to do without your sales team when you can reinvent their stall by making use of technology?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
