<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Technologies on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/technologies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Technologies on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:49:56 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/categories/technologies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, live Video Chat is an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some benefits of Video Chat:
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s Time to add Video to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/its-time-to-switchon-video-cctr/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/its-time-to-switchon-video-cctr/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a real-time interaction with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service or information they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: A Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is #WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>