<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>technologies on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/technologies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in technologies on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/technologies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionize your Customer Experience (CX) introducing a Video Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/revolutionize-your-customer-experience-with-video-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/revolutionize-your-customer-experience-with-video-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Connect, Reinvent, Empower&amp;hellip; your Business In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, customers expect to have a variety of communication options when interacting with businesses. Video is becoming an increasingly popular choice, and companies are finding that adding a video channel to their contact center is not just &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; but a necessity. That&amp;rsquo;s why a Video Contact Center or VCC is the solution you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for.
By adding video channels to your contact center, you can provide face-to-face interaction for your agents and improve your business with a more human customer care experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Background Effects</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-background-effects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-background-effects/</guid>
      <description>Live streaming complementary software packed with powerful features to enhance Video RTC. Simply add Manycam Lite CC as a webcam/video source for our Video RTC platforms and get access many interesting features to enhance your video call center: add IP cameras to show different angles, virtual backgrounds and chroma key, up to 24 video sources, switch between computer screens, screencast, draw &amp;amp; text board mode.
Manycam Lite CC is able to manage CPU or GPU optimization in local processing to ensure the best performance for your video agents and without any other dependence on the your desktop PC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is PBX?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-pbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-pbx/</guid>
      <description>A Private Branch Exchange (PBX) is a telephone system within an enterprise that switches calls between users on local lines, while enabling all users to share a certain number of external phone lines. In contrast to a public switched telephone network (PSTN), the main purpose of a PBX is to save the cost of requiring a line for each user to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.
Used as a business telephone system or private telephone network, a PBX is owned and operated by the enterprise rather than the telephone company &amp;ndash; the telephone company of which may be considered a supplier or service provider, however.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is ACD?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</guid>
      <description>An automated call distribution system, commonly known as Automatic Call Distributor (ACD), is a telecommunication system that answers incoming phone calls or video calls to distributes them within an organization. ACDs often provide some form of Automatic Customer/Caller Identification (ACIS), such as Direct Inward Dialing (DID), Dialed Number Identification Service (DNIS), Automatic Number Identification (ANI), or Video SPLIT ID (VSID) for use in routing calls based on a series of user-configured rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Resolution</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screen-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screen-resolution/</guid>
      <description>Deploying High Quality and fully Bandwidth adaptative Video Communications Services Resolution is the number of pixels on a specific screen. A single pixel, the smallest unit to measure the video resolutions, is a tiny dot on the screen often no visible individually to the naken human eye. The more the number of pixels, the higher the sharpness of the video streaming.
Resolution Settings Video RTC gateways manage the following resolution modes:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Widgets</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</guid>
      <description>Deploy full web responsive widgets with a single script or URL in your website or apps. Today we are excited to announce that we are open sourcing a new Widget for Video RTC to handle incoming or outgoing video calls and prompt users for input, record calls, connect callers to agents, and more.
Main features:
FAB Button enabled Flip Camera (new) Mute Camera Mute Audio Live Chat File Sharing Dual / Single Screen Sharing Snapshot (optional) Overprint Logo More options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Image in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</guid>
      <description>Allows you o display an image as your background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls replacing your background by a nice picture removes all your surroundings so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can change your background, or add a background image during your video call sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Blur in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</guid>
      <description>Allows you to blur the background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls blurring your background makes your surroundings appear out of focus so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can blur your background during your meeting, event, or training session.
Unretouched Screenshots:
Need to add it right now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · PIN Access</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/pin-access/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Aug 2020 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/pin-access/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Connect easily any real-time session from any device or browser with a PIN code. If you wish to utilize Video RTC / Solutions as part of your support efforts, a custom PIN access, where your customers can enter a unique pin code to connect with an agent is another way to start co-browsing, screen sharing or voice &amp;amp; video calling. You only have to redirects your customers to a landing page like our new one: https://pwrs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a Video Channel to your existing Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Transform your existing call center into a more engaging, customizable, and interactive solution with video calls. In today’s competitive market, companies need call center software to connect in real-time cross web browsers and mobile devices. Adding advanced video interactions such web call, video call, live chat, file sharing, co-browsing, screen sharing… give your clients and agents the option to communicate better than ever with your brand.
The Empowered Omnichannel: What any Contact Center in the Digital Age should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer-to-Peer?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</guid>
      <description>Make and Receive Video Calls between Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to manage and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) between two peers. This connection is based on a WebRTC communication session running voice, video and data.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.
How does Peer-to-Peer work? Peer-to-Peer (WebRTC) enables to connect many Web Browsers or Mobile Devices with Real-Time Communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Web Browsers support in 2020!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-web-browser-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-web-browser-2020/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration Video RTC Gateways are now ready to run most modern Web Browsers and Operating Systems for your Business. We can observe the success of WebRTC Technology through the evolution of web browsers. Increasingly more and more browsers are WebRTC-enabled, having incorporated the possibility of making video calls. In most of them users do not need even to install special applications or plugins. Let’s see what four of the most important web browsers on the market currently offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC-to-SIP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</guid>
      <description>Receive Audio Calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to control all media streams (video - audio - data) on any communication between users and a SIP softswitch or PBX/ACD. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice and data.
Connect a Web Widget for any existing Call Centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Reverse?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Make Video calls from your Contact Center to Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Outbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Microsoft Edge support for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-microsoft-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-microsoft-edge/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway is now ready to run with Edge Browser over Windows computers and devices. At Interactive Powers, we are really excited that Video RTC platforms and API Framework / Mobile SDK are now supporting Microsoft’s new Chromium based Edge Browser aka Edgium. From now, your real-time applications will work on Microsoft’s latest Edge browser released without any changes or updates in your existing code / services already deployed!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Forward?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</guid>
      <description>Receive Video calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TTS-API connectors updated!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/tts-api-connectors-updated/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45+ Languages &amp;amp; 300+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon, Google and Microsoft Cloud TTS-API Integration. Natural Language over the Phone&amp;hellip; All of you know about cognitive services is growing these days, and that&amp;rsquo;s why today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about our new TTS-API for &amp;ldquo;Text to speech&amp;rdquo;. This connector converts text into a dynamic natural voice in just a few milliseconds. There are a lot of Cloud Speech API, but we will focus on the Cloud Services main giants: Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Polly TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/amazon-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 27 Languages &amp;amp; 60+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon Polly Integration About Amazon&amp;hellip; Amazon Polly is a Text-to-Speech (TTS) service that uses advanced deep learning technologies to synthesize speech that sounds like a human voice. It&amp;rsquo;s part of the voice of Alexa and can do much more for your business too.
Amazon has arround 60 voices across 30 languages and variants. Amazon Polly offers Neural Text-to-Speech (NTTS) voices through Machine Learning approach.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 30+ Languages &amp;amp; 180+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Google TTS Integration About Google&amp;hellip; Google Cloud is one of the major Enterprise Cloud Services in the world, so its API does not fall short. There are a lot of features that are worth of mention, but we don’t have that time so, here are some of main features we consider:
Google has over 180 voices across 30+ languages and variants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft TTS connector</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45 Languages &amp;amp; 75+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Microsoft Azure TTS Integration About Microsoft&amp;hellip; Microsoft Azure like Google Cloud provides his own Text To Speech API. It is quite big and here are some of its main features with more than 75 voices over 45 languages.
Parameters for speed, pitch, volume, pronunciation, and additional pauses Custom voice models for developers and enterprises Neural Voices technology To get more information, you can read Microsoft TTS documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Gateway: RTMP &amp; WebRTC comparison</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-vs-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-vs-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers What are the main differences between RTMP and WebRTC gateway models? Currently, Video RTC is our flagship product line for any RTC project&amp;rsquo;s deployments. We have prepared this summary to clarify what are the main features and how to move forward for your business.
Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. RTMP is an open protocol for Adobe Flash Player that allows to connect flash compliant browsers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Services: IaaS, PaaS, SaaS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the differences between IaaS, SaaS, and PaaS, the three main Cloud Computing models? IaaS, PaaS, SaaS are three Cloud computing models popular in the market. Depending upon the requirement a company can opt for any of the three models. Here we explain IaaS, PaaS, SaaS model in the best possible way so that anyone can understand and differential among them.
What is IaaS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Sharing or Co-Browsing?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Discover Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing advantages, the secure new ‘no download’ complementary interactions improving phone calls for onboarding, sales and support. Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing (or Collaborative Browsing) are a relatively new technologies for Call Centers propelled by a Cloud evolution. However, customer experience professionals seem to think that CoBrowsing and Screen Sharing are one and the same when in reality, they’re not. So what is the difference between these two features and how does adapting your VideoRTC solution improve the overall customer experience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a STUN/TURN Server?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jul 2018 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-stun-turn-server/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay · Interactive Powers Creative Commons. WebRTC communications in real-world connectivity require to handle multi-party calls and interact with STUN and TURN servers. Our Video Gateway (WebRTC) platform offers all customers an advanced video real-time communications solution through all audio/video/data streams are transmitted. Generally, a Video Gateway has to be deployed over a public Internet so any user must connect and send media fragments over RTP (Real-time Transport Protocol) ports without specific network issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CPaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) is a form of cloud computing that is utilized to deliver communication applications like IVR or RTC to users over the internet. But, unlike SaaS which delivers specific apps and programs, Communication Platform as a Service is a bit closer related to IaaS. So, while IaaS is delivering the infrastructure, like servers and management tools, CPaaS is what delivers the entire communication platform for users to build and develop their own applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SaaS?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Software as a Service (SaaS) Software as a Service (SaaS) directly refers to any software that your business is using just about everyday. SaaS is of course a form of cloud computing, which allows for increase flexibility by relying on a third-party vendor to host and maintain the service — in this case, that service is that software. Since the software is hosted by a cloud provider, your business does not need to install and run applications on their own computers, or host their own servers in expensive data centers, yet still gains access to these powerful tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Web Browser Standard for an universal Password-free sign-in</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/web-standard-password-free/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A new web standard makes it possible to sign into virtually any web service without needing a password! This Authentication standard from W3C will use your fingerprint reader or inside camera in a wide variety of web browsers. That, in turn, lets you access virtually any online service in a PC or mobile device through password-free FIDO Authentication, not just specific services. You can continue to use familiar biometrics methods like fingerprint readers, cameras and USB keys, and it can serve both in place of and in addition to passwords.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Text-to-Speech</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Apr 2018 09:30:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/google-tts/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Google Speech API New Google Cloud Speech API Text-to-Speech for Developers has been released! Google is launching a new AI voice synthesizer as part of its suite of machine learning cloud tools. This new Cloud Speech API behind Google Assistant works really fast and use amazing voices to run your own advanced IVR or RTC services. For now, it’s only available in Beta version for Developers and already includes more than 30+ voices but this first cloud service aproach will probably grow quickly thanks to the AI WaveNet technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling with WebRTC on Android</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-android/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-android/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Make direct voice and video calls from Android devices thanks to VideoRTC.js and its native WebRTC based tecnology In previous posts, we have looked at some key considerations for building apps for video calling on web browsers and mobile devices, and some of the features you can include to make sure your users have a great experience.
Now any modern Android works with all compliant Smartphone, TV and Tablet devices which is an important component for creating frictionless, delightful apps, especially voice &amp;amp; video calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling with WebRTC on iOS</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-ios/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Make direct voice calls from Apple iOS devices thanks to VideoRTC.js and its native WebRTC based tecnology In previous posts, we have looked at some key considerations for building apps for video calling on web browsers and mobile devices, and some of the features you can include to make sure your users have a great experience.
Now iOS 11 works with all compliant Apple iPhone and iPad devices which is an important component for creating frictionless, delightful apps, especially voice calling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video ID · Facial Recognition Plugins</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 09:28:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/facial-recognition/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pexels. Creative Commons Facial recognition is a biometric method of identifying an individual by comparing live capture or digital image data with the stored record for that person. Facial recognition systems are commonly used for security purposes but they are increasingly applied in a wide variety of fields, like in mobile technology, online to shopping, even in medicine.
In a previous post we talked about secure identification API integrations and some of their uses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Web Browsers for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-desktop-web-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2017 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-desktop-web-browser/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway, is ready to run with most modern Web Browsers and Desktop Operating Systems. We can observe the success of WebRTC Technology through the evolution of web browsers. Increasingly more and more browsers are WebRTC-enabled, having incorporated the possibility of making video calls. In most of them users do not need even to install special applications or plugins. Let&amp;rsquo;s see what four of the most important web browsers on the market currently offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Kiosk?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:05:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Mattes. Creative Commons An interactive kiosk is a computer terminal that is placed in a public setting. The aim of a kiosk is to provide information to customers and users. They have an integrated touch screen, usually with a user-friendly interface to facilitate interactions. Thanks to computing technology it is possible to offer a wide range of functions and applications, from brand information, to product catalogues or real-time interactions with sales consultants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working on Safari 11 for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/videortc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration The Video RTC Gateway, Now ready run with Apple Safari 11 over MacOS computers and iOS devices Interactive Powers is proud to announce Video RTC support for Safari 11 over MacOS and iOS. It was a demand from all the market for a long time, know it becomes a reality past week. Safari 11 works fine on the basis of WebRTC to allow Apple users community to connect most features but with some specific web browser limitations that we will comment shortly&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Communications: The Security Factor</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-factor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Sep 2017 12:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-factor/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay, Creative Commons Communications Security is more important ever than ever to handle properly any business. Security tops the list on concerns about RTC. Considering the risks of new exposed system vulnerabilities and the increasing scope and scale of breaches, security is more important than ever. In fact, uncertainty about which device provides privacy and security has become a hindrance to purchasing an IoT device. But despite the increasing concerns among consumers, researches show that security is still one of the major challenges that companies need to deal with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC built-in Security Features</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 10:04:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-security/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons In essence, any software in the Internet is an inherent risk that your PC may become infected by a virus, malware, spyware or various other ‘bugs’ that threaten the security of your data. As such, the principal solution to combat viruses is to install firewalls and anti-malware software that work to defend your computer against any potential threats.
With WebRTC however, there’s no need to worry about any of that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser to SIP Calling?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration How can you call a Desk Phone from any Web Browser? Our both Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) can convert web browser media streams (video - audio - data) to SIP from WebRTC or RTMP peers communications. This interesting feature allows to connect easily web services to existing VoIP telephony channels of your IVR or PBX. We can consider all of this approach like a direct calling webphone or like a WebRTC-DDI or RTMP-DDI in a SIP trunk from an operator service configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins. WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is VoiceXML?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>The Voice eXtensible Markup Language (VoiceXML) is an XML-based markup language for creating distributed voice applications, much as HTML is a markup language for creating distributed visual applications. It is an industry standard defined by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) at http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml21/ (for VoiceXML V2.1) and http://www.w3.org/TR/voicexml20/ (for VoiceXML V2.0). The VoiceXML language enables IVR developers to use a familiar markup style and Web server-side logic to deliver applications for use over telephone lines.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
