<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webrtc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/tags/webrtc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webrtc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:49:56 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/tags/webrtc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Is video chat a good strategy to my business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/video-chat/benefits-videochat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/video-chat/benefits-videochat/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, live video chat is an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some benefits of video chat
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC. A Trending Technology to improve business results</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/webrtc/trending-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/webrtc/trending-technology/</guid>
      <description>Technology is changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology solutions have a great impact on customer experiences. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing business of marketing technology</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/increasing-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/increasing-business/</guid>
      <description>Demands for real-time communications solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information. To best position their companies and to meet necessities of digital customers, marketing departments face a range of challenges, including the extensive use of technologies for managing customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technology/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technology/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins.
WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About WebRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/webrtc/about-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 10:51:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/webrtc/about-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins.
WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>