<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Webrtc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/webrtc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Webrtc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/webrtc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information. To best position their companies and to meet necessities of digital customers, marketing departments face a range of challenges, including the extensive use of technologies for managing customer relationships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>