<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Covid19 on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/covid19/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Covid19 on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/covid19/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>COVID-19 is a Disruptive Event for Telehealth</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telehealth-evolution-in-times-of-covid-19/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels Telemedicine is now a becoming household term both for doctors and patients. If you need to see a doctor any time soon and it&amp;rsquo;s unrelated to COVID-19, chances are that your visit will be a virtual one. Today the people is open to the idea of seeing a doctor virtually instead of an in-person visit, there are a positive momentum and that awareness has increased. When a virus outbreak occurs, diagnosing patients promptly, minimizing travel time, and reducing public exposure helps to curb the rate of infection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times and habits have changed. Health and Safety are first. Simplicity and Speed too.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/virgo-healthcare-annoucement/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels We understand Telehealth has to be simple and fast, allowing doctors and patients to connect easier than ever during these difficult times! Interactive Powers as a leading video gateway developer has released Virgo Healthcare, a new smart videocall application &amp;ldquo;as a service&amp;rdquo; in response to the overwhelming increase virtual visits sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. This accessible and secure solution with hyper customization offers the greater doctor and patient experience for a such critical digital interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telemedicine is changing the face of Healthcare delivery during the Pandemic.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/telemedicine-is-changing-the-face-of-healthcare-delivery/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels The COVID-19 global pandemic has both rocked the economy and tested the limits of already-stretched healthcare systems. The COVID-19 / Coronavirus is quickly spreading its tentacles across the globe. This pandemic has brought out the best in people as new partnerships form to combat a common enemy. While the pandemic tears across the globe, so to do the unprecedented and innovative changes in pharma, manufacturing, and care delivery.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39;, it&#39;s a must have.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Now, It&amp;rsquo;s won’t be an option. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of business survival in post-COVID-19 society. Just one year ago, we had annouced that Video was no longer &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; for Call Centers, now it will change the entire world market.
 Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications
 As you may read in the research analyts reports, Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications according to &amp;ldquo;more optimistics&amp;rdquo; predictions published past year as usual&amp;hellip; Even, if video was much better than voice for any digital real time human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>