<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kiosk on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kiosk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Kiosk on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:22 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kiosk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key Benefits of Interactive Kiosks</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers WebRTC technology has disrupted traditional communications, but we have barely experienced its potential yet. One of the most relevant applications is going to take place at points of sale. Thanks to the latest breakthroughs in video technology, customer experience can be dramatically enhanced. Let’s see the main benefits of an Interactive Kiosk:
Immediate Real-Time Communications. Kiosks enable a personalized and immediate communication between an expert or a salesperson and a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Kiosk?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:05:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Mattes. Creative Commons An interactive kiosk is a computer terminal that is placed in a public setting. The aim of a kiosk is to provide information to customers and users. They have an integrated touch screen, usually with a user-friendly interface to facilitate interactions. Thanks to computing technology it is possible to offer a wide range of functions and applications, from brand information, to product catalogues or real-time interactions with sales consultants.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>