<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>split on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/split/</link>
    <description>Recent content in split on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:00:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/split/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SPLIT 6.x Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</guid>
      <description>The sixth generation Video RTC Gateways, meticulously developed by Interactive Powers, incorporate the innovative SPLIT module. This advanced feature enables the seamless separation of all media streams, including video, audio, and data, providing unprecedented flexibility and control. The SPLIT module represents a significant leap forward in communication technology, allowing for more efficient handling and routing of multimedia content.
This cutting-edge development is currently based on a robust combination of SIP (Session Initiation Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a Video Channel to your existing Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Transform your existing call center into a more engaging, customizable, and interactive solution with video calls. In today’s competitive market, companies need call center software to connect in real-time cross web browsers and mobile devices. Adding advanced video interactions such web call, video call, live chat, file sharing, co-browsing, screen sharing… give your clients and agents the option to communicate better than ever with your brand.
The Empowered Omnichannel: What any Contact Center in the Digital Age should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer-to-Peer?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</guid>
      <description>Make and Receive Video Calls between Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to manage and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) between two peers. This connection is based on a WebRTC communication session running voice, video and data.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.
How does Peer-to-Peer work? Peer-to-Peer (WebRTC) enables to connect many Web Browsers or Mobile Devices with Real-Time Communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC-to-SIP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</guid>
      <description>Receive Audio Calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to control all media streams (video - audio - data) on any communication between users and a SIP softswitch or PBX/ACD. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice and data.
Connect a Web Widget for any existing Call Centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Reverse?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Make Video calls from your Contact Center to Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Outbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Forward?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</guid>
      <description>Receive Video calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
