<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>split on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/split/</link>
    <description>Recent content in split on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/split/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Taking Your WhatsApp Channel to the Next Level</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/taking-your-whatsapp-channel-to-the-next-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/taking-your-whatsapp-channel-to-the-next-level/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Enhancing Customer Engagement with Direct Calls or Video Calls through WhatsApp in your Contact Center. WhatsApp has become an indispensable communication channel in today&amp;rsquo;s digital landscape, bridging the gap between consumers and businesses of all sizes. This transformation is especially notable in European and Latin American markets—with Brazil leading the way—where WhatsApp is deeply woven into daily communications, achieving remarkable user adoption and engagement. Contact centers have recognized this shift and are integrating WhatsApp into their customer engagement frameworks, meeting customers on their preferred platform while providing natural, accessible support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Recovery</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-call-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-call-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik Revolutionizing Customer Experience in Video Communications In today&amp;rsquo;s communication landscape, interruptions and wireless network disconnections are inevitable. These issues can significantly affect the quality of internet and video calls, presenting a serious challenge. They often lead to substantial time waste for both agents and users, frequently resulting in incomplete transactions. This problem is particularly critical in contact centers, where most service providers lack effective recovery mechanisms for phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT AI Copilot?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-ai-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-ai-copilot/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik SPLIT AI Copilot: Delivers real-time, proactive knowledge and actions during user-agent interactions. SPLIT AI Copilot is an AI-driven interface based on SIP and designed to support contact center agents by providing real-time assistance during customer interactions. Part of the Video RTC platform, SPLIT AI Copilot identifies customer intent and offers agents immediate access to relevant knowledge resources, next-step guidance, and real-time suggestions. This enables agents to handle inquiries more effectively without needing to search for information manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Deaf Interpreter?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-deaf-interpreter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-deaf-interpreter/</guid>
      <description>SPLIT Deaf Interpreter: Provides efficient sign language interpretation through real-time video communication to phone calls. SPLIT Deaf Interpreter is an innovative video communication interface designed to bridge the communication gap for deaf users during phone calls. This cutting-edge solution seamlessly connects deaf individuals with skilled sign language interpreters in real-time, enabling smooth and effective communication. By leveraging advanced video technology, SPLIT Deaf Interpreter ensures that deaf users can engage in phone conversations with ease, overcoming traditional barriers and fostering inclusivity in telecommunications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT WhatsApp?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik SPLIT WhatsApp: Enhancing Contact Center Communication with Voice and Video Calls. SPLIT WhatsApp offers a powerful feature that allows users to seamlessly transition from a standard WhatsApp conversation to a full-fledged video call. This functionality provides a smooth and efficient way to escalate communication when needed, enhancing the overall user experience. By enabling this scale-up capability, SPLIT WhatsApp bridges the gap between text-based messaging and face-to-face interaction, all within the familiar WhatsApp environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPLIT 6.x Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</guid>
      <description>The sixth generation Video RTC Gateways, meticulously developed by Interactive Powers, incorporate the innovative SPLIT module. This advanced feature enables the seamless separation of all media streams, including video, audio, and data, providing unprecedented flexibility and control. The SPLIT module represents a significant leap forward in communication technology, allowing for more efficient handling and routing of multimedia content.
This cutting-edge development is currently based on a robust combination of SIP (Session Initiation Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a Video Channel to your existing Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Transform your existing call center into a more engaging, customizable, and interactive solution with video calls. In today’s competitive market, companies need call center software to connect in real-time cross web browsers and mobile devices. Adding advanced video interactions such web call, video call, live chat, file sharing, co-browsing, screen sharing… give your clients and agents the option to communicate better than ever with your brand.
The Empowered Omnichannel: What any Contact Center in the Digital Age should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer-to-Peer?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</guid>
      <description>Make and Receive Video Calls between Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to manage and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) between two peers. This connection is based on a WebRTC communication session running voice, video and data.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.
How does Peer-to-Peer work? Peer-to-Peer (WebRTC) enables to connect many Web Browsers or Mobile Devices with Real-Time Communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC-to-SIP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</guid>
      <description>Receive Audio Calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to control all media streams (video - audio - data) on any communication between users and a SIP softswitch or PBX/ACD. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice and data.
Connect a Web Widget for any existing Call Centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Reverse?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Make Video calls from your Contact Center to Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Outbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Forward?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</guid>
      <description>Receive Video calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
