<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Browser on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/browser/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Browser on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:09:34 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/browser/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>3 WebRTC things you must know about Safari11</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-things-safari/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-things-safari/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration After years, Apple has officially released a new version of Safari with support for WebRTC!
These are the three essential things to know:
Interoperability with other web browsers. Basics work fine. If you run a simple peer-to-peer call between any of the 4 browsers, you’ll get a call going. Voice and video work over the lowest common denominator Opus+H.264 in Safari. Although Opus+VP8 will be also a possibility in the future, it is not right now with the current release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC on Safari11 for MacOS and iOS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration At past WWDC 2017 in San Jose, California, Apple announced that it will include support for WebRTC in Safari 11 and WebKit for all iOS 11 and MacOS Sierra devices. Until now, 80% of all browsers supported WebRTC including Firefox and Chrome. Regarding Safari it grows to 95%. Apple’s announcement gives companies that use WebRTC applications and tools, such as our VideoRTC solutions, a broader range for choice and flexibility over which browser their rich multimedia communications services are delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>