<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Contact Center on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/contact-center/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Contact Center on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/contact-center/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting your Website and Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/connecting-website-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>The old way: What others still doing…  Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons Outdated technologies are weighing companies down by limiting their view of customers and making it difficult to connect with the new digital age interactions over IP.
Click-to-Call &amp;amp; Callback This option requires to get the user phone number in oder to make a call; remember all new digital customers don’t like to give up a cell or landline number anymore.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to introduce New Channels into a Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/how-to-introduce-new-channels-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Last years, we have implemented several New Channels projects based on Video RTC to existing Contact Centers. At times, it was the result of Innovation, but most often it was to enhance the Customer Experience and your services according to a new Market demand. After all, any Contact Center should interact with the customer anywhere they are! Phone, Email, and Chat are making way for emerging channels such as Social media, Video, Text, Mobile apps and IVR self services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the Contact Center with WebRTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 13:30:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/webrtc-for-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The way people access customer service is changing. If existing they want to survive in a highly competitive digital market, Contact Centers must adapt properly their services and make a continuious effort to provide greater customer experiences.
Poor Customer Services Practices Today, Contact Centers cannot always provide the best customer service only over the phone channel. Clients who call in for specific support are usually kept on hold for long periods of time – considering that call centers numbers are not always included in phone price plans – they have to repeat information or if they write an email or if they interact on a web content they never receive an answer in real-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers: Digital Transformation, is not an Option</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 10:34:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-centers-digital-transformation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unplash. Creative Commons We know the way people communicate has changed, and therefore, the way customers want to communicate with organizations is also changing. Technology becomes more important to our day to day living. For instance, the phone is the most used platform but customers expect to engage with companies across multiple channels.
Phone usage is changing According to Dimension Data’s “2016 global contact center benchmarking report”, digital interactions account for over 42% of all interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>