<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>acd on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/acd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in acd on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/acd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Language &amp; Location for Web ACD 1.x</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/language-location-web-acd-1x/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Feb 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/language-location-web-acd-1x/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Breaking Barriers, Bridging Connections: Introducing extended Multilingual Support We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce that we&amp;rsquo;ve enhanced our Web ACD solution to better serve your needs across multiple countries and locations in the Americas! Now, our platform supports a variety of languages, including Spanish, English, and Portuguese, ensuring a seamless experience for users in diverse linguistic regions.
1. Improved Accessibility Navigate our Web ACD solution effortlessly in your preferred language, making communication smoother and more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.15.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.15.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2023 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.15.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.15.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations with a hotfix 1.15.1 included for all deployments as well. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.15.0:
### [1.15.0] - 2023-06-14 ### Added - WebSocket request to obtain a list of all users in the system for admins and supervisors - Parameter maxAttentionTime to a realtime queue - Option to show offline users in the dashboard - Added Copy and QRCode actions for the selected trigger - Sounds when dialpad keys are pressed - Added both user and name fixed vars for applications and queue triggers - Home section to the menu - Latest Calls view - Added new languages (en_CA, en_GB, es_AR, es_CL, es_CO, es_CR, es_EC, es_PA, es_PE, es_PR, pt_BR, pt_PT) to the platform ### Changed - The send-announce WebSocket action takes now a *to* parameter to allow directing the message to specific agents - Allowed the : character as part of the report query - The username can only contain letters, numbers or periods ### Fixed - Correctly limit the report preview of queries with the LIMIT word in them - Moved scroll from &amp;lt;html&amp;gt; to the main container - Dashboard items are now aligned via stretch ### [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.14.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.14.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.14.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.14.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.14.0:
### [1.14.0] - 2023-01-25 ​ ### Added ​ - Added getUserfieldById method to the DB custom module ​ ### Changed ​ - Disabled Google Translate from the platform - Upgraded videortc font to release v1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.13.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.13.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.13.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.13.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.13.0:
### [1.12.0] - 2022-05-12 ​ ### Added ​ - Target selection (iframe/tab) for the queue triggers - Home page customization ​ ### [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Business Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Leading companies have a wholeness approach about how to communicate better with customers across their processes. Communicate is a top priority for businesses today — but how can you quantify its value to your organization? That’s especially important in these times, with businesses managing the economic impact and uncertainty of disruptive events, and how this will impact both their customers and employees going forward. The History of Business Communications is, of course, closely linked with the histories of Communications itself and that of Business Operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Web ACD platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 10.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
Requirement Description Distribution Linux Debian 10 Linux Kernel x86_64 Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure Installer Minimal Install Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in an ACD service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.11.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.11.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.11.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.11.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.11.0:
## [1.5.0] - 2021-01-28 ​ ### Added ​ - Auto close functionality for the Queue triggers to select if they must be closed at call end or not - Administration/Supervision message to the agents - Custom PHP modules to extend platform functionalities ​ ## [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is ACD?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</guid>
      <description>An automated call distribution system, commonly known as Automatic Call Distributor (ACD), is a telecommunication system that answers incoming phone calls or video calls to distributes them within an organization. ACDs often provide some form of Automatic Customer/Caller Identification (ACIS), such as Direct Inward Dialing (DID), Dialed Number Identification Service (DNIS), Automatic Number Identification (ANI), or Video SPLIT ID (VSID) for use in routing calls based on a series of user-configured rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Connectivity Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Freepik. Creative Commons The following article outlines Video RTC and Mobile SDKs’ requirements for network connectivity. It lists the Interactive Powers CPaaS servers’ ports and IP addresses that the Widgets, Webclients or SDKs must be able to reach, and the bandwidth required for quality audio &amp;amp; video. As shown in the diagram below, two types of connections are required, Signalling and Media for Users and Agents sides.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.1.0:
## [1.0.0] - 2020-10-14 ​ ### First release ​ ## [1.0.1] - 2020-10-15 ​ ### Fixed ​ - Normalized the CallerID of the user to remove accents to avoid crashes on calls ​ ## [1.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
