<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Acd on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/acd/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Acd on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:12:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/acd/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Business Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 00:12:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-evolution-of-business-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Leading companies have a wholeness approach about how to communicate better with their customers across their processes. Communicate is a top priority for businesses today — but how can you quantify its value to your organization? That’s especially important in these times, with businesses managing the economic impact and uncertainty of disruptive events, and how this will impact both their customers and employees going forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/web-acd-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Web ACD platforms are designed to run over a Linux Debian 10.X x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.debian.org
   Requirement  Description      Distribution Linux Debian 10    Linux Kernel x86_64   Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure    Installer Minimal Install    Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in an ACD service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is ACD?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2021 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-acd/</guid>
      <description>An automated call distribution system, commonly known as Automatic Call Distributor (ACD), is a telecommunication system that answers incoming phone calls or video calls to distributes them within an organization. ACDs often provide some form of Automatic Customer/Caller Identification (ACIS), such as Direct Inward Dialing (DID), Dialed Number Identification Service (DNIS), Automatic Number Identification (ANI), or Video SPLIT ID (VSID) for use in routing calls based on a series of user-configured rules.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Network Connectivity Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/network-connectivity-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Freepik. Creative Commons The following article outlines Video RTC and Mobile SDKs’ requirements for network connectivity. It lists the Interactive Powers CPaaS servers’ ports and IP addresses that the Widgets, Webclients or SDKs must be able to reach, and the bandwidth required for quality audio &amp;amp; video. As shown in the diagram below, two types of connections are required, Signalling and Media for Users and Agents sides.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>