<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Startup on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/startup/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Startup on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/startup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with your customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us at our Spanish Website!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Interactive Powers in Spanish: Interacciones Digitales Interactive Powers is pleased to announce the release of our new spanish website called &amp;ldquo;Interacciones Digitales&amp;rdquo;, designed with a fresh new look and user-friendly responsive navigation, updated with the latest information about our products. We hope you will enjoy our new site in spanish. Our goal with new website is to provide our spanish speaker visitors and customers an easier way to learn about our solutions and cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy Holidays!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and happy holiday season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky Halloween night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>