<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trends on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trends on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice services are driven to increase the value of human interactions.</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-value-human-interactions/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Digital Transformation in Contact Center is not about Voice over IP, it&amp;rsquo;s about IA automation and more advanced human-to-human online collaboration. If the leading brands Google, Amazon, IBM and Microsoft are going to stay ahead of the competition, they need to quickly learn how to engage with customers using voice command technology in a meaningful way. All automated customer service platforms work using the same basic principle: process a question, crunch the relevant data, and deliver a response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voice Services are facing their biggest upgrade</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2018 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/voice-services-facing-biggest-upgrade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Today’s consumers are rekindling their love of voice and are learning to talk with machines better than ever. Automated text-based customer services, delivered through platforms such as WhatsApp, Messenger, Skype or any other Chat Service are still on the rise, but they aren’t dominating the conversation anymore. People are turning to Voice Assistants like Amazon Echo and Google Home Hub for quick answers to simple questions that are spoken, not typed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>