<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ecommerce on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ecommerce/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ecommerce on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ecommerce/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC Cloud Hosting platforms even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
 VoiceXML IVR CPaaS / SaaS Video RTC CPaaS / SaaS Turnkey SaaS: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Benefits</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week More data for a better service. Data provided by customers about their needs, preferences and individual tastes enable e-commerce businesses to create clients’ profiles and take into account their purchase history to better serve them. Clients should easily have the opportunity to give feedback, so their problems can be solved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Business Cases</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Nov 2017 00:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce-business-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 40% of online buyers who use live chat are more likely to make online purchases at least once a week Pre-sales support. Video options make it possible to show products to customers. They can check its appearance and functionality, making more informed purchase decisions.
Personalized shopping. Video and voice over the Internet allow you to pay the same special, individual attention to online customers as in face-to-face interactions in a more efficient way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>E-commerce · Industry</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 00:08:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-ecommerce/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons 77% of online shoppers want to contact a real person before buying, and more than half state that a lack of interaction has kept them from purchasing Video and voice over the internet allows to offer innovative ways for promotion. Attracting the attention of customers is a key element to increase sales and nowadays it is easier thanks to the numerous options this technology presents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>