<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnership on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/partnership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnership on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/partnership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Technologies and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Joining amazing eLearning Xlices tool with real-time experiences interactions MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies a pioneer in the field of elearning slide sharing Xlices, announces partnership with Interactive Powers to improve user experiences with real-time communications. In coming weeks, Xlices will be offered with advanced web voice calling features over web responsive service as well as over the phone.
Through this partnership, we will establish a framework for cooperation and work together to develop better software solutions, explore amazing Digital Transformation opportunities and amplify the impact along the eLearning on the customer journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers announces Video RTC integration with Genesys Cloud™</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 12:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Genesys - Interactive Powers Interactive Powers solutions combines with Genesys platforms to provide scalable Video Communications to Call Centers MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Interactive Powers has announced Video RTC is now available on the Genesys AppFoundry®, the industry&amp;rsquo;s largest dedicated marketplace focused on customer experience solutions. The AppFoundry allows Genesys customers from all market segments to discover and rapidly deploy a broad range of solutions that make it easier to interact with consumers, engage employees and optimize their workforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xenialab and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: XCally - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions! Customer Experience and new channels integration is a key factor for any company inside the digital world. Thank to Open Channel and Interactive Powers you can connect better and improve your interaction processes with customers and prospects. Xenialab and Interactive Powers are pleased to announce the integration between the Xenialab&amp;rsquo;s XCally (Open Channel) system and Video RTC technologies from Interactive Powers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>