<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Partnership on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/partnership/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Partnership on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/partnership/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Centribal Chatbot integration for Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/centribal-chatbots-integration-for-video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/centribal-chatbots-integration-for-video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Centribal - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions to ensure faster response times, more productive agents, and happier customers. MIAMI, August 22, 2021 — Interactive Powers and Centribal work together in complementary solutions since more than 2 years. That’s why we’re really excited to increase Centribal and Interactive Powers collaboration to offer the most complete Omnichannel Expericence that powers limitless, continuous CX conversations that cross boundaries while raising the bar on real-time visibility and control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Ubox: No Touch Kiosks &amp; Screens</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Gesture controlled Kiosks &amp;amp; Screens with Video RTC to enable new customer experiences. MIAMI, July. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies the creators of UBOX and Interactive Powers the creators of Video RTC announce new phygital experiences joining gesture and video real-time communications. UBOX is also a marketplace of experiences where hardware and software developers, designers, artists and data scientists can collaborate in projects together from different parts of the world easily, thus providing end-to-end​ ​solutions to consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Technologies and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquotechs-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Joining amazing eLearning Xlices tool with real-time experiences interactions MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies a pioneer in the field of elearning slide sharing Xlices, announces partnership with Interactive Powers to improve user experiences with real-time communications. In coming weeks, Xlices will be offered with advanced web voice calling features over web responsive service as well as over the phone.
Through this partnership, we will establish a framework for cooperation and work together to develop better software solutions, explore amazing Digital Transformation opportunities and amplify the impact along the eLearning on the customer journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers announces Video RTC integration with Genesys Cloud™</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 12:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/genesys-appfoundry-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Genesys - Interactive Powers Interactive Powers solutions combines with Genesys platforms to provide scalable Video Communications to Call Centers MIAMI, June. 1, 2020 — Interactive Powers has announced Video RTC is now available on the Genesys AppFoundry®, the industry&amp;rsquo;s largest dedicated marketplace focused on customer experience solutions. The AppFoundry allows Genesys customers from all market segments to discover and rapidly deploy a broad range of solutions that make it easier to interact with consumers, engage employees and optimize their workforce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Altitude Software and Interactive Powers celebrate more than 5 years of Video interactions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/altitude-software-xperience-hub-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 09:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/altitude-software-xperience-hub-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Altitude Software - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions for Altitude Xperience Hub! MIAMI, May 2, 2020 — Interactive Powers and Altitude Software work together in complementary solutions since more than 5 years. That’s why we’re really excited to increase Altitude Software and Interactive Powers collaboration to offer the most complete Omnichannel Contact Center that powers limitless, continuous CX conversations that cross boundaries while raising the bar on real-time visibility and control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Xenialab and Interactive Powers announce Integration Partnership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 May 2018 00:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/xenialab-interactive-powers-partnership/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: XCally - Interactive Powers Create amazing support and customer real-time interactions! Customer Experience and new channels integration is a key factor for any company inside the digital world. Thank to Open Channel and Interactive Powers you can connect better and improve your interaction processes with customers and prospects. Xenialab and Interactive Powers are pleased to announce the integration between the Xenialab&amp;rsquo;s XCally (Open Channel) system and Video RTC technologies from Interactive Powers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>