<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rtc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rtc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR. Give us a shout out!
https://twitter.com/ivrpowers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on at IVRPowers and on the latest news about RTC or IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Video-Audio SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint comes into Video Gateway (WebRTC | RTMP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins.
WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow IVRPowers on Instagram! We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you!
https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVRPowers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>IVRPowers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on RTC and IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
https://www.linkedin.com/company-beta/10060638/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening at IVRPowers by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced RTC and IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://blog.ivrpowers.com/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VideoRTC.js for Developers</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:30:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</guid>
      <description>Since 2015, IVRPowers has been diligently refining its Video RTC solutions, API Framework and SDKs to make embedded video much more accessible for developers and enterprises who are looking to rapidly integrate reliable video chat into their own applications.
Today, we’re thrilled to officially announce a new VideoRTC.js library – the launch of our self-service API Framework developer tools, which lets developers quickly and easily embed this same enterprise-grade, cloud-hosted, multiparty RTC video collaboration into any web, mobile or native application on virtually any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.test.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>