<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rtc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rtc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Screen Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-screen-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Secure screen share your desktop or any application in Real-Time Communications. Overview Screen Sharing application allows you to share live screen over the web or mobile instantly. Most business processes can take benefit of using Screen Sharing feature. For instance, it is a very powerful tool to improve online meetings, presentations, remote work or support services.
Screen Sharing functionality makes it easy to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content, all within the context of your website or application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · File Sharing</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-file-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Send and Receive Files or Documents in Real-Time Communications. Overview File Sharing application helps you to enhance your real-time communications experience with the power of content. It allows you to instantly transfer any file establishing a peer connection all within the context of your website or application. With the file sharing feature you can send and receive unlimited files just dragging them in the chat window.
File Sharing functionality makes it possible to share and receive documents during your voice or video call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Pop-up Agent</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-pop-up-agent/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-pop-up-agent/</guid>
      <description>Extend Existing Call Centers with Advanced Video RTC Capabilities. Overview Pop-up Agent is a specific peer component designed to add Video RTC services to an existing Call Center. It can operate over full WebRTC options or RTMP with limited functions. Pop-up Agent works with standard web browser or with an MS Windows executable application.
Pop-up Agent functionality is easily configurable with a set of buttons and toolkit. Main options are Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Core Features</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-core-features/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes core features that you can activate according to your own business requirements . All of this, is part of the main capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Know more about our Video RTC core features here:
Video Calling. Video Gateway provides a simpler way for people to communicate via web. It integrates seamlessly into the workflows and it is easy to manage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Live Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-live-chat/</guid>
      <description>Manage Smart Text Message interactions in Real-Time Communications. Overview Live Chat supplement your video and voice communication with advanced text chat capabilities using the WebRTC datachannel. Live Chat feature allows to send and receive text messages simultaneously, without any lag at a single click. It is the perfect tool to use for the customer and an agent conversation. Live chat integrates seamlessly into your application, eliminating the need for clunky third-party APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers · Microsites</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/products-microsites/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are pleased to share our nice product microsite links in this post. You will find a summary of all features and an easier way to talk about them from socials networks and email.
Microsite - VoiceXML IVR Refining IVR with Software · http://voicexml.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Video RTC Video Real Time Communications · http://videortc.ivrpowers.com
Microsite - Webclient Calling from any Web Browser · http://webclient.ivrpowers.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s E-commerce become a Better Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Latest Video Real-Time Communications can be decisive to improve e-commerce services. First of all, because they are becoming very accessible and easy to use through web browsers or most of mobile devices. Plugin downloads are no longer required, you just click and your are connected. Secondly, remember that creating a live interaction with your customers like a live chat or video call channels is a proven way to increase your sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) Roadmap 2017!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2017 23:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-roadmap-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons We are pleased to unveil some key elements of our Video RTC (WebRTC) evolution until 2017. Major changes will follow WebRTC’s evolution itself. Our primary goal is to provide improved features to all Special Extensions like SPLIT, Video Calling, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Video Recording, Snapshot&amp;hellip; In the next quarter, we will make significant improvements like adding a better Customer Experience with Video Real-Time Communications&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2.0:
## [2.2.0] - 2017-07-27 ### Added - Added interval Watchdog - Added autocall GET parameter to the Webclient URL usecase - Added overprint logo in the Webclient usecase  Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telehealth: When Technology Meets Medicine</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:31:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/technology-meets-medicine/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Flickr. Creative Commons Telemedicine exists since long time ago. In 19th century, Sigmund Freud used to write letters to his patients. It was a primitive distance doctor-patient relationship. However, in the next century telemedicine did not change a lot. Just few years ago, doctors would pick up the phone, and that was about as far as we have got in terms of telemedicine. But things have evolved in the last decade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser to SIP Calling?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration How can you call a Desk Phone from any Web Browser? Our both Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) can convert web browser media streams (video - audio - data) to SIP from WebRTC or RTMP peers communications. This interesting feature allows to connect easily web services to existing VoIP telephony channels of your IVR or PBX. We can consider all of this approach like a direct calling webphone or like a WebRTC-DDI or RTMP-DDI in a SIP trunk from an operator service configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of a WebRTC System</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/webrtc-system-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons A WebRTC System can bring several benefits to all types of enterprises and users. For different market segments, the benefit would really be overwhelming, as the app would give them the power to open up a wealth of opportunities to serve their clients and customers, in a very innovative way. Using the network, companies can open up real-time and live video chats sessions with customers, and vice-versa, to provide their help and support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VideoRTC.js for Developers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:30:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers elaboration Since 2015, Interactive Powers has been diligently refining its Video RTC solutions, API Framework and SDKs to make embedded video much more accessible for developers and enterprises who are looking to rapidly integrate reliable video chat into their own applications.
VideoRTC.js library Today, we’re thrilled to officially announce a new VideoRTC.js library – the launch of our self-service API Framework developer tools, which lets developers quickly and easily embed this same enterprise-grade, cloud-hosted, multiparty RTC video collaboration into any web, mobile or native application on virtually any device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) is a collection of communications protocols and application programming interfaces that enable real-time communication over peer-to-peer connections. This allows web browsers to not only request resources from backend servers, but also real-time information from browsers of other users.
This enables applications such as video conferencing, file transfer, chat, or desktop sharing without the need of either internal or external plugins. WebRTC is being standardized by the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) and the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR.
Give us a shout out! https://twitter.com/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>