<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rtc on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rtc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/rtc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR. Give us a shout out!
https://twitter.com/ivrpowers</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTMP?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 00:19:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Real Time Messaging Protocol or RTMP is mainly serving for high speed transmission of audio, video and data between flash player and a server. Initially developed by Macromedia, the protocol is now owned by Adobe, and specifications about it have only partially been released for public use.
According to those specifications, the RTMP protocol has multiple variations, i.e. the “plain” RTMP protocol, RTMPS which is RTMP over an TLS/SSL connection, RTMPE which is RTMP encrypted using Adobe’s own security mechanism, and RTMPT which is encapsulated within HTTP requests to traverse firewalls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key factors to select a Telehealth Solution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/4-factors-select-telehealth-solution/</guid>
      <description>Implementing telehealth can help physicians reach people in remote or rural areas who may not be able to travel to a particular facility or specialist as well as those in more densely populated urban areas who find inner-city mass transit insufficient for their needs. As a result, more organizations are turning to telehealth as a viable alternative to routine in-office physician visits.
To implement properly the kind of telehealth solution that both clinicians and patients will trust and use takes a lot of up-front planning, you should consider these four key considerations before putting telehealth into practice:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC: Special Extensions</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-special-extensions/</guid>
      <description>Video Gateway (WebRTC) includes many features or special extensions that you can activate according to your own business processes. All of this, is part of the capabilities of our Video RTC solution suite.
Video RTC special extensions are:
Live Chat. Video Gateway supports Live Chat feature thru a DataChannel. You can customize all the User or Agent front-end in Flash or HTML5 according the gateway mode you have deployed for your service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VideoRTC</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is IVR?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Voice Response (IVR) is a technology that allows a computer to interact with humans through the use of voice and DTMF tones input via keypad. In telecommunications, IVR allows customers to interact with a company’s host system via a telephone keypad or by speech recognition, after which services can be inquired about through the IVR dialogue. IVR systems can respond with prerecorded or dynamically generated audio to further direct users on how to proceed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is RTC?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-rtc/</guid>
      <description>A clear definition of Real-time communications (RTC) is important to understand what will be the newest evolution of Internet applications and services for businesses and individuals. All is moving around to more real-time, more video, better sound quality, better screen resolution, easier human-interfaces… RTC technology helps to share together most of our senses thru digital networks at light’s speed:
RTC is any mode of telecommunications in which all users can exchange information instantly or with negligible latency.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>