<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Support on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/support/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Support on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/support/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s E-commerce become a Better Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 12:14:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/e-commerce-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Latest Video Real-Time Communications can be decisive to improve e-commerce services. First of all, because they are becoming very accessible and easy to use through web browsers or most of mobile devices. Plugin downloads are no longer required, you just click and your are connected. Secondly, remember that creating a live interaction with your customers like a live chat or video call channels is a proven way to increase your sales.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>