<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sdk on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/sdk/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sdk on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/sdk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · API Framework</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-api-framework/</guid>
      <description>Provide Core Functions to easily develop any Video RTC application for Web and Mobile. Overview API Framework feature helps to make your job easier, adapting services to your needs and personalizing them. Our platform provides developers with a wide range of possible solutions, through a flexible and powerful toolkit for building Web APIs.
API Framework feature enables developers to design new APIs or edit existing ones. You can also customize all the way down, just using basic regular features.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing VideoRTC.js for Developers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2017 00:30:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/development/introducing-videortcjs-developers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers elaboration Since 2015, Interactive Powers has been diligently refining its Video RTC solutions, API Framework and SDKs to make embedded video much more accessible for developers and enterprises who are looking to rapidly integrate reliable video chat into their own applications.
VideoRTC.js library Today, we’re thrilled to officially announce a new VideoRTC.js library – the launch of our self-service API Framework developer tools, which lets developers quickly and easily embed this same enterprise-grade, cloud-hosted, multiparty RTC video collaboration into any web, mobile or native application on virtually any device.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>