<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nlu on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/nlu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in nlu on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/nlu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR · Speech Recognition Reloaded</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/smart-ivr-speech-recognition-reloaded/</guid>
      <description>More and better protocols to improve performance of your interactive phone services.  Speech recognition is a key complementary feature for any IVR in order enables the recognition and translation of spoken language into text for your voice application coding. It is also known as automatic speech recognition (ASR) or speech to text (STT). Smart IVR support today three connectors since the last release 2.x and it has the ability to use them in perfect combination for all services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Feb 2019 02:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/getting-started-with-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Conversational IVR, is the Next Big Thing in Telephony and Internet of Things to connect better your customers with your business.  Forget the technology, building the next generation of IVR self-services is more a question of business process to understand how your voice self-service has to manage the conversation. We are please to share this interesting video from Google about DialogFlow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU for Chatbots?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Feb 2019 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/what-about-chatbots/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Dialog Flow - Desconstructing Chatbots, Interactive Powers edited. Building the future of Conversational IVR with a Natural Language Understanding NLU interfaces instead of Prompts or Menus with direct dialogs.  We are pleased to share a very interesting video from Google about Chatbots under the wood technology. It’s really easy to understand in just few minutes: what is the new approach to build an advanced Natural Language Understanding (NLU) interfaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip;  Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
 Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
