<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Nlu on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/nlu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Nlu on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/nlu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip; Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is NLU?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-nlu/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: “Her” (movie) – A man talking to a machine… Natural Language Understanding (NLU) can be a complementary in-side programing feature or a specific engine for an IVR. Currently, NLU is still an emerging technology but its nearest evolution is already starting to change the business of Customer Service.
 Natural Language Understanding (NLU) is a branch of artificial intelligence (AI) that uses computer software to understand input made in the form of sentences in text or speech format.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>