<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Humaninteraction on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/humaninteraction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Humaninteraction on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/humaninteraction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Secret is the Emotion</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 13:10:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/secret-emotion/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons New technologies make it possible than ever to resolve problems on multiple channels. And because of new digital behaviors, users also expect a better customer experience: faster and easier. Therefore, companies need to ensure a differentiated customer service that keeps clients satisfied.
Selfservice is not the answer to all situations Digital services, such as IVR, are a good supplement and, if company employs efficient technology, customers enjoy self-service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video gets more Honest Buyers than other Channels</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 19:11:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons According to a W. Frank Barton School of Business at Wichita State University new research, sending a text message, making a phone call or have a face-to-face conversation leads people to lie often than video conferencing. The study found that buyers were:
 95% more likely to report deception via text messages than if they had interacted via video 31% more likely to report deception when compared to face-to-face communication in person 18% more likely if the interaction was via audio chat or phone call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>