<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>showroom on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/showroom/</link>
    <description>Recent content in showroom on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/showroom/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC for Genesys / Demo Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/demo-center-video-rtc-for-genesys/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/demo-center-video-rtc-for-genesys/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Getting started&amp;hellip; Demo Center is only available for Customers and Partners that are deploying or running our platforms, if you are not registred please contact our Sales Team to get all information and partnerships.
Features:
 Video &amp;amp; Voice Calling Live Chat File Sharing Dual Screen Sharing CoBrowsing Snapshot Flip Camera QR Code  Ask for your Live Demo, register and login at: https://support.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest VoiceXML IVR features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of main features (VoiceXML):
 Dashboard VoiceXML editor Applications SIP Connectivity Speech Connectors CDR Reporting Settings Logs  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (RTMP)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 15:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (RTMP) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (RTMP):
 SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Playground (Flash Configurator) Click-to-call (Webclient) Documentation  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (WebRTC):
 Videoroom (multi-conference) Private room (ID/password) SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Click-to-call (Webclient) Videomail (post a video message) Videoplayer (play single and dual video records) Meeting Point (OAuth Authentication Meetings)  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
