<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>videocc on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocc/</link>
    <description>Recent content in videocc on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videocc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HD Quality / Video Recording</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires scalable HD quality and powerful video recording for any size professional service.  No one wants laggy audio or pixelated video quality in a meeting, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re meeting with clients or prospects. Interactive Powers comes with crystal-clear HD video and the most advanced video recording storage system for any size Video Call / Contact Centers deployment.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Centric / Unified Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires powerful real-time communications where Video is a top priority integrated channel.  Beyond video calls, what if your team also communicates through phone calls and text chat? Interactive Powers lets you consolidate all those tools into one. Talk, message, and meet all from one convenient channel. That makes for fewer software to pay for and manage and less time wasted on context-switching for all your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust Security Setting</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC Privacy and Security are key mandatory questions for your business and customers.  Keep your meetings secure with strong 256-bit encrypted real-time communications and session tokenization. Interactive Powers&#39; settings allow the host to mute participants, process biometrics API, lock file sharing, limit screen sharing, encode parameters and much more.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.0 features to get the best Video CC experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Control / Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 15:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires at least the same transactional call functions as Voice to ensure agents performance.  In our agent side, all the call controls you need are easily in reach. Adjust your call settings, start a screen share, mute and unmute yourself, or start and pause yourself or video recording. It&amp;rsquo;s all in a clean, video first, easy-to-use interface that lays out all these options for you right on the screen and our flap button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual Screen Sharing / CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC without advanced web collaborative tools, is like a Call / Contact Center without call management.  Need to zoom in on a design mockup or run through a contract approval? Interactive Powers dual screen sharing feature lets double share contents from agent and user at the same time. By the way, you choose between sharing a specific window or tab or your whole desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Responsive based Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers No Apps, No Downloads, No Register is a must be, not an option for your Video CC deployment.  Some video conferencing software will make you download the desktop or mobile app to host and join video calls. But Interactive Powers solutions are browser-based, which means it won’t force you or your clients to download an app. Host and join meetings from a web browser using your computer or mobile device, and get it all running with No Apps, No Downloads, No Register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call / Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 12:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC productivity must be part of your Call / Contact Center, it&amp;rsquo;s not just a nice to have feature.  Need to meet face-to-face virtually your clients? Start managing unlimited transactional video calls for your team. It isn&amp;rsquo;t always practical to have every single meeting in person. And today, there are lots of video meeting apps that are designed more for hangouts with colleagues and chatting with loved ones.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
