<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with you customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (RTMP)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 00:00:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (RTMP) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (RTMP):
 SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Playground (Flash Configurator) Click-to-call (Webclient) Documentation  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (WebRTC):
 Videoroom (multi-conference) Private room (ID/password) SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Click-to-call (Webclient) Videomail (post a video message) Videoplayer (play single and dual video records) Meeting Point (OAuth Authentication Meetings)  Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video gets more Honest Buyers than other Channels</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 19:11:25 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/video-gets-more-honest-buyers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons According to a W. Frank Barton School of Business at Wichita State University new research, sending a text message, making a phone call or have a face-to-face conversation leads people to lie often than video conferencing. The study found that buyers were:
 95% more likely to report deception via text messages than if they had interacted via video 31% more likely to report deception when compared to face-to-face communication in person 18% more likely if the interaction was via audio chat or phone call.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>