<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turnkey on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/turnkey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Turnkey on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/turnkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Web Dialer</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-dialer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jul 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-web-dialer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Unsplash · Interactive Powers Creative Commons. Make calls from any Web Browser and easily connect your Call Center or PBX to improve your business communications. Click-to-call converts your website&amp;rsquo;s users into engaged customers by creating an easy way for your customers to contact your sales and support teams right on your website without using their phone. Today&amp;rsquo;s sales and support teams expect to be able to make calls directly from their modern web browser, and their efficiency improves when they can.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Turnkey</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</guid>
      <description>The Turnkey Solutions for your business Our Trunkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
 Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business.
 Web Dialer. Make Voice Calls from any modern Web Browser
Web Dialer allows all your customers and users to make phone calls directly to your PBX, IVR, Call Center from any desktop web browser (Firefox, Chrome, IE, Safari, Opera,…).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Remote Viewer</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-remote-viewer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 May 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-remote-viewer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock · Interactive Powers. Dramatically improves Customer Experience (CX) extending phone calls with Live Chat, Dual File Sharing, Dual Screen Sharing… Sometime, you don&amp;rsquo;t have to change all things to build something new and really better to improve your existing Business Communications. Remote Viewer is a new Video RTC Use Case and solution that allows to add advanced powers both to your call center agents and phone callers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>