<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trends on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trends on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Data: Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons Nearly one-third of Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat to improve Customer Engagement According to a research from Dimension Data, nearly one-third of contact centers expect to deploy video chat for customer engagement. The research says that giving customers the additional option to remotely connect face-to-face, at moments that are important to them (and on their terms), can make their customer experience even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>