<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trends on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/trends/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trends on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/trends/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39;, it&#39;s a must have.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Now, It&amp;rsquo;s won’t be an option. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of business survival in post-COVID19 society. Just one year ago, we had annouced that Video was no longer &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; for Call Centers, now it will change the entire world market permanently.
As you may read in the research analyts reports, Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications according to &amp;ldquo;more optimistics&amp;rdquo; predictions published past year as usual&amp;hellip; Even, if video was much better than voice for any digital real time human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39; for Call Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers It&amp;rsquo;s not Fashion, it&amp;rsquo;s a question of Evolution. Companies and brands that are not yet concidering a progresive transition of their phone channel to Real-Time Communications (RTC) within the next years for their customer care, sales or support will quickly become old fashioned and irrelevant for new consumers. The next customers generation is no longer accepting to downgrade their daily high speed interactions and expectations on advanced devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video calls are not an annoying feature for younger generations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Children feel more confortable having video calls than phone calls. If you have the opportunity to check how children understand Live Communications, you will quickly realise that phone is absolutly not a priority for them. They will never ask you about using a phone number and never want to remember just what it is. This new generation is born under a full digital world&amp;rsquo;s devices with high speed Internet and they absolutly are not aware about using limited or poor interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videobots are coming…</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>Video AI agents with an human like behaviour are closer than you may think… Today, Xinhua, China’s state-run press agency, has unveiled new “AI anchors” — digital composites created from footage of human hosts that read the news using synthesised voices.
The news anchor, based on the latest AI technology, has a male image with a voice, facial expressions and actions of a real person. &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rdquo; learns from live broadcasting videos by himself and can read texts as naturally as a human.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Total Cost of Ownership</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/total-cost-of-ownership/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/total-cost-of-ownership/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons. TCO is particularly important when you’re deploying Video RTC solutions, and it allows companies to gain substantial cost advantages in implementation, training, maintenance, and system management. Most analysts agree that on-premises will cost you less up front. You pay a one-time license fee, along with a maintenance subscription covering things like vendor support. These are far cheaper than the cost of your cloud subscription over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Premise vs Cloud</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons. There is many reasons to consider replacing an on-premises infrastructure with a cloud-based video real-time communication platform as a service. If your communication infrastructure don’t supports modern video communications or faces end-of-life, you need to plan your migration strategy now to avoid pitfalls down the road. Also consider the seasonality of your business and the best time to be upgraded. For reference, on-premises solutions typically require more time to procure, generally weeks or months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>McKinsey: Banks branch in the Digital Age</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/mckinsey-bank-branch-digital-age/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/mckinsey-bank-branch-digital-age/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Smart-branch in the digital age will dedicated 70% of services areas to self-services thank to advanced technologies.  Digital technology holds the key to the branch of the future.
 Changing customer behavior and the emergence of new technologies spell not the end of the branch but rather the advent of the “smart branch.” Smart branches use technology to boost sales and improve customer experience significantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, as a new game changer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-as-a-new-game-changer/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Consumers welcome convenience of Video Calling to talk to brands and businesses, 24% would consider switching to a bank that offered Video Calling. The majority of person-to-person video calls currently happen through third-party social media and messaging applications like Skype, Messenger and WhatsApp etc. especially on mobile phones. To capitalize on this user behavior, 38% of brands and businesses have to integrate video calling within their own website and mobile applications, while a further 46% are currently considering it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling, is the next CX frontier for brands</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-calling-is-the-next-cx-frontier-for-brands/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons. Video Calling is becoming the next channel to include for businesses and avoid consumer switching to other brands with an complete omnichannel customer services. Facing the demand, 21% of businesses expect to launch video calling pilot services within the next two years. The key benefits driving this uptake include improved customer experience (CX). &amp;ldquo;Consumers are expecting to be able to engage with the brands and businesses in their lives whenever, and however they like, with Video Calling becoming an increasingly important complementary channel across multiple industries from retail to financial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voicebots are the new IVR for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2018 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voicebots-ivr-call-center-voice-channel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. The Contact Center Voice Channel may not going away in the &amp;ldquo;short time&amp;rdquo;, but it will be progressively supplemented by Voicebots in the next few years&amp;hellip; Past months, Google’s Duplex demo forced us to think more about a world where we might get a random call from a business and not realize it is a robot making the call. Recent proof of concepts have verified that this technology is not just a staged demo but it actually works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of CPaaS for Video Real-Time Communications in Businesses</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Feb 2018 10:46:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/rise-of-cpaas-video-real-time-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers In the next 12 months, up to 49% of Business Cases that will run video services are using a Communication Platform-as-a-Service (CPaaS). Telemedicine and Insurance Professionals. Trends are showing that a leading industry in incorporating video is telehealth with 47% of respondents embedded video into a telehealth application. Video offers numerous advantages to this sector. It allows patients to receive attention at convenience from the comfort of their homes and it helps health institutions to significantly reduce costs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers and Customer Experience in 2018</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2018 20:23:11 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/2018-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Companies must recognize CX as a key competitive differentiator and make sweeping changes in Channels to keep up this year. In the last years, digital technologies have changed the way we work and relate to each other. These changes have also impacted on customers’ expectations. Clients increasingly demand a more personalized, accessible and comfortable attention.
Daily Business Communications. Clients expect from companies the possibility of contacting them through the same variety of channels they use in their everyday life communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AI in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2018 21:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/ai-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. By 2030, AI solutions will surpass the services provided by agents. Just a few years ago, talking about Artificial Intelligence (AI) meant talking about a futuristic scenario. Today, AI is everywhere and, directly or indirectly, we are starting to use it almost every day. The rapid evolution of AI allows it to be increasingly applied to more sophisticated processes which require a high precision like customer services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>79% of Consumers Want the Opportunity to Contact Businesses Online</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 09:03:53 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/enghouse-business-online/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons In a recent Enghouse Interactive survey, customers have made it clear that they want online communication channels with companies. 79% of consumers believe that businesses should provide a way for customers to contact them online.
It is also interesting to compare this figure with the responses to the very same question in previous years&amp;rsquo; surveys. In 2014, only 29% of respondents answered that the possibility to contact a company online was relevant.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Rise of Public Cloud API Services</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-api-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 20:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-api-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers The public cloud computing market is raising earnings for Internet&amp;rsquo;s giants Google, Amazon, Microsoft&amp;hellip; One of the major trend that is working behind the scenes and driving many of the most successful businesses these past few years is: Cloud Application Programming Interfaces (API). APIs are a technology that allow firms to interact and share information with other firms at an unprecedented scale, taking advantage of the far-reaching progress in digitization and the rising influence of software in our day-to-day lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons to embrace Cloud Hosting</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:50:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. Upgrade your business communications to the Cloud to deliver more value with less costs Computing based on the internet is booming business. The global cloud communication market is projected to reach $4.45 by 2021. Why are more and more companies turning to the cloud for their business communications needs?
Communications solutions at a lower cost. Cloud computing is a cost saver since it can reduce or even eliminate the need for a company to buy an expensive hardware and software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technavio: IVR market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/technavio-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The Interactive Voice Response (IVR) market is growing, but what’s driving that growth? Market research analysts from Technavio suggest that the IVR, or Interactive Voice Response market, will see a growth of around 13% between this year, and 2021. For those who are new to the industry, IVR systems are the solutions that give companies a stronger way of engaging their customers through various customer service solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner: 20 percent of Global Businesses will deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest Global Businesses will implement Video Chat. Time is the new currency for your customers who are looking for painless and informed solutions to their issues. We are also starting, growing and running companies in an &amp;ldquo;attention economy,&amp;rdquo; which is defined by the view that human attention is a scarce commodity. By 2018, according to research from Gartner, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Forrester: Voice Channel as Self-service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/forrester-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons 63 percent of US adult callers report to use the voice channel for self-service (IVR) According to a 2016 Forrester Research study, 83 percent of U.S. adult Internet users had a phone conversation with a customer service representative in the past year. Sixty-three percent of them also reported using the voice channel for self-service, such as Interactive Voice Response (IVR) systems whose Conversational AI capabilities enable callers to converse with a virtual agent as if there were a human rep on the other end.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Economist: Visual Recognition with &#39;Deep Learning&#39; is suparsing Humans for First Time</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/theeconomist-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons Visual Recognition Algorithms reach an accuracy of 96% with &amp;ldquo;Deep Learning&amp;rdquo; The rehabilitation of “AI”, and the current excitement about the field, can be traced back to 2012 and an online contest called the ImageNet Challenge. ImageNet is an online database of millions of images, all labelled by hand. For any given word, such as “balloon” or “strawberry”, ImageNet contains several hundred images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Data: Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons Nearly one-third of Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat to improve Customer Engagement According to a research from Dimension Data, nearly one-third of contact centers expect to deploy video chat for customer engagement. The research says that giving customers the additional option to remotely connect face-to-face, at moments that are important to them (and on their terms), can make their customer experience even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deloitte: Global Contact Center Survey - Customer Interaction Channels 2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/deloitte-contact-center-customer-interaction-channels-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons The most significant change predicted for Contact Centers in the next two years is a decrease in voice interactions by around -26%. Contacts by Phone are expected to drop from 64 percent of interactions today to 47 percent in 2019. Much of this migration away from the phone could shift to online chat and messaging; respondents expect use of these channels to increase to 16 percent by 2019, from 6 percent this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Next Step in Security: Your Face is Your Password</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2017 10:09:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/security-face-as-password/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons You can leave behind all the tricks to remember dozens of passwords and PINs because biometrics are already here. One of the leading businesses applying it are banks.
New authentication processes through technology New digital services make most of visits to bank branch unnecessary. Biometric software allows customers to log into their bank accounts through their mobile phones without a password. A mobile phone with a camera is enough to solve everyday bank issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Trends Impacting Customer Experience</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2017 12:30:37 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-trends-customer-experience/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is more important than ever. While brands that focus on getting an excellent service are immediately rewarded, a poor customer service highly damages companies: disloyalty, bad image and loss of money are some of the serious consequences. Because of it, according to Forrester, 72% of businesses say improving customer experience is their top priority
Some challenges present an opportunity to add strategic value to your business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC: a Trending Technology for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/webrtc-trending-technology-business/</guid>
      <description>Technology is continuously changing our daily tasks. We pay bills, book concert tickets, buy food and even we can control our home from a device. People, especially younger generations, expect technological innovations in their everyday life. It happens so in business and ignoring this reality will lead to loss of potential and therefore of competitiveness.
Technology Impact Technology solutions have a great impact on Customer Experience. And one of the latest trends in the field is WebRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The increasing Business of Real-Time Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jun 2017 13:32:54 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/increasing-business-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Demands for Real-Time Communications (RTC) solutions are growing. In an increasingly connected world, customers access to information through multiple channels and expect personalized and always available services. According to Pew Research Center, 1 in 5 adults in US. report that are always almost on line and, overall, 73% of US citizens go online on a daily basis.
For Buyers, Sellers, Prospects Today, buyers, sellers, prospects and partners expect a bidirectional exchange of information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
 they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number…
 they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context…  That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>