<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>cctr on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cctr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in cctr on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cctr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Recovery</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-call-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-call-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik Revolutionizing Customer Experience in Video Communications In today&amp;rsquo;s communication landscape, interruptions and wireless network disconnections are inevitable. These issues can significantly affect the quality of internet and video calls, presenting a serious challenge. They often lead to substantial time waste for both agents and users, frequently resulting in incomplete transactions. This problem is particularly critical in contact centers, where most service providers lack effective recovery mechanisms for phone calls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT AI Copilot?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-ai-copilot/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-ai-copilot/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik SPLIT AI Copilot: Delivers real-time, proactive knowledge and actions during user-agent interactions. SPLIT AI Copilot is an AI-driven interface based on SIP and designed to support contact center agents by providing real-time assistance during customer interactions. Part of the Video RTC platform, SPLIT AI Copilot identifies customer intent and offers agents immediate access to relevant knowledge resources, next-step guidance, and real-time suggestions. This enables agents to handle inquiries more effectively without needing to search for information manually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Deaf Interpreter?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-deaf-interpreter/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-deaf-interpreter/</guid>
      <description>SPLIT Deaf Interpreter: Provides efficient sign language interpretation through real-time video communication to phone calls. SPLIT Deaf Interpreter is an innovative video communication interface designed to bridge the communication gap for deaf users during phone calls. This cutting-edge solution seamlessly connects deaf individuals with skilled sign language interpreters in real-time, enabling smooth and effective communication. By leveraging advanced video technology, SPLIT Deaf Interpreter ensures that deaf users can engage in phone conversations with ease, overcoming traditional barriers and fostering inclusivity in telecommunications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT WhatsApp?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-whatsapp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers - Freepik SPLIT WhatsApp: Enhancing Contact Center Communication with Voice and Video Calls. SPLIT WhatsApp offers a powerful feature that allows users to seamlessly transition from a standard WhatsApp conversation to a full-fledged video call. This functionality provides a smooth and efficient way to escalate communication when needed, enhancing the overall user experience. By enabling this scale-up capability, SPLIT WhatsApp bridges the gap between text-based messaging and face-to-face interaction, all within the familiar WhatsApp environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SPLIT 6.x Update</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 20:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/split-6-x-update/</guid>
      <description>The sixth generation Video RTC Gateways, meticulously developed by Interactive Powers, incorporate the innovative SPLIT module. This advanced feature enables the seamless separation of all media streams, including video, audio, and data, providing unprecedented flexibility and control. The SPLIT module represents a significant leap forward in communication technology, allowing for more efficient handling and routing of multimedia content.
This cutting-edge development is currently based on a robust combination of SIP (Session Initiation Protocol) and WebRTC (Web Real-Time Communication) technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Picture-in-Picture</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/picture-in-picture-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/picture-in-picture-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Maximizing Agent Productivity with “Picture-in-Picture” during Video Calls. Picture-in-picture (PiP) is a useful feature for contact center agents who need to multitask during transactional video calls. With PiP, agents can continue to have a conversation with their customers while also keeping an eye on other important information or tasks that require their attention.
Some features that can make PiP even more useful for agents include the ability to resize and reposition the PiP window, the option to customize which part of the screen is shown in the PiP window, and the ability to mute or pause the PiP video while still keeping it visible on the screen.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phone Number Obsolescence: The Shift to Web Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/phone-number-obsolescence-the-shift-to-web-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/phone-number-obsolescence-the-shift-to-web-calling/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Communication has evolved rapidly over the past few decades, and one of the most notable changes has been the shift from traditional phone numbers to web calling methods. This evolution has changed the way we connect with each other and has provided new avenues for businesses to communicate with customers. In this blog post, we’ll explore the evolution of phone numbers to web calling methods and how they have impacted communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Operational differences between transactional video calls and video room meetings</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/transactional-video-calls-vs-video-room-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/transactional-video-calls-vs-video-room-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Transactional video calls and video room meetings are two different forms of communication that have been made possible by modern WebRTC and SIP technologies. Transactional video calls are a form of one-on-one communication in real-time, while video room meetings are a form of group collaboration linked connection.
Transactional Video Calls Transactional video calls enable two or three people to communicate with each other in real-time, and are typically used for professional conversations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing device and network conditions before making Video Calls in Customer Support or Customer Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/test-device-conditions-before-making-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/test-device-conditions-before-making-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers In the digital communication era, video calls have become a fundamental tool for companies that offer advanced customer services or customer support as well. However, often these video calls can present technical and network issues that can affect the quality of communication and the user&amp;rsquo;s experience.
That is why it is essential to have a Tester application that tests the communication conditions, web browser, audio devices, microphone, and bandwidth available before making a video call with Internet users in a service open to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 reasons to use Background Effects for Video Contact Center services</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-reasons-to-use-background-effects-for-video-contact-center-services/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-reasons-to-use-background-effects-for-video-contact-center-services/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Improving Video Calling performance and Customer Experience with professional Background Effects: Solid, Picture or Blur In recent years, video contact center services have become increasingly popular as more and more businesses realize the benefits of being able to connect with customers face-to-face, even if they&amp;rsquo;re not in the same physical location. With the pandemic accelerating the shift to remote work, the use of video calls has become a critical part of providing customer support, sales, and other services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 Key Benefits of Building a Conversational IVR with Natural Language in VoiceXML</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-key-benefits-of-building-a-conversational-ivr-with-natural-language-in-voicexml/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 18:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/5-key-benefits-of-building-a-conversational-ivr-with-natural-language-in-voicexml/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers In recent years, there has been a growing trend towards the use of conversational IVR systems with natural language interaction. This type of IVR system allows users to interact with the system in a more natural and conversational way, which can improve the overall user experience and increase customer satisfaction. When it comes to building a conversational IVR system, VoiceXML is a popular technology that offers a number of advantages over other technologies like Voice API or legacy IVR.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of Video Call Recording for online customer support</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/the-importance-of-video-call-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Feb 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/the-importance-of-video-call-recording/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Why getting video recordings is key for a successful Video Contact Center? Benefits, Implementation Considerations, and Recommendations Currently, many companies are looking for implementing a video contact center as a way to improve the customer experience. However, not all of these companies are fully taking advantage of the potential of this tool. One of the most important features to consider when implementing a video contact center is the ability to record customer interactions on video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 6 reasons you should upgrade your Call Center to a Video Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/6-top-reasons-you-may-upgrade-your-call-center-to-a-video-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 19:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/6-top-reasons-you-may-upgrade-your-call-center-to-a-video-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Video Contact Centers are a rising trend in the customer service industry As the world emerges from the pandemic, the way businesses operate is also changing. One emerging trend in the customer service industry is the adoption of video contact centers. Unlike traditional call centers, video contact centers offer a more personalized and interactive experience for customers, and are becoming increasingly popular among Digital Age consumers. In this post, we will discuss the advantages of video contact centers over traditional call centers, and how they can benefit businesses and their customers alike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Revolutionize your Customer Experience (CX) introducing a Video Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/revolutionize-your-customer-experience-with-video-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/revolutionize-your-customer-experience-with-video-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Connect, Reinvent, Empower&amp;hellip; your Business In today&amp;rsquo;s digital world, customers expect to have a variety of communication options when interacting with businesses. Video is becoming an increasingly popular choice, and companies are finding that adding a video channel to their contact center is not just &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; but a necessity. That&amp;rsquo;s why a Video Contact Center is the game changer you&amp;rsquo;ve been looking for.
Video Channels as a game changer By adding Video Channels to your Contact Center, you can provide face-to-face interaction for your agents and improve your business with a more human customer care experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Widgets</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/video-rtc-widgets-update/</guid>
      <description>Deploy full web responsive widgets with a single script or URL in your website or apps. Today we are excited to announce that we are open sourcing a new Widget for Video RTC to handle incoming or outgoing video calls and prompt users for input, record calls, connect callers to agents, and more.
Main features:
FAB Button enabled Flip Camera (new) Mute Camera Mute Audio Live Chat File Sharing Dual / Single Screen Sharing Snapshot (optional) Overprint Logo More options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Image in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2020 20:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-image/</guid>
      <description>Allows you o display an image as your background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls replacing your background by a nice picture removes all your surroundings so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can change your background, or add a background image during your video call sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Background Blur in Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/background-blur/</guid>
      <description>Allows you to blur the background during your business video calls. Improve your sales or business video calls blurring your background makes your surroundings appear out of focus so people can&amp;rsquo;t see the details of what&amp;rsquo;s going on behind you.
Limit distractions and maintain privacy in your current surroundings by using a virtual background. You can blur your background during your meeting, event, or training session.
Unretouched Screenshots:
Need to add it right now?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to add a Video Channel to your existing Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/how-to-add-video-channel-to-existing-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Transform your existing call center into a more engaging, customizable, and interactive solution with video calls. In today’s competitive market, companies need call center software to connect in real-time cross web browsers and mobile devices. Adding advanced video interactions such web call, video call, live chat, file sharing, co-browsing, screen sharing… give your clients and agents the option to communicate better than ever with your brand.
The Empowered Omnichannel: What any Contact Center in the Digital Age should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Peer-to-Peer?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-peer-to-peer/</guid>
      <description>Make and Receive Video Calls between Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to manage and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) between two peers. This connection is based on a WebRTC communication session running voice, video and data.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.
How does Peer-to-Peer work? Peer-to-Peer (WebRTC) enables to connect many Web Browsers or Mobile Devices with Real-Time Communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is WebRTC-to-SIP?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-webrt-to-sip/</guid>
      <description>Receive Audio Calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a SPLIT module which enable to control all media streams (video - audio - data) on any communication between users and a SIP softswitch or PBX/ACD. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice and data.
Connect a Web Widget for any existing Call Centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Reverse?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 16:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-reverse/</guid>
      <description>Make Video calls from your Contact Center to Web Browsers or Mobile Devices. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Outbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT Forward?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split-forward/</guid>
      <description>Receive Video calls from Web Browsers or Mobile Devices in your Contact Center. Video Gateways (WebRTC) developed by Interactive Powers include a special SPLIT module which enable to separate and synchronize media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
The Video Channel (Inbound) for existing Call Centers without worries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Merge of IVR and RTC into the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 00:18:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/the-merge-ivr-rtc-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Contact Center: Artificial Inteligence and Omnichannel strategies will require to upgrade and rethink all your IVR and RTC technology or services. At Interactive Powers, when we launched our first products, we had always considered the Contact Center as a primary technology platform that requires to connect many and new channels to become a Multi-channel system or much better ever an Omnichannel system. In the early stage of the Digital Transformation, we couldn’t imagine our main business product lines Smart IVR and Video RTC to become so close that they are now just part of a whole strategic approach for any Contact Center evolution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Browser to SIP Calling?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-rtmp-to-sip-calling/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration How can you call a Desk Phone from any Web Browser? Our both Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) can convert web browser media streams (video - audio - data) to SIP from WebRTC or RTMP peers communications. This interesting feature allows to connect easily web services to existing VoIP telephony channels of your IVR or PBX. We can consider all of this approach like a direct calling webphone or like a WebRTC-DDI or RTMP-DDI in a SIP trunk from an operator service configuration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SPLIT?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-split/</guid>
      <description>All Video Gateways (WebRTC | RTMP) developed by IVRPowers include a special plugin which allows separate the media streams (video - audio - data) for any communication between users and agents. This development is based on SIP and WebRTC | RTMP peers communications for the integration of voice, video and data in Contact Centers.
How does SPLIT work? The Audio-Video SPLIT mode works as following:
A Videocall is initiated by a customer endpoint and comes into the Video Gateway.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updating the Inbound Phone Channel</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/updating-inbound-phone-channel/</guid>
      <description>Most Call Centers are only managing standard inbound phone calls with the addition of &amp;ldquo;Click-to-call&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Call-me-back&amp;rdquo; buttons. It&amp;rsquo;s a very interesting &amp;ldquo;work around&amp;rdquo; option but it&amp;rsquo;s not enough. More and more users don&amp;rsquo;t like to make a phone call when they are browsing the net.
Users just want to keep on the same channel for many reasons:
they don&amp;rsquo;t want to unveils their phone number… they don&amp;rsquo;t know if one agent will be available now or better later… they don&amp;rsquo;t want to leave their web session context&amp;hellip; they may have bad cellular coverage conditions to make a mobile call&amp;hellip; they may be traveling outside their country under expensive roaming conditions… they may not be able to explain properly their current webpage context… That&amp;rsquo;s a lot of reasons to make any inbound phone service fail?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
