<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phone on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/phone/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phone on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/phone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Voice Channel Automation and Its Limits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voice-channel-automation-and-its-limits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/voice-channel-automation-and-its-limits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The Machine as Efficient Filter, the Human as High-Value Connection Next-generation voicebots have achieved quality almost indistinguishable from human voice in guided dialogues, significantly reducing operational costs compared to the average agent in Europe and Latin America. The financial equation drives massive automation of the traditional phone channel.
However, when interaction requires handling complex emotional ambiguity, delicate negotiation, or trust recovery, AI reaches its limit. Attempting to &amp;ldquo;deceive&amp;rdquo; the customer by passing the bot off as human generates frustration and loss of credibility as soon as limitations are detected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phone Number Obsolescence: The Shift to Web Calling</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/phone-number-obsolescence-the-shift-to-web-calling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2023 15:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/phone-number-obsolescence-the-shift-to-web-calling/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers Communication has evolved rapidly over the past few decades, and one of the most notable changes has been the shift from traditional phone numbers to web calling methods. This evolution has changed the way we connect with each other and has provided new avenues for businesses to communicate with customers. In this blog post, we’ll explore the evolution of phone numbers to web calling methods and how they have impacted communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Children 6-15: Proportion of time spent communicating (Phone Calls 2%)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-phone-calls-trends/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Children 6-15 years old only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. Last survey from Ofcoms,the UK&amp;rsquo;s communications regulator shows: Chidren 6-15 years old, in average of a week with any device and from any location in UK, only spent 2% of their communicating time with phone calls. That&amp;rsquo;s not really a suprise, if you know some children of this age in a country like UK or any other one&amp;hellip; but think about what will be the real-time communication market in the next 10 years under this generation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
