<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>smartivr on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/smartivr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in smartivr on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:00:26 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/smartivr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Suite 2024 Updates</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/suite-2024-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 20:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/suite-2024-updates/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Getting started&amp;hellip; We&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to announce the latest enhancements and advancements across our suite of platforms and solutions for the 2024 roadmap. Here&amp;rsquo;s a summary of what&amp;rsquo;s our evolution and changes:
New Roadmap 2024 Video RTC (Real-Time Communications) v5.x Our 5th generation flagship platform of Video RTC continues to deliver unparalleled stability, ensuring smoother and more reliable communication experiences than ever before.
Video REC (Video Call Recording) v1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR: System Requirements</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/smart-ivr-system-requirements/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are the recommended Servers? Operating System Requirements Smart IVR platforms are designed to run over a Linux CentOS 7 x86_64 distribution. Please make a minimal Linux Debian installation from Internet, USB or CD / DVD. To download the Linux distribution installation iso file go to: https://www.centos.org
Requirement Description Distribution Linux CentOS 7 Linux Kernel x86_64 Cloud Ready AWS, Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure Installer Minimal Install Port / Channel Definition A port or channel is an aggregation of multiple software communication interfaces that creates a logical interface in a IVR service.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Help Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 15:00:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/help-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Getting started&amp;hellip; Help Center is only available for Customers and Partners that are deploying or running our platforms, if you are not registred please contact our Sales Team to get all information and partnerships.
Register and Login at: https://support.ivrpowers.com
Service Desk Portals:
Smart IVR Video RTC Cloud Hosting Solutions Get support with our team in a single place Channels available:
Email Web Portal, when logged in at: https://support.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
