<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Business on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Business on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Tester</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Add a Four Steps Tester for your Video RTC services to improve Customer Experience and QoS. Most users are not aware about their communications and hardware conditions to make video calls over an Internet access. If you don&amp;rsquo;t take care about this, some of them will be disappointed of been rejected by technical issues. In order to improve your Customer Journey and Experience, add a simple testing four steps process in front of your Video RTC communications services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons Securely share and browse in your web pages simultaneously with your customers. The Cobrowsing humanises the online sales and support experience, enabling your contact center agents to interact with your customers and assist them via a shared browser. Thanks to the use of the Cobrowsing, the communication becomes far more natural, effective, and efficient, bringing the customer-agent exchange closer to that of an in-store, in-person interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Video calling has become a major part of the new normal. Simplicity and Speed too. Interactive Powers has released Virgo Business in response to the overwhelming increase virtual interactions sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. The simplest, accessible and secure video calling solution offers easy and immediate coverage of a telework process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the user experience of any business visit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>