<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>business on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/business/</link>
    <description>Recent content in business on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/business/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Flip Camera</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-flip-camera/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-flip-camera/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Switching all cameras during any video call for your services on Video RTC We are pleased to announce a new feature called Flip Camera ready for all Video RTC widgets that enables switch to next available camera inside your device. In case you’re using a smartphone or tablet, this feature switch from front to back camera. In desktop web browsers, this feature will change to the next camera until you make a complete loop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Background Blur</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-blackground-blur/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-blackground-blur/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Defocusing agents background without any plugin. We are pleased to announce Background Blur powered by JS inside your web browser for all Video RTC agents without any plugin or software installation. This new feature is now available for projects under special conditions according to your web browser performance and devices deployed in the agent side.
Unretouched Screenshots:
System Requirements. This feature do now require specific hardware and run real-time video processing on the top of WebRTC, we recommend to use it only on desktop web browsers with enough CPU/RAM.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Geolocation</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-geolocation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-geolocation/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Enable user geolocation detection for your business communications and video calls Knowing where your video callers location is a useful feature, that can help you provide a better support or customer service. For instance, you can show them results that are tailored to their location or display their location on the map or convert latitude/longitude to a street address.
What is IP geolocation? IP geolocation is the mapping of an IP address to the geographic location of the internet from the connected device.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo · Stats</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-stats/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Getting key analytics to follow Virgo Solution data usage: Emails, SMS, Calls&amp;hellip; Interactive Powers has released a new update for Virgo Business and Virgo Healthcare in response to the overwhelming increase virtual interactions sparked by the global pandemic. Now, administrators can check stats and export main account usage data.
Virgo Solutions are the simplest, accessible and secure scheduled video calling solution that offers easy and immediate coverage of a telework process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the user experience of any business visit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC · Tester</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Aug 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc-tester/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Add a Four Steps Tester for your Video RTC services to improve Customer Experience and QoS. Most users are not aware about their communications and hardware conditions to make video calls over an Internet access. If you don&amp;rsquo;t take care about this, some of them will be disappointed of been rejected by technical issues. In order to improve your Customer Journey and Experience, add a simple testing four steps process in front of your Video RTC communications services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Creative Commons Securely share and browse in your web pages simultaneously with your customers. The Cobrowsing humanises the online sales and support experience, enabling your contact center agents to interact with your customers and assist them via a shared browser. Thanks to the use of the Cobrowsing, the communication becomes far more natural, effective, and efficient, bringing the customer-agent exchange closer to that of an in-store, in-person interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virgo Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/virgo-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons Video calling has become a major part of the new normal. Simplicity and Speed too. Interactive Powers has released Virgo Business in response to the overwhelming increase virtual interactions sparked by the COVID-19 global pandemic. The simplest, accessible and secure video calling solution offers easy and immediate coverage of a telework process, including collaboration and virtual attention optimizing the user experience of any business visit.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
