<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Voicebot on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voicebot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Voicebot on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/voicebot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Connecting Phone Calls to DialogFlow</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/connecting-phone-calls-to-dialogflow/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons What are main questions about connecting a DialogFlow agent to a telephony system? It’s important to get some important differences between the Google Phone Gateway and our DialogFlow Gateway powered by a Smart IVR platform.
Can I get a Number (PSTN) from any country?  🟢 Phone Gateway = Yes, select a PSTN Number in the list of each available country. 🟢 DialogFlow Gateway = Yes, connect your own DDI Number or any IP PBX extensions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to connect DialogFlow to your PBX?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-connect-dialogflow-to-your-pbx/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Build a Voicebot IVR with DialogFlow for your existing PBX and telephony system. Continuing on our quest of better business communications, both old DTMF menus and speech direct dialog are outdated IVR options, we can replace them by the power of a DialogFlow advanced Conversational AI service.
Prerequisities 1- Text-to-Speech API account (TTS) You can connect any TTS according to your language and voice preferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to improve your PBX with Conversational AI?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way In The New Digital Age, standards commons PBX functions used by most companies are weighing down Customer Experience (CX) making tedious to contact their phone services or customer assistance.
 Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons  What most companies still doing…
 DTMF Menus. Most PBX use touch tone menus to select departments, services or key an extension. Of course, everybody may knows how to press a key, but it’s not really confortable to do this with hands free, driving or when you don’t get the right option…</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t forget to train your Voicebot</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Oct 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/voicebot-training/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Like any human performance, your AI powered system requires to be properly trained. Training is the most important thing to consider to make your Voicebot IVR smart enough when it goes in production. Many projects forgot to review continuously learning rules, intents and transactions logs.
When a Voicebot or conversational agent does not understand you, it is because, in reality, he does not have been properly trained.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videobots are coming…</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Nov 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/videobots-are-coming/</guid>
      <description>Video AI agents with an human like behaviour are closer than you may think… Today, Xinhua, China’s state-run press agency, has unveiled new “AI anchors” — digital composites created from footage of human hosts that read the news using synthesised voices.
The news anchor, based on the latest AI technology, has a male image with a voice, facial expressions and actions of a real person. &amp;ldquo;He&amp;rdquo; learns from live broadcasting videos by himself and can read texts as naturally as a human.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>