<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kiosks on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kiosks/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kiosks on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kiosks/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ubiquo Ubox: No Touch Kiosks &amp; Screens</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/ubiquo-ubox-kiosks-screens-no-touch/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Ubiquotechs - Interactive Powers Gesture controlled Kiosks &amp;amp; Screens with Video RTC to enable new customer experiences. MIAMI, July. 1, 2020 — Ubiquo Technologies the creators of UBOX and Interactive Powers the creators of Video RTC announce new phygital experiences joining gesture and video real-time communications. UBOX is also a marketplace of experiences where hardware and software developers, designers, artists and data scientists can collaborate in projects together from different parts of the world easily, thus providing end-to-end​ ​solutions to consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Real-Time Communications Endpoints</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/videortc-endpoints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 18:01:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/videortc-endpoints/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Real-Time communication technology represents a qualitative leap in any communication process. One of the most outstanding advantages is VideoRTC. But what platforms can we use to benefit from this innovative technology? Web browsers, mobile devices and interactive kiosks are the main endpoints from which to interact in real time.
Web Browsers. Browsers are still the most important terminals from which to access the Internet when it comes to everyday work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
