<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videochat on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videochat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videochat on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videochat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39;, it&#39;s a must have.</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Apr 2020 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longer-a-nice-to-have-it-is-a-must-have/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Now, It&amp;rsquo;s won’t be an option. It&amp;rsquo;s a question of business survival in post-COVID-19 society. Just one year ago, we had annouced that Video was no longer &amp;ldquo;a nice to have&amp;rdquo; for Call Centers, now it will change the entire world market permanently.
 Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications
 As you may read in the research analyts reports, Video was just representing no more than 8% or less of business communications according to &amp;ldquo;more optimistics&amp;rdquo; predictions published past year as usual&amp;hellip; Even, if video was much better than voice for any digital real time human interaction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is no longer a &#39;nice to have&#39; for Call Centers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-is-no-longuer-a-nice-to-have-for-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers It&amp;rsquo;s not Fashion, it&amp;rsquo;s a question of Evolution. Companies and brands that are not yet concidering a progresive transition of their phone channel to Real-Time Communications (RTC) within the next years for their customer care, sales or support will quickly become old fashioned and irrelevant for new consumers. The next customers generation is no longer accepting to downgrade their daily high speed interactions and expectations on advanced devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video calls are not an annoying feature for younger generations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2019 00:01:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/children-understand-video/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Children feel more confortable having video calls than phone calls. If you have the opportunity to check how children understand Live Communications, you will quickly realise that phone is absolutly not a priority for them. They will never ask you about using a phone number and never want to remember just what it is. This new generation is born under a full digital world&amp;rsquo;s devices with high speed Internet and they absolutly are not aware about using limited or poor interactions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Key Benefits of Interactive Kiosks</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 12:16:22 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/key-benefits-kiosk/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers WebRTC technology has disrupted traditional communications, but we have barely experienced its potential yet. One of the most relevant applications is going to take place at points of sale. Thanks to the latest breakthroughs in video technology, customer experience can be dramatically enhanced. Let’s see the main benefits of an Interactive Kiosk:
Immediate Real-Time Communications. Kiosks enable a personalized and immediate communication between an expert or a salesperson and a customer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gartner: 20 percent of Global Businesses will deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2017 10:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/gartner-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Pexels. Creative Commons By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest Global Businesses will implement Video Chat. Time is the new currency for your customers who are looking for painless and informed solutions to their issues. We are also starting, growing and running companies in an &amp;ldquo;attention economy,&amp;rdquo; which is defined by the view that human attention is a scarce commodity. By 2018, according to research from Gartner, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dimension Data: Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat for Customer Engagement</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/dimensiondata-trend/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons Nearly one-third of Contact Centers expect to deploy Video Chat to improve Customer Engagement According to a research from Dimension Data, nearly one-third of contact centers expect to deploy video chat for customer engagement. The research says that giving customers the additional option to remotely connect face-to-face, at moments that are important to them (and on their terms), can make their customer experience even more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Live Video Calling: The New Eye Witness for Insurance Companies</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 13:49:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/live-video-calling-insurance/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons The popularity of Live Video Calling is increasing quickly in the view of the fact that it can help to provide a better customer service and reduce costs. One of the most growing sectors in applying live video is insurance businesses.
Access to convenience. Customers expect to use the more convenient channel at every moment. Thanks to new technologies like WebRTC it is not necessary to make a prior appointment and move to a real office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Videochat Support Channel Recommendations</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 13:13:47 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/videochat-support/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Video Real-Time Communications (RTC) is increasingly becoming a popular support channel. According to report from Gartner, more than 100 of the 500 largest global businesses will introduce video-based chat by 2018. But bringing online chat to website is not enough. To obtain good results, it should also be implemented correctly.
Humanized Interactions. Self-service-tools are not always the best option. Customers can feel frustrated trying to reach a live agent or jumping from bot to bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>