<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Videochat on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videochat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Videochat on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/videochat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Millennials don&#39;t Phone Anymore!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 10:44:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/millennials-phone/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons A joke circulating on twitter said “The phone call is becoming the new hand written letter”. And it was right, because a paradigm shift has taken place. Recent surveys show that we are not primarily using our phone to make calls. Nowadays, we are more likely to contact family and friends via alternative means, like instant messaging services.
After a decade of growth, the amount of time we spent talking on our mobile phones went into reverse around 2012.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Your Next Doctor&#39;s Appointment will be Online</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 13:39:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/healthcare/next-doctor-appointment/</guid>
      <description>Telemedicine services are increasing year by year. The main reason is Real-time communications (RTC) technology is becoming a great way to connect doctors and medical facilities with patients. Through a video conference session the patient can show his swollen ankle, and on basis of that image, doctor can decide whether an appointment is advisable.
Telemedicine Telemedicine is not an answer to everything, but consumers see web-based or mobile application visits more convenient to get treated for minor ailments, such as allergy symptoms, coughs, flu or bug bites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Online Onboarding</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2017 13:13:32 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/financial/video-online-onboarding/</guid>
      <description>Video Online Onboarding allows anyone to open an account or become customer in just a few minutes and start banking, getting a service or insurance contract right away. This new approach uses an innovative procedure that verifies a customer’s identity through a selfie and a video call. Video Online Onboarding is combining Video ID to verify the authenticity of identity documents with facial recognition and Video RTC to have a video call with an agent to approve the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time to add a Webcall button to your Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 10:55:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/time-add-webcall-button-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Beyond improving quality of service QoS and call productivity, any Contact Center has to be ready for the next Internet evolution challenges. For any online business or ecommerce website, the most efficient way to contact a sale representative or get human support is a Web Real-Time Communication (WebRTC) with your agents but without leaving the web session, so you have to add a one-click button located near to the product or service they are selecting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Key Benefits of Live Video Chat</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 10:51:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/3-key-benefits-video-chat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Currently, bots can solve a small proportion of customers’ needs. However, even if a bot has been trained to understand complicated statements and is able to answer in an intelligent and sophisticated manner, there are cases when customers need to speak with a live agent. Bots should not alienate nor irritate your customers. This is the point when WebRTC technology plays its role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>