<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:58:21 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>It&#39;s time for companies to use Web and Mobile RTC Applications</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 12:58:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article6/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone bills with voice call minutes have been reduced or even disappeared both at home and in businesses. We communicate at work writing emails, tweets, posts, notifying by Skype, Google Hangout, LinkedIn or Facebook, and get in touch with our friends via Whatsapp or Snapchat, sharing multimedia content in real time. Phone calls are no longer a relevant channel in our personal communications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Things you have to know about WebRTC on Apple Safari 11</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-3-things-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/webrtc-3-things-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration After years, Apple has officially released a new version of Safari with support for WebRTC!
These are the three essential things to know:
Interoperability with other web browsers. Basics work fine. If you run a simple peer-to-peer call between any of the 4 browsers, you’ll get a call going. Voice and video work over the lowest common denominator Opus+H.264 in Safari. Although Opus+VP8 will be also a possibility in the future, it is not right now with the current release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Real-Time Communications the Phone won&#39;t be the King anymore</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2017 10:45:02 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article5/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Telephone dominated customer attention services of companies over any other channel, since its popularization during the first half of the twentieth century. The invention of the mobile phone did not particularly harm its leadership, as far as at first it was simply mobile phone handsets. Today, the mobile phone is a widespread device that has supplanted the use of fixed terminals.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WebRTC on Safari11 for MacOS and iOS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:09:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/webrtc-safari11/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration At past WWDC 2017 in San Jose, California, Apple announced that it will include support for WebRTC in Safari 11 and WebKit for all iOS 11 and MacOS Sierra devices. Until now, 80% of all browsers supported WebRTC including Firefox and Chrome. Regarding Safari it grows to 95%. Apple’s announcement gives companies that use WebRTC applications and tools, such as our VideoRTC solutions, a broader range for choice and flexibility over which browser their rich multimedia communications services are delivered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Transformation: Doors of Opportunity for Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 13:02:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article4/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All interactions cannot be managed by bots, since users, when facing with certain problems, need to contact a real agent. If consumer is not allowed to communicate with a person, it leads to frustration and the relation client-company is seriously damaged. At this point, video offers contact centers the possibility of developing a very differential customer experience management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video is Transforming Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 12:04:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article3/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
Companies must understand that the processes of digital transformation driven by society are inevitable. In the last years, the improvement of customer support services accelerates the pace of adaptation to digital processes. The reason is the good results obtained by companies that have already integrated advanced digital tools, based, for instance, on WebRTC technology for real-time communication via the web or mobile applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Businesses need to Face Digital Challenges</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 11:30:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article2/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
The spread of new communication behaviour among users is pushing companies to modify their contact channels with customers. At Interactive Powers we observe that adapting to an increasingly digitized market poses new challenges. However, it also opens one door of opportunity for companies to improve and differentiate themselves.
From our offices in Spain and the United States, we provide solutions that facilitate secure and real-time multimedia interactions over the Internet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Digital Revolution in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 12:00:08 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/linkedin-article1/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow me on Linkedin
All of us, as consumers, are becoming increasingly familiar with the use of new channels. We must also take into account that the first generation of digital natives is entering into the market. However, phone continues to be the most widely used channel in customer service and voice over IP technology. This situation is specially extended in the Spanish business landscape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>