<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>contactcenter on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/contactcenter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in contactcenter on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/categories/contactcenter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HD Quality / Video Recording</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 18:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/hd-quality-video-recording/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires scalable HD quality and powerful video recording for any size professional service.  No one wants laggy audio or pixelated video quality in a meeting, especially when you&amp;rsquo;re meeting with clients or prospects. Interactive Powers comes with crystal-clear HD video and the most advanced video recording storage system for any size Video Call / Contact Centers deployment.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Centric / Unified Communications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 17:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-centric-unified-communications/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires powerful real-time communications where Video is a top priority integrated channel.  Beyond video calls, what if your team also communicates through phone calls and text chat? Interactive Powers lets you consolidate all those tools into one. Talk, message, and meet all from one convenient channel. That makes for fewer software to pay for and manage and less time wasted on context-switching for all your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robust Security Setting</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 16:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/robust-security-setting/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC Privacy and Security are key mandatory questions for your business and customers.  Keep your meetings secure with strong 256-bit encrypted real-time communications and session tokenization. Interactive Powers&#39; settings allow the host to mute participants, process biometrics API, lock file sharing, limit screen sharing, encode parameters and much more.
 Discover all renewed Video RTC 5.0 features to get the best Video CC experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Control / Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 15:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-control-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC requires at least the same transactional call functions as Voice to ensure agents performance.  In our agent side, all the call controls you need are easily in reach. Adjust your call settings, start a screen share, mute and unmute yourself, or start and pause yourself or video recording. It&amp;rsquo;s all in a clean, video first, easy-to-use interface that lays out all these options for you right on the screen and our flap button.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dual Screen Sharing / CoBrowsing</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 14:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/dual-screen-sharing-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Video CC without advanced web collaborative tools, is like a Call / Contact Center without call management.  Need to zoom in on a design mockup or run through a contract approval? Interactive Powers dual screen sharing feature lets double share contents from agent and user at the same time. By the way, you choose between sharing a specific window or tab or your whole desktop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Responsive based Video Calls</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 13:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/web-responsive-based-video-calls/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers No Apps, No Downloads, No Register is a must be, not an option for your Video CC deployment.  Some video conferencing software will make you download the desktop or mobile app to host and join video calls. But Interactive Powers solutions are browser-based, which means it won’t force you or your clients to download an app. Host and join meetings from a web browser using your computer or mobile device, and get it all running with No Apps, No Downloads, No Register.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call / Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 12:00:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Interactive Powers Delivering real human interactions and unified collaboration in your Digital Space.  Need to meet face-to-face virtually your clients? Start managing unlimited transactional video calls for your team. It isn&amp;rsquo;t always practical to have every single meeting in person. Even if there are lots of video meeting apps that are designed more for hangouts with colleagues and chatting with loved ones. Any Call / Contact Center should be turned into a Video CC to improve its inbound/outbound processes and performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowered Omnichannel with Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/empowered-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Traditional Omnichannel is not enough to provide a complete Digital Experience.  Video RTC solutions provide many integrations to enable an Empowered Omnichannel over your existing channels and services keeping your existing Contact Center platform. Video RTC is ready to be connect to any CC handling a SIP connectivity interface that mean most of on premise or cloud based products.
Traditional Omnichannel Traditional Omnichannel use to include following features:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call Transferring Interoperability</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-call-transferring-interoperability-for-contact-centers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: FreePik. Creative Commons Interoperability becomes the key requirement: a seamless video transfer integration between all software contact center solutions.  Contact centers, like the rest of the communications industry, are experiencing a rapidly changing landscape. These changes in technology are spurring changes in human behaviors and customer expectations. The post-COVID19 situation is making the Customer Experience (CX) a key factor in the consumer decision-making process.
It’s no longer a world of call centers, today’s contact center has to be prepared to handle omnichannel communications: video calls, calls, emails, online chat, and text messages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding Video RTC to your existing Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2018 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/interoperability-contact-center/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Whatever your contact center is, we can make it interoperable with videocalls and advanced online interactions.  Many companies fear that the integration of video in their contact centers will involve a large investment of human and economic resources. Because companies think they will be forced to change the entire contact center solution, they may ignore video integration and, therefore, the opportunity to significantly improve their services and customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Integration in the Contact Center</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2017 10:09:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/video-integration/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons The Video Channel is the next level Customer Experience frontier for existing Contact Centers  Video is not a separate solution from the services that contact centers have been providing until now and it is not a substitute for voice calls. The key to the Video in Real-time communications lies in the possibility of offering a new channel, whose use is progressively increasing in customer care services for most industries.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does VideoRTC fit in my Contact Center?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2017 12:36:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/contact-center-videortc/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pexels. Creative Commons Call Centers have to upgrade their services to the next level implementing new advanced interactions  The ever-growing digital world can give new opportunities for existing contact centers to provide a superior customer experience. Nowadays new technologies drive clients to ask for multiple options when looking for support. It is here where VideoRTC can help your contact center to enhance its services.
Save time providing the right channel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IVR plays a Key Role for an Effective Omnichannel Strategy</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2017 12:29:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/contactcenter/ivr-role-omnichannel/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Customer experience is the current battleground for differentiation. In order to stay relevant and even survive in an increasingly competitive market, contact centers must think different and deploy more advanced communication solutions. The primary path for improving customer experience is enhancing time response and quality of service. Customers expect companies to resolve issues easily and quickly and there is a lot to lose in a disappointing customer expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
