<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cloud on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cloud/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Cloud on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on &amp;ldquo;Communication Platform as a Service&amp;rdquo; or CPaaS at last year 2018 VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
CPaaS is the new cloud&amp;rsquo;s Game Changer The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Understanding Cloud Services: IaaS, PaaS, SaaS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/understanding-cloud-hosting-iaas-paas-saas/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What are the differences between IaaS, SaaS, and PaaS, the three main Cloud Computing models? IaaS, PaaS, SaaS are three Cloud computing models popular in the market. Depending upon the requirement a company can opt for any of the three models. Here we explain IaaS, PaaS, SaaS model in the best possible way so that anyone can understand and differential among them.
What is IaaS?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is a Communications Platform as a Service Company</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/interactive-powers-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The future of communications is driven by the cloud. Interactive Powers was created to help companies embed voice and video communication into the software applications and web applications that are part of their workflow and how they do business with the same communication options and convenience that mobile devices provide for their customers and employees in their person lives. With Interactive Powers, communication becomes more immediate and contextual resulting in better business outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Premise vs Cloud</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2018 22:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/on-premise-vs-cloud/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash Creative Commons. There is many reasons to consider replacing an on-premises infrastructure with a cloud-based video real-time communication platform as a service. If your communication infrastructure don’t supports modern video communications or faces end-of-life, you need to plan your migration strategy now to avoid pitfalls down the road. Also consider the seasonality of your business and the best time to be upgraded. For reference, on-premises solutions typically require more time to procure, generally weeks or months.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen Sharing or Co-Browsing?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Aug 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/screensharing-or-cobrowsing/</guid>
      <description>Discover Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing advantages, the secure new ‘no download’ complementary interactions improving phone calls for onboarding, sales and support. Screen Sharing and Co-Browsing (or Collaborative Browsing) are a relatively new technologies for Call Centers propelled by a Cloud evolution. However, customer experience professionals seem to think that CoBrowsing and Screen Sharing are one and the same when in reality, they’re not. So what is the difference between these two features and how does adapting your VideoRTC solution improve the overall customer experience?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EU Store · Europe CPaaS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/eu-store-europe-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new EU Store - Europe CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Europe and others countries.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Store · America CPaaS</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jun 2018 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/us-store-america-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay, Creative Commons We have very exciting news for you! Now, it&amp;rsquo;s time for a new change, to work with our IVR and RTC cloud hosting services even better than ever. Our company is pleased to announce our new US Store - America CPaaS ecommerce portal offering Communications Platform as a Service (CPaaS | SaaS) for all regions in Canada, USA and South America.
 Interactive Voice Response: VoiceXML IVR Video Gateways: Video RTC Turnkey Solutions: Web Dialer, Video SPLIT, Remote Viewer Professional Services Support Services  Now you can get more with:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is CPaaS?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-cpaas/</guid>
      <description>Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) Communication Platform as a Service (CPaaS) is a form of cloud computing that is utilized to deliver communication applications like IVR or RTC to users over the internet. But, unlike SaaS which delivers specific apps and programs, Communication Platform as a Service is a bit closer related to IaaS. So, while IaaS is delivering the infrastructure, like servers and management tools, CPaaS is what delivers the entire communication platform for users to build and develop their own applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is SaaS?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 01:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-saas/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Software as a Service (SaaS) Software as a Service (SaaS) directly refers to any software that your business is using just about everyday. SaaS is of course a form of cloud computing, which allows for increase flexibility by relying on a third-party vendor to host and maintain the service — in this case, that service is that software. Since the software is hosted by a cloud provider, your business does not need to install and run applications on their own computers, or host their own servers in expensive data centers, yet still gains access to these powerful tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Services Revolution</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/cloud-apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Nov 2017 12:19:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/cloud-apis/</guid>
      <description>Photo Source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Recent promotion of Cloud API services by the dominant Internet service providers can lead to a substantial change in the use of legacy systems and technologies. Cloud-based services, which enable high-value-added interactions with voice, natural language, artificial intelligence, etc., will make it possible to leave existing solutions behind.
More Efficient and Cost-Saving. Google, Amazon, Apple and Microsoft are starting to provide amazing cloud-based services to enterprises, which were just available to developers until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 Reasons to embrace Cloud Hosting</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Sep 2017 12:50:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/cloud-hosting-ivr-rtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons. Upgrade your business communications to the Cloud to deliver more value with less costs Computing based on the internet is booming business. The global cloud communication market is projected to reach $4.45 by 2021. Why are more and more companies turning to the cloud for their business communications needs?
Communications solutions at a lower cost. Cloud computing is a cost saver since it can reduce or even eliminate the need for a company to buy an expensive hardware and software.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>