<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Custexp on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/custexp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Custexp on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/custexp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Time is Money on Customer Experience</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 12:04:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/time-is-money/</guid>
      <description>Customer expectations are growing every day and two of the key factors are time and effort. Customers can be frustrated if they need to spend a lot of time resolving an issue or jumping hoops to do it. They hate being transferred and feel tired of repeating themselves. Difficult or high effort experiences make the customer feel exhausted and are the main cause of disloyalty.
Companies should take into consideration that the impact of a bad experience is huge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Centers should Know Video is Here to Stay</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 16:15:59 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/trends/video-call-centers/</guid>
      <description>Video in Real-Time Communication (RTC) is changing the image of the customer service industry. The success of pioneers who provide video chat customer service marked the dawning of a new era, because offering a good customer service is a key part for any business success.
Humanifying Customer Care But despite the good results, video has not been widely adopted in contact centers. Maybe it’s time for the industry to consider how the use of video can enhance the effectiveness of customer services and solve some of the big issues of contact centers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Age of the Customer in Contact Centers</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 14:08:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/age-of-consumer/</guid>
      <description>Surveys say customers highly value great customer experiences. But companies should take into account that customer expectations are rising. A shift is taking place. The explosion of digital and technological innovations is having a profound impact on Customer Empowerment. Therefore, the need for a great Customer Experience is higher than ever.
Many companies are worried when customer satisfaction with Contact Centers declines. And they are right, Contact Centers are directly responsible for maintaining the company’s image.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Approaches on Ecommerce Customer Service</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 12:46:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/new-approaches-ecommerce-customer-service/</guid>
      <description>Exceptional customer service is critical in e-commerce. Surveys show that customer experience highly affect purchases. 70% of buying experiences are based on how the customers feel they are being treated. The impact is so high that 91% of unhappy customers will not willingly do business with the company again.
Feedback and Personalization. Customers appreciate a good service, which is an essential part of ecommerce businesses. Customers who do not get the service they would prefer can just move onto to another store.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon&#39;s Mayday Button. The Road to the Future</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 10:42:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/support/amazon-mayday-button/</guid>
      <description>Five years ago, Amazon launched the Mayday button to its line of Kindle Fire tablets. It provides on-device tech support all day, every day. Just by tapping the Mayday button the Kindle user is put in direct contact with an Amazon technician.
In less than six months, the feature became the most popular way for Kindle customers to contact Amazon’s customer service. What are the ingredients for success?
First of all, it gives customers the option of reaching out to a real person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is Video Chat a good Strategy for my Business?</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 13:49:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-chat-good-strategy-business/</guid>
      <description>More than ever businesses need to pay attention to customer experience and provide them with quality support. In addition to phone, email and self-service, Live Communications are an excellent tool to improve customer satisfaction. Video Chat makes available an efficient and immediate support. And it is a cost-saving option to companies that provide personalized services.
Some Benefits of a Video Chat are:
Seeing is believing. Video chat allows to show the product in real time for the customer while talking to an agent or sales rep.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>