<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>callcenters on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/callcenters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in callcenters on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/callcenters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Benefits</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-benefits/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Omnichannel experience. Omnichanneling opens the opportunity for call centers to take a significant step in improving customer services and surpassing clients’ growing expectations. It is one of the key for businesses to implement an integral strategy. Clients perceive the advantages as they can engage when needed and through the most convenient channel: chat, phone call, self-service or video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Centers · Business Cases</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters-cases/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers By 2018, more than 100 out of the 500 largest global businesses will have implemented video chat Customer Service. VideoRTC is seamlessly integrated into your previous infrastructure, adding, for instance, a universal button that makes it easier for clients to contact the customer service.
Technical Support. Thanks to video chat, co-browsing and screen share functionalities agents can walk the customer through remote control functions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call Center · Industry</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/industries/industries-callcenters/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Shutterstock licensed to Interactive Powers 90% of companies name improving customer experience as a strategic focus Customers are moving more and more online and businesses are forced to provide them with new ways for assistance and support. Contact centers face the challenge of offering personalized services and meeting customer expectations. Video and Voice Real-Time communications over the Internet are the most efficient way to provide support. Thanks to them, clients can always have available services, including the possibility to interact with an agent, which improves customer experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
