<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>miami on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/miami/</link>
    <description>Recent content in miami on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/miami/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2025</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2025/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next 11 &amp;amp; 12 February at ITEXPO 2025 event, Fort Lauderdale, Florida Interactive Powers will be attending IT-EXPO 2025 on February 11–12 in Fort Lauderdale, Florida. We&amp;rsquo;re excited to connect with industry leaders and partners while exploring new technologies and telecom solutions.
Overview of IT-EXPO 2025 IT-EXPO 2025 is a premier technology industry event showcasing experts and emerging trends. Interactive Powers is thrilled to participate in this dynamic gathering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2023</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2023/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next 15th February at next ITEXPO 2023 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida Interactive Powers will be attending the IT-EXPO 2023 event February 15 at Fort Lauderdale / Florida. We&amp;rsquo;re excited to connect with other industry leaders, partners, learn about new technologies and telecom solutions.
Overview of IT-EXPO 2023 IT-EXPO 2023 is a top event for the technology industry, featuring experts and emerging trends. Interactive Powers is thrilled to join this exciting event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers at next eMerge Americas 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us next days 30th - 31h March at eMerge Americas event at Miami Beach, Florida For the first time, Interactive Powers (ivrpowers.com) will be attending eMerge Americas, March 30 – 31, 2019 in Miami Beach - Convention Center. eMerge Americas is the premier technology event connecting the Americas. eMerge Americas is not just an event- it’s an ecosystem that is transforming Miami into the Tech Hub of the Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next days 11th - 14th February at next ITEXPO 2020 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida If you are attending ITEXPO and would like to discuss how to get enhance your business and opportunities with Cloud Communications for Conversational IVR, WebRTC gateways and CPaaS. Let&amp;rsquo;s set up some time to sit down and discover how we are helping all our partners with our Video RTC and Smart IVR solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
