<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ivrpowers on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivrpowers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ivrpowers on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/ivrpowers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to our New Blog!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-blog/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels. Creative Commons Our Corporate Blog is build with Hugo and will give us a unique opportunity to better share news, updates and technology content, while also offering a place for us to interact with all our community. If you’re wondering what you can expect from the content you find on our blog, and how the information here differs from the information you may find on our website, read on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Brand &amp; Media Kit</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2020 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/interactive-powers-brand-media-kit/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers The Interactive Powers brand is an expression of our team, culture and the solutions we create. To tell our story and represent our brand, here are our brand assets. We’d like to keep our brand consistent. If you have questions about how to use the Interactive Powers brand correctly, reach out to us.
Our Story Interactive Powers provides Smart IVR and Video RTC platforms to reimagine enterprise customer service to deliver standout experiences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Interactive Powers</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/about-interactive-powers/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers develops technology that helps your organization connect, communicate and engage with your customers, employees and stakeholders. Contact with us to find out more about how we can help you achieve your business communication goals.
Interactive Powers delivers communication platforms that enables advanced real-time interactions over public or private networks. We allow to deploy secure channels with unified voice, video, live chat and screen sharing capabilities for web, apps, and kiosk-based customer engagement to sale or support faster than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2023</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2023/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next 15th February at next ITEXPO 2023 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida Interactive Powers will be attending the IT-EXPO 2023 event February 15 at Fort Lauderdale / Florida. We&amp;rsquo;re excited to connect with other industry leaders, partners, learn about new technologies and telecom solutions.
Overview of IT-EXPO 2023 IT-EXPO 2023 is a top event for the technology industry, featuring experts and emerging trends. Interactive Powers is thrilled to join this exciting event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.14.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.14.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.14.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.14.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.14.0:
### [1.14.0] - 2023-01-25 ​ ### Added ​ - Added getUserfieldById method to the DB custom module ​ ### Changed ​ - Disabled Google Translate from the platform - Upgraded videortc font to release v1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2022/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Wishing you a wonderful holiday season. We are grateful for the opportunity to collaborate and celebrate with our community. We hope that you are able to cherish these holidays and enjoy a truly remarkable gift - the gift of togetherness. With our partners and clients, we venture into a new year filled with opportunity.
Merry Christmas 2022 and hope you to your loved ones.
God bless you all!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.7</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.7.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.7.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.7.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.7:
## [2.7.0] - 03-11-2022 ### Added - Parameter start-input-timers to res-speech-unimrcp to disable the default timers initialization in the RECOGNIZE - Channel variable (VOICEDETECTED_TIMEOUT) to select a different timeout to allow speech inputs longer than 10s ### Fixed - A bug during the collection of the next audio sample during the NLU phase Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.13.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.13.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.13.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.13.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.13.0:
### [1.12.0] - 2022-05-12 ​ ### Added ​ - Target selection (iframe/tab) for the queue triggers - Home page customization ​ ### [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.6.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Mar 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.6.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.6.1:
## [2.6.1] - 28-03-2022 ### Fixed - Added a safeguard to the restoring of the readformat of the channel for the cases where it is not present Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.6</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Mar 2022 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.6.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.6.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.6:
## [2.6.0] - 23-03-2022 ### Added - Hability to record the user speech during an ASR session ### Fixed - Applied patch to the speech_create Asterisk function to prevent crashes after lots of ASR sessions Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v5.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-5.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-5.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v5.0.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 5.0.0:
## [5.0.0] - 2022-01-12 ### Added - New configuration params to the Tester usecase: autoStart, autoTroubleshoot and showRedirectBtnOnlyIfTestOk - Added a way for the Tester to know which checks are necessary to display the Next button - Advice feature to the SPLIT Agent usecase - Possibility in the Webclient to differentiate when a call in queue or on hold - Possibility to download chat history from the SPLIT Agent usecase - Flip Camera action on both the Videocall and RemoteViewer usecases - Possibility to configure webpage title and favicon by theme - Possibility to setup RemoteViewer without ScreenSharing or Audio - Option to configure an endpoint to send snapshots via URL request from the SplitAgent - Added a way to apply different CSS rules depending on the theme name - Webclient can now be configured in escalating mode ### Changed - OS System required has gone up to Debian 11 - New structure of the web resources after a build - Added camera check before starting SplitAgent plus moved auto recording trigger from onAcceptedVideo to onJoined event ### Updated - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2022!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2022/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, inspiration and happiness be yours throughout New Year 2022! Hard work, creativity, and commitment to excellence has been invaluable to us this 2021. As we step into another year, I wish you confidence and courage to accept new challenges and work further towards your goals!
Happy New Year! Wishing all the best to you and your family as we head into 2022! 🍾 🥂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 23:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Wishing you a wonderful holiday season. The year 2021 has also been a year of growth for Interactive Powers and impresive video adoption, in many industries. We are proud enabling businesses to stay connected to their customers growing and improving their business communication services.
From all our team at Interactive Powers, we want to express sincere gratitude for our amazing clients, partners, and all people who give us meaning and drive us forward every day.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.5</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.5.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.5:
## [2.5.0] - 29-11-2021 ### Added - Support for recording the NLU user voice and retrieve its contents - Max duration option for the NLU interaction - PJSIP support ### Changed - Improved the NLU with Google for phrases where the user takes breaks between words - Improved NLU session cleanup - Improved the &amp;#34;voicexml hangup session&amp;#34; Asterisk command - Improved the output of the &amp;#34;voicexml show nlu&amp;#34; Asterisk command - Improved the behavior of the Asterisk module for the cases where the connection with the message queue is lost during a long time ### Fixed - The indexing of the output for the command &amp;#34;voicexml show statistics&amp;#34; Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplah, Creative Commons Celebrate your blessings and cherish the memories that you&amp;rsquo;ve shared, with happiness and cheer. Interactive Powers wants to give special thanks to every customer and business for all the support you have given us through the years!
We wish every one a wonderful and happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🎉
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.11.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.11.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.11.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.11.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.11.0:
## [1.5.0] - 2021-01-28 ​ ### Added ​ - Auto close functionality for the Queue triggers to select if they must be closed at call end or not - Administration/Supervision message to the agents - Custom PHP modules to extend platform functionalities ​ ## [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.4</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.4.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.4:
## [2.4.0] - 04-03-2021 ### Added - Added res_srtp Asterisk module to support RTP over SSL - Added &amp;lt;context&amp;gt; support for the &amp;lt;nlu&amp;gt; recognition ### Changed - General internal updates to the NLU logic ### Fixed - Fixed a couple of scenarios where the NLU result was not properly detected - Properly cleaned the CompletionQueue of the GRPC NLU Google session by performing the needed tasks explicitly- Memory leak on the interpreter engine Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.4.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.4.0:
## [3.4.0] - 2021-02-04 ### Added - Added a new event `onReadyLocalStream` on the Videoroom module - Added video support in the SIP module - Added `replaceVideo` action for SPLIT modules - Added `fwvga` resolution for SPLIT modules ### Changed - Aligned to the new VideoGateway `v4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Feb 2021 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.3.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.3.0:
## [4.3.0] - 2021-02-04 ### Added - Video feature in the Remote Viewer usecase - Parameter to set the bitrate when screensharing in the SPLIT usecases - Possibility to mute/unmute audio when using the RemoteViewer - Autoconnect feature in the RemoteViewer - Added a new usecase: SIPClient - Possibility to configure a shortener URL to the RemoteViewer - Possibility to start a RemoteViewer interaction without audio - Recording prefix parameter on the SPLIT Agent - Possibility to mute/unmute the local video automatically when screensharing - Added urlClose param on the SPLIT Agent usecase - File sharing as action on the Webclient - Possibility to customize the Max.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Empowered Chatbot!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/empowered-chatbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 09:42:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/empowered-chatbot/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Integrating Chatbot on our websites for more comprehensive way to grab visitors&amp;rsquo; interactions. Our Chatbot is a software-programmed, conversational virtual agent which is able to understand human text/speech inputs and 24/7 respond back with a meaningful answer, in the most natural (read human) way possible. It includes many smart integrations to enable a Phone Call Transfer or Video Call to a real agent.
Our Chatbot speaks in several languages according to our both portals:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy New Year 2021!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-new-year-2021/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, inspiration and happiness be yours throughout New Year 2021! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our clients, partners, employees, providers, and friends for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.
We gratefully want to wish you a better New Year 2021! 🍾 🥂</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Sending our best wishes to you and yours. The year 2020 has been a strange, hard and challenging year for everyone, but one that has forever cemented the importance of digital connection in our personal and business lives when safety or social distancing is required. It has also been a year of growth for Interactive Powers and video adoption, in general. We are proud of the part we are playing in enabling businesses to stay connected to their customers growing and elevating their services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.4.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.4.2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.4.2/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.4.2 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.4.2:
## [1.1.1] - 2020-10-28 ​ ### Fixed ​ - Last status is only checked and rendered for SIP users ​ ## [1.1.2] - 2020-10-28 ​ ### Fixed ​ - The report directory creation is now done with the proper mode and mask ​ ## [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you Miami-Dade County!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-you-miami-dade/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Very honoured to have been presented with the key of Miami by Miami-Dade Beacon Council &amp;amp; Mayor Carlos Gimenez. A trully wonderful and welcoming city.
Es un gran honor que Miami-Dade Beacon Council y el alcalde Carlos Giménez nos hayan entregado la llave de Miami. Una ciudad verdaderamente maravillosa y acogedora.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Thanksgiving!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Nov 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-thanksgiving-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik, Creative Commons Celebrate your blessings and cherish the memories that you&amp;rsquo;ve shared, with happiness and cheer. Interactive Powers wants to give special thanks to every customer and business for all the support you have given us through the years!
We wish every one a wonderful and happy Thanksgiving! 🦃🎉
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2020/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web ACD v1.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-web-acd-1.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Web ACD v1.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.1.0:
## [1.0.0] - 2020-10-14 ​ ### First release ​ ## [1.0.1] - 2020-10-15 ​ ### Fixed ​ - Normalized the CallerID of the user to remove accents to avoid crashes on calls ​ ## [1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Aug 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a specific security fix for data channel recommendations. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.2.1:
## [4.2.1] - 2020-08-13 ### Fixed - Fixed usrsctp vulnerability in SCTP module Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Apr 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2:
## [2.2.1] - 10-04-2020 ### Fixed - The resizing of the history of recordings files was sometimes crashing the Asterisk. ## [2.2.0] - 30-03-2020 ### Added - New VoiceXML element &amp;lt;nlu&amp;gt; with support for Google GRPC Speech API - New Asterisk command to display current nlu sessions ### Changed - Project build now with c++11 version - Accounts information is now only loaded &amp;amp; displayed if the license loaded successfully ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 13:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.3.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.0:
## [3.3.0] - 2020-03-25 ### Added - Added a new event `onSipMessage` on the SPLIT Client to receive SIP Messages - Added a new streamOption `resolution` in all modules where video is used - Added a new className `is-local-video` in all local video elements Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes specific improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.2.0:
## [4.2.0] - 2020-03-25 ### Added - Enabled ScreenSharing in the WebClient for Chrome and Opera browsers - Added possibility to send links via chat - Added SPLIT reverse feature in the SPLIT Agent usecase - Added possibility to configure the autoclose option in &amp;#39;forced&amp;#39; mode for SPLIT usecases - Added a new URL parameter called `from` on the Webclient and Escalating usecases - Added a new theme parameter `resolution` in all usecases where video is used ### Updated - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers at next eMerge Americas 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-emerge-americas-2020/</guid>
      <description>Join us next days 30th - 31h March at eMerge Americas event at Miami Beach, Florida For the first time, Interactive Powers (ivrpowers.com) will be attending eMerge Americas, March 30 – 31, 2019 in Miami Beach - Convention Center. eMerge Americas is the premier technology event connecting the Americas. eMerge Americas is not just an event- it’s an ecosystem that is transforming Miami into the Tech Hub of the Americas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.1.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 17:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.1.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix a vulnerability in usrsctplib that has already been fixed, so make sure you pull this latest release if you&amp;rsquo;re using data channels. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.1.1:
## [4.1.1] - 2020-02-28 ### Fixed - Fixed critical vulnerability in `usrsctp` library Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ITEXPO 2020</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itexpo-2020/</guid>
      <description>Meet us next days 11th - 14th February at next ITEXPO 2020 event at Fort Lauderdale, Florida If you are attending ITEXPO and would like to discuss how to get enhance your business and opportunities with Cloud Communications for Conversational IVR, WebRTC gateways and CPaaS. Let&amp;rsquo;s set up some time to sit down and discover how we are helping all our partners with our Video RTC and Smart IVR solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:20:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1:
## [2.1.0] - 03-02-2020 ### Added - Support for the &amp;lt;data&amp;gt; element - Added noinputtimeout for the &amp;lt;record&amp;gt; element ## [2.0.3] - 03-12-2019 ### Fixed - Removed unnecessary error message when making a TTS request through HTTP - Added verification check for the existance of a cached file before trying to access it to avoid error messages - Fixed the conversion from interpreter value to JSI double numbers on subdialog return ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.2.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.0:
## [3.2.0] - 2019-11-28 ### Added - Added new events on the Videocall and SPLIT modules to detect slow links with the remote video Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2019 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.1.0:
## [4.1.0] - 2019-10-21 ### Added - Added support for Safari &amp;gt;= 12.1 - Added possibility to choose the default quality of the Webclient through theme configuration - Added autocall, autoclose and hangup button in the Escalating - Added a new config param in the Webclient and Escalating usecases to redirect when a call ends (e.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.1.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.1.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.1.0:
## [3.1.0] - 2019-10-21 ### Added - Added device field in the Opaque ID object - Added support for Safari &amp;gt;= 12.1 ### Changed - Aligned to the new VideoGateway `v4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We are moving to a new Office!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/new-alcobendas-madrid-office-2019/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers We are excited to announce that Interactive Powers has moved to a new location in the fast growing city of Alcobendas in Madrid (Spain). We spent the previous three years in Madrid Downtown &amp;ndash; our old office served us well, and we made great memories there, but we couldn&amp;rsquo;t be more excited about our new modern space.
The new office is actually in Alcobendas business park, putting us in a really nice place for growing and looking toward the Madrid&amp;rsquo;s Skyline.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v4.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-4.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v4.0.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 4.0.0:
## [4.0.0] - 2019-03-12 ### Added - Added Escalating usecase - Added Tester usecase - Added Remote Viewer usecase ### Changed - Web developments have been created with a modern tech stack using Webpack, Vue and Bulma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v3.0.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.0.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v2.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Feb 2019 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Smart IVR 2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.0:
## [2.0] - 2019-02-29 ### New - First release of Smart IVR 2.0 - New PBX-SIP Connect - New TTS-HTTP/MRCP - New ASR-HTTP/MRCP Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us at our Spanish Website!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 14:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/welcome-interaccionesdigitales/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Interactive Powers in Spanish: Interacciones Digitales Interactive Powers is pleased to announce the release of our new spanish website called &amp;ldquo;Interacciones Digitales&amp;rdquo;, designed with a fresh new look and user-friendly responsive navigation, updated with the latest information about our products. We hope you will enjoy our new site in spanish. Our goal with new website is to provide our spanish speaker visitors and customers an easier way to learn about our solutions and cloud services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.5.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.5.1 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.5.1:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Communication Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on &amp;ldquo;Communication Platform as a Service&amp;rdquo; or CPaaS at last year 2018 VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
CPaaS is the new cloud&amp;rsquo;s Game Changer The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy New Year!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Dec 2018 16:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and Christmas season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners, employees, providers, friends and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you again for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2018!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day-2018/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2018, 11th Anniversary Freak Conferences, on November 14th &amp;amp; 15th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about CPaaS for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “Communications Platform as a Service”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation.
We would like to thank our partners, USA-VOIP and Avanzada7, and all the people who were involved in organizing the event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.3.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.3.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a hot fix for Firefox Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.1:
## [3.3.1] - 2018-11-13 ### Added - If the Videoplayer only finds one record, it&amp;#39;s preselected ### Fixed - Resized calling message for mobile devices - Fixed SDP negotiations from Firefox 63+ Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us at VoIP2Day to talk about Communications Platform as a Service</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Nov 2018 20:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Communications Platform as a Service at next VoIP2DAY2018 11th Freak Conferences edition:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
Keynote: Communications Platform as a Service Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 14th, 2018 Time: 12:30pm Synopsis The level of maturity of the services in the cloud is reaching a new point of evolution for the telecommunications platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, Exevi!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-itsmf-vision18/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended itSMF VISION18, Conferences, on October 25th, at LA NAVE del Ayuntamiento de Madrid. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Voicebots for OTRS in the presentation entitled “OTRS and Voicebots: First Steps for the IA Automation of the Service Desk”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in Voicebots exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoIP2Day 2018: 11th Freak Conferences</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2018/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 11th edition of VOIP2DAY, the major event about Voice over IP of the year in Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at VoIP2DAY 2018: November 14th &amp;amp; 15th at Wanda Metropolitano Stadium, Madrid. We will share latest industry news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all companies and visitors of the main sector of Telephony and Comunications in Europe and Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2018/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky 👻 Halloween 🎃 night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VISION18: 13th edition itSMF National Congress</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itsmf-vision18/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-itsmf-vision18/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 13th edition of the &amp;ldquo;Congreso Nacional VISION18&amp;rdquo;, the major IT &amp;amp; Digital Transformation event from itSMF Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at Vision18 congress October 25th at Centro de Innovación LA NAVE del Ayuntamiento de Madrid - Calle Cifuentes, 5, 28021 Madrid. We will share latest technologies news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all startups, companies and visitors.
We are really pleased to be at itSMF - VISION18 with our partner Exevi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Hosting: Turnkey Solutions</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Oct 2018 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-cloud-hosting/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Unsplash. Creative Commons Turnkey Solutions are designed to provide a quick startup without any IT requirement for your business. Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Sep 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.3.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.3.0:
## [3.3.0] - 2018-09-14 ### Added - Added Log rotation utility ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.js library (v2.5.0) - Updated Videocall usecase (UX improvement) - Updated the webrtc-gateway internal core Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.5.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.5.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.5.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.5.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.4.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.4.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.4.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.4.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0 · 2.4.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added `videoStream` and `videoEnabled` option parameters in the SplitAgent module - Added `onReadyLocalAudio`, `onAcceptedData` and `onScreensharingClosed` events in the SplitClient module - Added `onAcceptedData` and `onReadyLocalStream` events in the SplitAgent module - Added a mechanism that guarantees the sending of files through the Datachannel - Added `onFileTransferOk` and `onFileTransferKo` events in the modules that use the Datachannel - Added `startScreensharing` and `stopScreensharing` actions in the SplitClient module - Added `notify` method in the following modules: SplitClient and SplitAgent - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated recording mode in the SPLIT modules ### Fixed - Fixed the use of the debug parameter at library level ## [2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Real-Time Communications applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/real-time-communications-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 20:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/real-time-communications-applications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Real-time Communications applications to streamline your online business. Video RTC platforms are changing the way real-time communications are developed and delivered. It is fast becoming the platform of choice for rapidly building enterprise class real-time voice and video applications. Our communications platform is 100% cloud ready, offering continuous evolution, scalability and high availability.
Video chat is a clearer and modern way to communicate for online businesses</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conversational IVR applications</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/conversational-ivr-applications/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons Conversational IVR applications to improve your customer experience in phone services. Tradicional IVR systems have been built as limited DTMF and direct IVR dialogs for a long time. Yet it is not a secret that the experience using those solutions has is rather poor. In 70% of those interactions, the end users end up frustrated; at “best” case scenario are rerouted to a human agent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Turnkey</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/turnkey-solutions/</guid>
      <description>The Turnkey Solutions for your business Our Turnkey Portfolio offers flexibility and deliver significant savings to enterprises or service providers. These pay-as-you-go products can be standalone or used in combination to provide an end to end communication services for many kind of businesses over WebRTC, RTMP, VoIP to PSTN networks.
Forget technology, it&amp;rsquo;s about business. Web Dialer. Make Voice Calls from any modern Web Browser
Web Dialer allows all your customers and users to make phone calls directly to your PBX, IVR, Call Center from any desktop web browser (Firefox, Chrome, IE, Safari, Opera,…).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Jun 2018 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.2.1 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes some improvements and a crital &amp;ldquo;hot fix&amp;rdquo; for Firefox 6+ Web Browsers. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.1:
## [3.2.1] - 2018-06-08 ### Fixed - Fixed compatibility of all modules with Firefox 60+ ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2018 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.2.0:
## [3.2.0] - 2018-05-15 ### Added - Added Remote Viewer usecase as extension - Added WebRTC communication verification functions - Added possibility to transfer a call using the SPLIT usecases - Added a GET parameter to set the CallerID from the URL in the Webclient usecase ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.1.0:
## [3.1.0] - 2018-01-16 ### Added - Added the possibility of configuring different SPLIT scenarios at Flavour level - Added `autoRecording` option in the SPLIT Agent usecase - Added texts option in the SPLIT usecase - Added FileSharing in the Webclient usecase - Added ScreenSharing in the Webclient usecase - Added possibility to show a message until the Video agent is accepted - Added `split_id_strategy` in the VideoGateway - Added Safari iOS 11 support in the SplitClient module (Audio mode) ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.3.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.3.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.3.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3.0:
## [1.3.0] - 2018-01-08 ### Added - Favicon in Split Use Case (Webclient and Agent) ### Changed - The default look for the agent webphone is now &amp;#39;agent&amp;#39; - Removed extra HTML code that was in the index.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Merry Christmas &amp; Happy Holidays!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/merry-christmas-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers May peace, prosperity, and happiness be yours throughout Christmas and New Year! At the close of another year, we gratefully want to wish you a warm and happy holiday season! We are deeply grateful and thankful to all our partners and customers for striving to succeed together. Thank you for your confidence and loyalty and let season’s holidays be sweet and simple for you and your families.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2017 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Cloud API for Voice over IP at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about the rise of a new generation of cloud resources and services.
The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate. We are experiencing an Internet revolution that begins to affect basic services that we now operate with specific devices or business systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you, VoIP2Day 2017!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2017 12:12:48 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/thank-voip2day/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers attended VoIP2Day 2017, 10th Anniversary Conferences, on November 16th, at Wanda Metropolitano. Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers, talked about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP in the presentation entitled “The Cloud API revolution is coming.”
We are delighted with the success of the event and the warm welcome of our participation. Interest of the public in voice integration APIs exceeded all our expectations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Cloud API Revolution is Coming to VoIP</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Nov 2017 12:14:39 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conference-voip2day2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers &amp;amp; VoIP2DAY Iván Sixto, founder of Interactive Powers will be pleased to speak about Cloud API’s novelties for Voice over IP at next VoIP2DAY2017 10th Anniversary Conferences:
Ivan Sixto Founder, CEO, Business Development
Follow him on Linkedin
Keynote: The Cloud API Revolution is coming to VoIP Location: Madrid, Wanda Metropolitano Stadium Keynote: November 16th, 2017 Time: 10:00am Synopsis Digital Transformation is changing the way in which we propose the systems we use to communicate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VoIP2Day 2017: 10th Conferences Anniversary</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2017 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/next-voip2day-2017/</guid>
      <description>Be ready to assist at the 10th edition of VOIP2DAY, the major event about Voice over IP of the year in Spain! As you may know, Interactive Powers will be speaking at VoIP2DAY 2017: November 15th &amp;amp; 16th at Wanda Metropolitano Stadium, Madrid. We will share latest industry news, knowledges, experiences, trends with all companies and visitors of the main sector of Telephony and Comunications in Europe and Latin America.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy Halloween!</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 20:40:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/happy-halloween-2017/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Pexels, Creative Commons We want to wish you a dreadful and spooky Halloween night from all Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; team.
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v3.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-3.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v3.0.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 3.0.0:
## [3.0.0] - 2017-10-03 ### Added - Added a new usecase: Videocall - Added return button inside the usecases - Added list of platform extensions in the landing page ### Changed - Updated VideoRTC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>VideoRTC.js (API) v2.0.0</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.0.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-js-2.0.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our API Framework for Javascript VideoRTC.js v2.0.0 has been released for suitable for Web Developments and Mobile SDK . All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.0.0 · 2.0.0:
# Change Log All notable changes to this project will be documented in this file. ## [1.0.0] - 2017-02-10 ### First release ## [1.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added VoiceProcessor feature in the Videoroom module - Added `disconnect()` method for destroy a session with the VideoGateway - Added `closeUsecase()` method for close a use case with the VideoGateway (All usecases) - Added download link of VideoRTC Screensharing extension for Chrome - Added `videoRate` and `screenRate` parameters in the `call()` method (Split Client) - Added timestamp in Videomail messages to achieve multiple records with the same id/name ### Changed - Updated `webrtc-adapter` version release to `3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 11:06:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest VoiceXML IVR features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of main features (VoiceXML):
Dashboard VoiceXML editor Applications SIP Connectivity Speech Connectors CDR Reporting Settings Logs Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (RTMP)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 15:00:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-rtmp/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (RTMP) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (RTMP):
SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Playground (Flash Configurator) Click-to-call (Webclient) Documentation Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Showroom · Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Sep 2017 00:00:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/showroom-videortc-webrtc/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Request your Demo Get in touch today and meet online one of our sales consultant or manager. We will be pleased to show you our latest Video RTC Gateway (WebRTC) features and applications.
Showroom:
http://www.ivrpowers.com/showroom/
List of Use Cases (WebRTC):
Videoroom (multi-conference) Private room (ID/password) SPLIT Agent (SIP Connect) Click-to-call (Webclient) Videomail (post a video message) Videoplayer (play single and dual video records) Meeting Point (OAuth Authentication Meetings) Contact us To contact our Sales, you have to send a meeting request to schedule your online demo according to your business requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on Google&#43;</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-googleplus/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own Google+ page! Meet more people interested on the latest collections and trends. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Google+ page at https://plus.google.com/110474380379482164317/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.2.0:
## [2.2.0] - 2017-07-27 ### Added - Added interval Watchdog - Added autocall GET parameter to the Webclient URL usecase - Added overprint logo in the Webclient usecase Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Value of Video Communication</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2017 10:13:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/general/conferencevoip2day/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers (IVRPowers) founder CEO, Iván Sixto, gave a conference about min trends on Video Communications for Contact Centers at last VoIP2Day Event. He provided a general overview of the current situation about real-time communications channels. Users’ behaviors and preferences are changing as we are always connected, specially through their mobile devices. It means a huge amount of data is circulating. However, we don’t use anymore our mobile phones just to call.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interactive Powers is on LinkedIn</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 12:40:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/follow-linkedin/</guid>
      <description>Interactive Powers has its own LinkedIn page! Meet more people interested on the latest trends on #RTC and #IVR. And if you have any questions feel free to contact us.
Follow our Linkedin page at https://www.linkedin.com/company/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Instagram</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 11:44:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-instagram/</guid>
      <description>You can now follow us on Instagram!. We want to share our best tech pictures with you. Products, trends, promotions, innovations, conferences, updates&amp;hellip;
We are waiting you! at https://www.instagram.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Facebook</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2017 11:23:01 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followfacebook/</guid>
      <description>Do not forget to follow us on Facebook. You can contact us and stay updated on all that’s going on our company and on the latest news about #RTC or #IVR.
Join us and stay tuned for new information at https://www.facebook.com/ivrpowers/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join us on Tumblr</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 12:47:15 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/join-tumblr/</guid>
      <description>You can easily track what’s happening by following us on Tumblr. Keep up to date about the most advanced #RTC and #IVR solutions and breakthrough technologies.
Follow us at http://tumblr.ivrpowers.com/
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (WebRTC) v2.1</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-webrtc-2.1.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway WebRTC) v2.1.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 2.1.0:
## [2.1.0] - 2017-04-17 ### Added - Added Snapshot feature in the Split Agent usecase - VideoGateway notifies to participants when a Split session is finished - Added Autoclose feature in the Split Agent usecase - Added `split_screen_bitrate` in the Split configuration file - Added `videorate` and `screenrate` parameters in the `call_split` request - Added Quality selector in the Webclient usecase - Added sound notification when a message is received in the Split Agent usecase - Added sound notificator handle (Mute/Unmute) in LiveChat mode - Added visual notificacion when a file is sent in the Split Agent usecase - Added icon that identifies the file type sent/received - Added Drop feature for File Sharing (Agent -&amp;gt; Client) - Added Emoji feature in LiveChat (Webclient and Split Agent) - Added FullScreen mode in ScreenSharing (Webclient) - Added SplitAgent configuration feature via Flavour (Autoclose, Emoji.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Follow us on Twitter</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/socials/followus-twitter/</guid>
      <description>Be sure to follow us on Twitter with great brand updates, promotions and news about all things RTC or IVR. Our hand is @ivrpowers and our favorite hashtags right now are #RTC and #IVR.
Give us a shout out! https://twitter.com/ivrpowers
Interactive Powers - Streamline your business communications</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video RTC (RTMP) v1.2</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-video-rtc-rtmp-1.2.0/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new Video RTC (Gateway RTMP) v1.2.0 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.2.0:
## [1.2.0] - 2017-01-18 ### Added - GET parameters to customize some variables of the client and agent flashphones { Action: parameter=[possible values] (default) ---------------------------------------------- Enable video: video=[true|false] (false) Video quality: quality=[1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Smart IVR v1.3</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2017 00:20:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/updates/update-voicexml-ivr-13.1/</guid>
      <description>Release Note We are pleased to announce that our new VoiceXML IVR 1.3 has been released for suitable production services. This new version includes a lot of improvements and new features. All users with previous maintained versions can upgrade today. Please contact our support!
ChangeLog Version 1.3:
## [1.3] - 2016-06 ### Added - Initialization of the freepbx_security.log during the fail2ban installation if not exists - Added pagination for CDR results - Added Presence extras source files - Added the extras module installation to the installation process - Added the extras module update to the update process ### Changed - Fixed posible exploit in the vxml editor directory browser - Fixed a typo in the web uninstallation steps - Updated Openvxi V12.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: Video RTC</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2017 11:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-rtc/</guid>
      <description>The Video Real Time Communications Platform Our Video Gateway connects peers or endpoints between WebRTC, RTMP and SIP technology to create advanced Video services. It works in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.
Cloud Ready. Our Video Gateway solutions are software based and ready to run over Cloud environments and Virtual Servers. You can setup our Video RTC platforms over Amazon EC2 servers or any Private/Public Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know our Products: VoiceXML IVR</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2017 13:25:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/voicexml-ivr/</guid>
      <description>The Interactive Voice Response Platform Our VoiceXML IVR software platform gives operators and solution providers the ability to rapidly develop and deploy innovative voice applications from VoIP to PSTN networks.
This powerful IVR solution is fully compliant with the W3C’s VoiceXML 2.1 specification and is integrated with automatic speech recognition (ASR) and text-to-speech (TTS) software to enable advanced interactive services, and real-time calling applications.
It can be installed in common hardware or Cloud VM servers configurations, providing a highly scalable base system to meet all customers’ business and technical requirements.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
