<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>kpi on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kpi/</link>
    <description>Recent content in kpi on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/kpi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Video Calling KPI Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-calling-kpi-dashboard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 10:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/products/video-calling-kpi-dashboard/</guid>
      <description>Source: Interactive Powers. Creative Commons Introducing New KPI Dashboard: Best Performance Tracking We are excited to announce the latest update to our Web ACD 1.21 platform, which introduces a cutting-edge KPI Dashboard. This significant enhancement represents a major leap forward in our system&amp;rsquo;s capabilities and promises to improve the user experience for our clients.
The newly implemented KPI Dashboard offers a comprehensive and intuitive view of critical productivity metrics, meticulously designed to cater to the needs of both Supervisors and Agents.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Call / Contact Center metrics (KPI)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-call-contact-center-metrics-kpi/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 12:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/video-call-contact-center-metrics-kpi/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers Speeding up your queue, and increasing customer satisfaction metrics, can be as simple as giving your video agents more power to do their job. Our approach to video communications allows to deliver security, scalability, and reliability to our customers. Ensure that your strategic plans for this year will improve both the employee and customer experience. An exceptional employee experience fuels an unparalleled customer experience, two key ingredients necessary to retain customer loyalty, drive new customer acquisition, and gain a competitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Net Promoter Score (NPS)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/net-promoter-score-nps/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/net-promoter-score-nps/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does NPS differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center? What is a Net Promoter Score (NPS)? The Net Promoter Score (NPS) is an index ranging from -100 to 100 that measures the willingness of customers to recommend a company&amp;rsquo;s products or services to others. It is used as a proxy for gauging the customer&amp;rsquo;s overall satisfaction with a company&amp;rsquo;s product or service and the customer&amp;rsquo;s loyalty to the brand.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Effort Score (CES)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-effort-score-ces/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-effort-score-ces/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does CES differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center? What is a Customer Effort Score (CES)? A Customer Effort Score (CES) is a service metric that measures how much effort customers put in to interact with your business. These interactions can be something like how much effort it takes to use your product or service or how easy it was for them to have a problem solved by your service reps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Average Handle Time  Score (AHT)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/average-handle-time-score-aht/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/average-handle-time-score-aht/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does AHT differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center? What is a Average Handle Time Score (AHT)? When you work in customer support, you know how important it is to optimize your handle times. But while it’s clearly important to reduce average handling time at a Call / Contact Center, it’s not always that simple. Average handle time (AHT) is, as you’ve probably guessed, the average amount of time that a customer call takes from start to finish a process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Call Resolution Score (FCR)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/first-call-resolution-score-fcr/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/first-call-resolution-score-fcr/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does FCR differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center? What is a First Call Resolution Score (FCR)? The First Call Resolution (FCR) can come in handy as one of many important metrics to keep track of in the pursuit of exceptional customer service. Furthermore, FCR measures a company&amp;rsquo;s ability to resolve phone calls, chats, emails, video calls, and website customer interactions resolved on the first contact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customer Satisfaction Score (CSAT)</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-satisfaction-score-csat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jan 2022 21:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/customer-satisfaction-score-csat/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Interactive Powers How does CSAT differ from Phone and Video interactions in your Call / Contact Center? What is a Customer Satisfaction Score (CSAT)? A big strength of Customer Satisfaction Score (CSTA) is an easy way to close the loop on a customer interaction and determine whether or not it was effective in producing happiness. If for some reason the experience wasn&amp;rsquo;t satisfactory, it&amp;rsquo;s easy to pinpoint that moment and take actions to remedy the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
