<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Microsoft on Blog</title>
    <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/microsoft/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Microsoft on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/microsoft/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>TTS-API connectors updated!</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/cloud-tts-connector-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/cloud-tts-connector-update/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45+ Languages &amp;amp; 300+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Amazon, Google and Microsoft Cloud TTS-API Integration. Natural Language over the Phone&amp;hellip; All of you know that cognitive services are growing this days, and that&amp;rsquo;s why today we&amp;rsquo;re going to talk about a brand-new API, &amp;ldquo;Text to speech&amp;rdquo;. This API can convert text into natural voice in just a few seconds even less. There are a lot of Cloud Speech APIs for Text To Speech, but we will focus on the Cloud Giants: Google Cloud, Microsoft Azure and Amazon Web Services.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft TTS connector</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/microsoft-tts-connector/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers Interactive Powers introduces 45 Languages &amp;amp; 75+ additional Text-to-Speech voices with Microsoft Azure TTS Integration About Microsoft&amp;hellip; Microsoft like Google provides his own Text To Speech API. It is quite big and here are some of its features: More than 75 voices over 45 languages.
 Parameters for speed, pitch, volume, pronunciation, and additional pauses Custom voice models for developers and enterprises Neural Voices technology  For more information, read the Microsoft Documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Edge moves to Chromium in 2019</title>
      <link>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/microsoft-edge-chromium-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/news/microsoft-edge-chromium-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Image source: Interactive Powers&amp;rsquo; elaboration Microsoft annonces officialy that Edge will become a Chromium-based browser in early 2019! Microsoft is reworking its Edge browser on Windows 10 so that it will based on the Chromium open source project. Microsoft CVP Joe Belfiore made a big announcement and explained that it was all about creating “better web compatibility for our customers and less fragmentation of the web for all web developers.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>