<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pbx on Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/pbx/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pbx on Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:05 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.ivrpowers.com/tags/pbx/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is PBX?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-pbx/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 00:00:05 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/technologies/what-is-pbx/</guid>
      <description>A Private Branch Exchange (PBX) is a telephone system within an enterprise that switches calls between users on local lines, while enabling all users to share a certain number of external phone lines. In contrast to a public switched telephone network (PSTN), the main purpose of a PBX is to save the cost of requiring a line for each user to the telephone company&amp;rsquo;s central office.
Used as a business telephone system or private telephone network, a PBX is owned and operated by the enterprise rather than the telephone company &amp;ndash; the telephone company of which may be considered a supplier or service provider, however.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Channels for your Business</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 00:20:30 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/marketing/video-channels-for-your-business/</guid>
      <description>Photo source: Freepik Creative Commons. Build consistent, effective, personalized engagements across Video channels with Voice, Video, Live Chat, File Sharing, Screen Sharing, Co-browsing…. The most successful enterprises are defined by their ability to communicate. Today that means meeting consumers where they hangout – online, on multiple platforms like: Skype, FaceTime, WhatsApp, Telegram, Zoom, Microsoft Teams…
There’s no doubt that the name of the game today when we speak of Omnichannel Customer Experience is convenience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to improve your PBX with Conversational AI?</title>
      <link>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Feb 2020 18:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.ivrpowers.com/post/customerengagement/how-to-improve-your-pbx-with-conversational-ai/</guid>
      <description>The Old Way In The New Digital Age, standards commons PBX functions used by most companies are weighing down Customer Experience (CX) making tedious to contact their phone services or customer assistance.
Photo source: Pixabay. Creative Commons What most companies still doing…
DTMF Menus. Most PBX use touch tone menus to select departments, services or key an extension. Of course, everybody may knows how to press a key, but it’s not really confortable to do this with hands free, driving or when you don’t get the right option…</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
